<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<data ts="2014-04-15 17:00:00">
	<active>
		<news id="20140415_1" date="2014-04-15">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Ernest Borel appears in TIME Sweet TIME exhibition]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[
				La Chaux-de-Fonds, Switzerland, is the global capital of watchmaking and its watchmaking museum is the most beautiful in the world. 2014 marks the 40 years of the current building Musée International d'Horlogerie (The international Watchmaking Museum) in La Chaux-de-Fonds. The anniversary exhibition aims to demonstrate the relevance of the increase in its collections. Visitors are invited to browse through the entire museum to discover 40 highlights.

				The international Watchmaking Museum has asked watch companies to donate contemporary pieces in a move to conserve these items which, in addition to being technical or prestige items, are part of the heritage and could provide a window for future generations into the ingenuity and artistic endeavours of the experts of today. 

				More than 30 companies including Ernest Borel responded to the museum’s request, 44 timepieces including 2 Ernest Borel antique watches, are exhibited in two special display cases. Ernest Borel was established in Switzerland since 1856. The company has a deep and profound watch-making culture of more than 150 years, bringing countless romantic sentiments to couples over the years with classic designs. The couple logo is also very well known to the public. Ernest Borel is so proud and pleased to showcase the valuable antique watch to all.

				One the other hand, the latest Cocktail Collection is exhibited in the watch showcase, it is one of the most representative models of Ernest Borel. Cocktail Collection has a patent for its external structure since it was introduced in 1940s. The ultra-slim hollow sub-dial rotates in accordance, forming the dynamic kaleidoscopic pattern keeping extending from inward to outward. The new generation of Cocktail Collection recreates classic in color, creativity and uniqueness and displays a perfect blend of physical mechanics, classical aesthetics and Swiss exquisite watchmaking techniques. Come and visit the International Watchmaking Museum if you are interested. For exhibition details, please visit <a href="http://www.mih.ch">http://www.mih.ch</a>.
				]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2014</tag>
				<tag>2013</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20140211_1" date="2014-02-11">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Ernest Borel in Baselworld 2014 --- Mar 27 - Apr 3]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[
The 42nd BASELWORLD 2014 (Basel Watch Fair) will be held in Basel, Switzerland. 
Ernest Borel will participate in the 2014 BaselWorld and we are pleased to invite you to discover the latest models of Ernest Borel Timepieces. 
Do visit us at our booth located in Hall 2.2 Hall of Visions First Avenue – Booth no. B05.
				]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20140211_1_1">
					<![CDATA[Caption1]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20140211_1_2">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2014</tag>
				<tag>2013</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20140121_1" date="2014-01-21">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Ernest Borel appears in TIME Sweet TIME exhibition]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[
				Swiss Ernest Borel made its official launch of New Retro Collection couple watches, which is entitled “Warm New Year Gift, Romantic Couple Watches,” in Chengdu on the 17th of January, 2014. Swiss made Ernest Borel watches across 158 years have showed up for the most romantic and luxurious new year exhibition tour in Chengdu known as “the Land of Abundance.”  Mr. Su Da, Asia Pacific Chief Executive Officer of Ernest Borel, and Mr. Raymond Lam, the brand ambassador, attended the event together to announce the debut of New Retro Collection couple watches. 
				On that day, Swiss made Ernest Borel watches have arrived at the most beautiful city of Southwest China, Chengdu, also called the City of Hibiscus, to experience a romantic encounter with Chunxi Road, which is also nicknamed as the “Hundred Year Gold Street.” Similar to that Chunxi street has gone through hundred years of testing and accumulation but is still flourishing in the ever changing times, Ernest Borel has always insisted on the heritage of exquisite watchmaking craftsmanship and romantic legendary story. Adhering to the brand philosophy of “Romantic Moments, A life Companion” and the spirit of pursuing “excellence,” Ernest Borel watches combines traditional Swiss watchmaking craftsmanship with high-end techniques to bring customers more stylish, elegant, classic, romantic and high-tech wristwatches.  
				According to Mr. Su Da, “Chengdu’s long history, rich cultural heritage and comfortable urban pace just coincide with the brand philosophy we have pursued and insisted on. Swiss Ernest Borel has attached itself to China for over one hundred years since it entered into China in 1903. During which, the brand has witnessed countless romantic moments of couples, so that we hope to continue the romantic love in Chengdu and share it with people with a romantic attitude to life, leading them to enjoy romantic moments in theirlives.” 
				The grand opening ceremony for the new collection of Swiss made Ernest Borel watches began with the violin and guitar ensemble, where the perfect classical and modern combination has showed the audience a magnificent visual feast. The ceremony reached its climax when Mr. Raymond Lam, both the special guest of this event and the brand ambassador, appeared and attracted greatest attention. As a renowned artist in the Asia-Pacific region, Raymond is the pop idol that has won the hearts of millions of fans. Mr. Su Da attended the event with Raymond to announce the debut of New Retro Collection couple watches, and as a gift, he gave Raymond a watch with precise shape, clean lines, understated natural curvature and harmonious geometric elements. Raymond  said that “Since Ernest Borel is the Swiss brand with a 158-year long history and rich cultural heritage, it can evoke people’s desires and dreams for better and romantic life in their deepest heart. It is a reliable brand."  
				As the event day was also the opening ceremony of “Romantic journey of Swiss Ernest Borel Watches in the City of Hibiscus,” Raymond sent the gift with Shu brocade and wished good luck for this special event. When asked why he chose the Shu brocade as a gift, he replied: “Shu brocade is one of the distinctive products in Sichuan and is also known as the leading one of four famous brocades in China. At this special moment, I sent this Sichuan brocade with the brand philosophy, “Romantic Moments, A life Companion,” embroidered on it, to wish Ernest Borel a successful event for the ‘Romantic Journey in the City of Hibiscus.’”  The event for romantic journey in the City of Hibiscus started by the “Romantic Prince”, Mr. Raymond Lam, will convene 12 pairs of romantic couples from the city to find 12 romantic dating places with Ernest Borel together. The brand will help more romantic lovers witness happiness in Chengdu, this historic fashion city. In the event, Raymond enjoyed the interaction with his fans in a very warm atmosphere until nightfall, where the event has successfully ended under dazzling lights.
				]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20140121_1_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20140121_1_2">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20140121_1_3">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2014</tag>
				<tag>2013</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20140107_1" date="2014-01-07">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Ernest Borel appears in TIME Sweet TIME exhibition]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[
				4th January 2014, Ernest Borel’s Warm New Year Gift, Romantic Couple Watches  Swiss Ernest Borel made its official launch of New Retro Collection couple watches in Liuzhou, Guangxi.  With the 158 years of history, the brand began its romantic journey here with the traditional Swiss watchmaking craftsmanship and elegant, classic lifestyle.  Mr. Su Da, Asia Pacific Chief Executive Officer of Ernest Borel, and Miss Angie Chiu, the brand ambassador, announced the debut of new automatic couple watches in its Retro Collection. 

				Liuzhou is romantic in that the warm landscapes in the winter of the south are beautiful, poetic, and mesmerizing.  Similarly, after 158 years of testing and accumulation, Swiss Ernest Borel watches have always insisted on the heritage of exquisite watchmaking craftsmanship and romantic legendary story.  Adhering to the brand philosophy of “Romantic Moments, A life Companion” and the spirit of pursuing “excellence” while following the trend of the time, Ernest Borel watches combines traditional Swiss watchmaking craftsmanship with high-end techniques to bring customers more stylish, elegant, classic, romantic and high-tech watches.  According to Mr. Su Da, “Liuzhou’s status in the territory of Ernest Borel's development in China cannot be ignored; it has become one of the most important Ernest Borel watch markets.  With this Swiss Ernest Borel new product opening, we hope to help customers develop a romantic and elegant attitude to life.”

				On that day, Mr. Su Da, Asia Pacific Chief Executive Officer of Ernest Borel, and Miss Angie Chiu, announced the debut of new automatic couple watches in its Retro Collection.  The unparalleled romantic aesthetics of automatic couple watches in Retro Collection displays the ultimate retro glamour.  Its precise shape, clean lines, understated natural curvature and harmonious geometric elements all contribute to the elegant style. 

				The ceremony reached its climax when Angie Chiu, the brand ambassador, appeared and attracted greatest attention.  As one of pivotal actresses in Hong Kong, the dignified and gracious Angie Chiu known as “the classic beauty of China, the gorgeous Asian woman,” represents the brand image of elegant temperament and romantic style.  After the opening, Mr. Su Da gave a pair of charming gifts, the couple watches in Retro Collection, to Miss Angie Chiu and her husband.  As a great model of romantic love, this couple who treat each other with respect perfectly interpreted Retro Collection automatic couple watches with their love stories.

				 After the event, Miss Angie Chiu showed up in the tour area of Swiss Ernest Borel watches and signed her name on the light box and interacted with her fans, building a friendly and warm atmosphere.  Just as Mr. Su Da said, “Since its establishment in 1856, the Swiss Ernest Borel has been committed to spreading the romantic and elegant lifestyle to every corner of the world.  We also believe that the SwissErnest Borel watches can forge ahead and continue to write the legend of high-end watches! "

				]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20140107_1_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20140107_1_2">
					<![CDATA[]]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20140107_1_3">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2014</tag>
				<tag>2013</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20131219_1" date="2013-12-19">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Ernest Borel appears in TIME Sweet TIME exhibition]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[
				Ernest Borel celebrated its grand opening ceremony of Xi’an Bell Tower flagship store and the debut of Retro Collection I in Xi’an on December 14, 2013. The 157-year-old brand was excited to introduce their masterpieces to Xi’an, the ancient capital with thousand years of brilliant civilization, starting a conversation with this cultural city with long history and also paying tribute to the rich heritage of Qicheng. Mr. Su Da, Asia Pacific Chief Executive Officer of Ernest Borel, and Raymond Lam, the brand ambassador, attended the event, cut the ribbon for the new store opening ceremony, and announced the debut of new automatic watches, Retro Collection I.

			    Xi’an Bell Tower, the landmark building located in the most prosperous downtown area, is vast and elegant, mysterious and romantic with more than 600 years of history, telling the stories and legends of this Chinese ancient capital. Similarly, after 157 years of testing and accumulation, Ernest Borel has always insisted on the heritage of exquisite watchmaking craftsmanship and romantic legendary story. Adhering to the brand philosophy of “Romance in Heart” and the spirit of pursuing excellence while following the trend of the time, Ernest Borel combines traditional Swiss watchmaking craftsmanship with high-end techniques to bring customers more stylish, elegant, classic, romantic and high-tech watches. In this way, Ernest Borel has built its flagship store at Xi’an Bell Tower to pay tribute to both Chinese culture and classic legends.

				According to Mr. Su Da, “Xi’an is one of the four world's most famous ancient capitals, ranking first among Chinese ancient cities. It is not only the birthplace of Chinese civilization, representing Chinese culture; it is also an innovative and stylish modern city. Xi’an has cultural heritage with grace and elegance Ernest Borel understands; its fashion sense also has resonance for the brand. In 2013, the development of Ernest Borel in China’s watch market entered a new accelerated period. As an ancient capital of Chinese civilization, Xi'an’s status in the territory of China's development cannot be underestimated; it has become one of the most important Ernest Borel watch markets. With this Ernest Borel new flagship store in Xi'an, we hope to help customers develop a romantic and elegant attitude to life. I believe the opening of Xi’an Bell Tower flagship store will bring new vitality to the city!”

				On that day, Ernest Borel watches celebrated the grand opening ceremony of Xi’an flagship store and the debut of automatic watches, new Retro Collection I. The ceremony reached its climax when Raymond Lam, the brand ambassador, appeared and attracted greatest attention.  As a renowned artist in the Asia-Pacific region, Raymond Lam is the pop idol that has won the hearts of millions of fans and also the representative of elegant and romantic style. Mr. Su Da gave Raymond the stylish gift, a new model of automatic watches - Retro Collection 8380, whose delicate design and exquisite craftsmanship highlight the brand’s excellent artistic taste and elegant temperament. After the ceremony, Raymond Lam attended Ernest Borel’s cocktail party and unveiled their favorite Christmas watches. Mr. Raymond Lam enjoyed the interaction with his fans in a very warm atmosphere.

				When asked about his favorite Christmas gift, Raymond Lam said Retro Collection I would be the best choice for Christmas gifts for its perfect combination of vintage art and excellent workmanship, quality movement and unique design, and original style and superior performance.   This model can both express romantic feelings and feature aesthetic and practical functions.
				]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20131219_1_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20131219_1_2">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20131219_1_3">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2013</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20130902_1" date="2013-09-02">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Ernest Borel appears in TIME Sweet TIME exhibition]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[
				(Hong Kong – 2 September 2013) Ernest Borel today hosted a grand ceremony in Hong Kong to mark the appointment of German gymnast and Olympic medallist Marcel Nguyen as the global ambassador of the 157-year Swiss timepiece brand. During the event, the prince of gymnastics formally assumed his role and also put on a dashing array of watches from Ernest Borel's brand new Retro Collection, effortlessly highlighting the series' classic elegance and modern sophistication.

			    At the 2012 London Olympics, Marcel stunned the world with his brilliant performance on the gym floor and came out as the third German gymnast in 76 years to have won an Olympic medal. His impressive gymnastic skills, striking physique and affable smile have grabbed headlines around the world, making him one of the fastest rising stars in the sports world. In every aspect, the 25-year-old athlete is the perfect figure to represent Ernest Borel. For one thing, his recognised achievement as an athlete and the inch-perfect precision with which he performs all manner of difficult moves are in the same vein as Ernest Borel's sophisticated watchmaking art. The immense confidence, charisma and charm that the Munich-born gymnast exudes echo the unique allure and romantic style of Ernest Borel's design.

				Following the ceremony, Marcel said: "I am absolutely delighted and excited to be the global ambassador of Ernest Borel. As a professional gymnast, every move I make on the gym floor has to be precise and elegant and demonstrate my skills. When Ernest Borel first approached me, it occurred to me that gymnastics had a lot in common with a magnificent timepiece brand. Ernest Borel's superb watchmaking art and romantic, classic image are second to none. So I did not hesitate for a moment about Ernest Borel's invitation."

				"Recently I was invited to Ernest Borel's factory in Switzerland to learn how to assemble watch components. It was an eye-opening experience that brought me closer to understanding the highly sophisticated and complex work that goes into watchmaking at Ernest Borel. It is a procedure that somewhat echoes what I do professionally. Both involve enormous concentration, a lot of trying and testing and pursuit for perfection."

				Speaking of Marcel's appointment, Mr. Renaud de Retz, Chief Executive Officer of Ernest Borel said: "Ernest Borel is celebrated for its romantic, elegant and stylish design. For more than a century, the romantic and elegant philosophy of the brand has fulfilled the desires of those with discerning taste. It is with great delight and excitement that we have invited the internationally renowned Olympic medallist Mr. Marcel Nguyen to be Ernest Borel's global ambassador. As the prince of gymnastics, Mr. Nguyen's personal aura, talent and achievements are a perfect fit for Ernest Borel's unparalleled status and exquisite watchmaking art, and for presenting our brand new Retro Collection. Besides, our brand logo features a dancing couple to reflect the elegance and romance associated with the brand. Both dancing and gymnastics are about grace and style, which makes the choice of Mr. Nguyen all the more fitting as the brand's global ambassador."

				Officially unveiled today, the Retro Collection is Ernest Borel's signature collection in 2013. Its design is characterised by dual time function, Roman numerals and a variety of classic motifs. Grounded on the original collection's classic retro design 70 years ago, the new version pays tributes to the classics and is fused with modern elegance and cutting edge watchmaking technology, highlighting aesthetics and functionality in equal measure. The Retro collection is a limited edition of 1,000 pieces released worldwide, with each piece carrying a serial number in a unique certificate that proves the watch is Swiss made. It is the first masterpiece collection presented by Ernest Borel to celebrate our affiliation with Marcel.

				The appointment of Marcel follows the naming of Asian pop diva Kelly Chen as Ernest Borel's "Goddess of Romance" in March 2010, when a grand ceremony was held in Shanghai to celebrate Kelly appointment. As Ernest Borel's Cocktail Collection is unveiled this year, the Hong Kong-born star is now in the limelight, displaying the brand's latest Cocktail Collection in her elegance and grace. "This collection is an absolute masterpiece. I love the special visual effect that plays with the brilliant colours. The incredible precision with which the watches are made is simply in keeping with Ernest Borel's sophisticated watchmaking art," Kelly said.

				This year, Ernest Borel marks the 70th anniversary of the birth of Ernest Borel's Cocktail Collection. To celebrate the Platinum Jubilee, the brand has restored the historic continuity of the classic collection with a brand new version. The most representative technical interpretation of Ernest Borel, the Cocktail Collection drew inspiration from Art Deco of the 20th century. It was immediately known as a masterpiece when it first came out and obtained patents for its appearance and structure in the 1940s. The new collection is a brilliant showcase of classic beauty and modern joie de vivre. The needle plate is hollowed to an ultra-thin extent. The rotation of the second and minute plates creates a striking kaleidoscope effect whereby the plates seem to reach out from the epicentre of the dial.
				]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20130902_1_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20130902_1_2">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20130902_1_3">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2013</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20130822_1" date="2013-08-22">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Ernest Borel appears in TIME Sweet TIME exhibition]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[In fall 2013, the Olympic “prince of gymnastics” Marcel Nguyen from Germany officially becomes the global ambassador of the Swiss watch brand Ernest Borel. He will spread the brand-new romantic fashion all over the world and show the romantic and elegant style of the Ernest Borel watches.

			    In London Olympic Games, the sport new star Marcel Nguyen collected the third all-round gymnastic medal for Germany since 1936. He not only excels at gymnastic skills but also fascinates the global fans with his handsome outlook and charming smile.

				Marcel Nguyen’s performance and status in the international sport field is greatly acclaimed. His elegant and precise high-difficulty gymnastics elements are as exquisite as the precise and delicate watchmaking crafts. The medal winner Marcel Nguyen, endowed with the unique confidence and glamour of a successful man, perfectly presents Ernest Borel’s brand essence.

				The international fashion image of the well-known “prince of gymnastics” Marcel Nguyen highly corresponds to the romantic elements of Ernest Borel, making him well-deserved as the new global ambassador of the Swiss watch brand Ernest Borel.
				Marcel Nguyen then plays the leading role in the promotion of the Retro Collection of Ernest Borel, showing the world the outstanding watches of the Retro Collections. The brand-new Retro Collection looks extremely charming, elegant and glamorous through Marcel Nguyen’s presentation.

				The Retro Collection 8880T is a limited edition with only 1,000 in number, which makes it even more precious. The case is engraved with Marcel Nguyen’s autograph. The collection is also the first masterpiece aimed to celebrate that Marcel Nguyen becomes the new global ambassador, so it is worth collecting. The Retro Collection 8880T is the 2013 classic collection of Ernest Borel. The medieval Roman numerals and various classic patterns are added into the design. The classic nostalgic design is combined with the elements of the latest trend and fashion. The classic beauty and the contemporary famous watchmaking crafts are perfectly integrated.

				The 8880T Retro Collection is equipped with Swiss TT651 mechanical caliber. The exclusive design of showing double time zones in the large and small chapter rings is not only eye-catching but also useful during business trips. It is inspired by the chapters of the main time zone on the tower bell of St. Peter’s Church in Zurich, intertwining geometric metal with the Medieval Roman numerals. The small chapter ring shows the second time zone in modern standard Roman numerals. In the clear and elegant style, the collection inherits the romantic and delicate elements of the brand.

				12 H digit exhibition of the big calendar and the 3D case made by multiple crafts concretize the extraordinary spirit of the brand. Five handmade sapphire hands in different styles bring the most comfortable visual enjoyment, manifest the great taste, and clearly show the time. The tip of the second hand is decorated with the classic butterfly icon in the 1940s, which furthers emphasizes the nostalgic elegance of the brand.

				Ernest Borel plans to show each of the eye-catching and touching collections with the global ambassador which will surely make the brand prosper in the international timepiece industry and climb onto another peak.
				]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20130822_1_1">
					<![CDATA[caption1]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20130822_1_2">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20130822_1_3">
					<![CDATA[caption3]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20130822_1_4">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2013</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
	</active>
</data>
