<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
	<data ts="2015-08-19 20:00:00">
		<active>
			<news id="20150819_1" date="2015-08-19">
				<title>
					<![CDATA[For the True Gentleman and Fair Lady - Yally Collection]]>
				</title>
				<desc>
					<![CDATA[The simpler the outfit, the more impressive the wearer. Honoring this fashion code, The Yally Collection always appears to be elegantly clean. The three new couple watches continue the collection’s refreshing style, with the added luxury of rose gold elements. 12 Roman numerals circle the dial in order, resembling a line of loyal guards or a monument with a timeless epigraph. With the hour and minute hands evolved from the classic lozenge hand, the tips of which are shaped to be finer pinpoints. With luminescent coating on them, these customized hands possess eye catching detail. Furthermore, the new dial is equipped with a date window at 3 o’clock, reminding its owner of every important day not be missed. 

					The new Yally watches are presented in three different models, which are: a white dial with stainless steel bracelet, a white dial with leather strap and a brown dial with leather strap. The overall design is one of simple elegance with refined details emanating excellence.]]>
				</desc>
				<images>
					<image id="20150819_1">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20150819_2">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20150819_3">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
				</images>
				<tags>
					<tag>2014</tag>
				</tags>
			</news>

			<news id="20150805_1" date="2015-08-19">
				<title>
					<![CDATA[Ernest Borel shines in Lincheng this summer:</br>Ernest Borel’s celebration for Chinese Valentine’s Day takes place at Guiyang]]>
				</title>
				<desc>
					<![CDATA[(August 15, 2015) Ernest Borel’s celebration for Chinese Valentine’s Day “Ernest Borel Shines in Lincheng This Summer” took place at Lincheng, Guiyang on August 15. With a long 159 years of history, the Swiss watchmaking tradition and elegant lifestyle open up the romantic journey for this Chinese Valentine’s Day. Ernest Borel’s Chief Executive Officer in the Asia-Pacific Region, Su Da, and Spokesperson in Asia, Raymond Lam, attended this event together and displayed the Yally Collection.

					Founded in 1856, Ernest Borel is popular among the watch industry for its long history, profound culture, and pursuit of excellence. For more than 159 years, Ernest Borel has always kept in mind the brand’s philosophy of “ Romance in Heart” to carry out romantic and elegant mechanical aesthetics, the pursuit of excellence, making technological advances, providing services around the world, and being devoted to providing watches matching the tastes of those in pursuit of exquisite and fashionable lifestyles. On Chinese Valentine’s Day, Ernest Borel showed up in Guiyang to present a great chance for lovers to demonstrate their love romantically. The Yally Collection made the romantic holiday even better. As Su Da suggests, “Since Ernest Borel entered China for the first time in 1903, it has been associated with China for more than a hundred years. During this period of time, Ernest Borel witnessed countless romantic moments between lovers. It is hoped that through this event in Guiyang, the romantic and elegant lifestyle of Ernest Borel can be conveyed to each consumer.”

					During the event, the presence of Raymond Lam aroused enthusiasm and pushed the event to a climax. As a celebrity in the Asia-Pacific Region, Lam is the idol of hundreds of millions of fans as well as a spokesperson for elegance and romanticism. Su Da and Lam revealed the Yally Collection together. In the end, Su gave the exquisite and original couple watches to Lam. It is worth noting that the three pairs of new couple watches of the Yally Collection continue the unique, mild style of the Collection with its extra rose gold touch. The beautiful and mild lines and magnificent colors around the wrist refresh the affection between lovers. The combination of stainless steel with rose gold betters and brightens each other—the watch is as spectacular as a true gentleman and as elegant as a fair lady, praising the romantic affection for the perfect match. Lam indicates, “As a Swiss brand of 159 years of history, Ernest Borel is a synonym of romanticism and elegance. It is hoped that Ernest Borel will witness more love stories and we wish everyone here a wonderful romance.”]]>
				</desc>
				<images>
					<image id="20150805_1">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20150805_2">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20150805_3">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20150805_4">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20150805_5">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
				</images>
				<tags>
					<tag>2014</tag>
				</tags>
			</news>

			<news id="20150319_1" date="2015-03-19">
				<title>
					<![CDATA[Ernest Borel in Baselworld 2015 --- 19 - 26 Mar]]>
				</title>
				<desc>
					<![CDATA[The 43rd BASELWORLD 2015 (Basel Watch Fair) will be held in Basel, Switzerland.&#xA;&#xA;Ernest Borel will participate in the 2015 BaselWorld and we are pleased to invite you to discover the latest models of Ernest Borel Timepieces.

					 Do visit us at our booth located in Hall 2.2 Hall of Visions First Avenue – Booth no. B05.]]>
				</desc>
				<images>
					<image id="20150319_1">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20150319_2">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
				</images>
				<tags>
					<tag>2014</tag>
				</tags>
			</news>
			<news id="20150217_1" date="2015-02-17">
				<title>
					<![CDATA[Ernest Borel’s Romantic Journey in Jining and Linyi, Shandong]]>
				</title>
				<desc>
					<![CDATA[Despite the spring chill below zero in Jining and Linyi along the eastern coast, the brand’s events held on February 7 and 8 have boosted warmth all over these cities. On this romantic journey, Ernest Borel debuted its global limited edition couple watches with Miss Angie Chiu, the brand ambassador, in Guihe Shopping Square, Jining and Hengdeli Wanyue City, Linyi during Valentine’s Day and Chinese New Year. 

					The people in these two cities were excited about Angie’s coming, and the local mainstream media was ready and passionate fans looked forward to seeing this lady known as “the gorgeous beauty of China” and “the most beautiful woman in ancient costume.” The nicely tailored skirt suit in blue-grey and big pearl necklace Angie was wearing were just perfect her elegant and dignified image, and the brand’s limited edition lady watch on her wrist was an added attraction in her every movement. Here success in career, family and love makes her a best model of “time is eternality for those who love.”  She admitted: “time can change but also witness everything. To cherish every moment with your love and family and share happiness is also one of the most romantic things in life.” 

					When it comes to the role promoting Ernest Borel watches, Angie explained that as a brand with a 159-year history and the reputation as “the model of Swiss Couple Watches,” its heritage of exquisite craftsmanship and rich, romantic culture makes each watch so unique. One thing she admires most is the brand concept that they have insisted on for over one hundred years, which actually echoes with the idea of eternal love people pursue and desire. It is no doubt that Ernest Borel becomes one of the most affectionate watch brands. 

					The two-day romantic journey passed quickly while with the lingering love Angie have experienced with time, her glowing charm will last for long in the eyes of Ernest Borel clients.  With the brand concept of “Romantic Moments” Ernest Borel will always witness the miracle of love with you!
					]]>
				</desc>
				<images>
					<image id="20150217_1">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20150217_2">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20150217_3">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20150217_4">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20150217_5">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20150217_6">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
				</images>
				<tags>
					<tag>2014</tag>
				</tags>
			</news>

			<news id="20150113_1" date="2015-01-13">
				<title>
					<![CDATA[Timeless Love Ernest Borel Watches Witness Romantic Moments]]>
				</title>
				<desc>
					<![CDATA[Love is a source of sparkling life, exciting thoughts and the perpetual scene in your mind. The life spent with your beloved is like a song, playing a sweet and beautiful melody. People may reach the end of the road in their life but love never does.  Time becomes eternal when we are in love, and love continues as time goes by. Ernest Borel is the world-famous “role model of Swiss couple watches,” which is the testimony of 159 years of history. Happy Valentine’s Day!

					<b>Romantic Love Engravings</b><br>There are only 999 pairs of limited edition Yally Collection watches in the world available with love engravings on the all stainless steel back case. The 316L stainless steel case and bracelet are solid and reliable. The unique arched lugs bring the case and the bracelet together. The see-through back clearly displays the mechanical aesthetics through the motion of gears in the Swiss high-end movement. The pressurized dial pattern looks like a silk paper telling love stories. Each Roman numeral index made by stainless steel with the polishing processing is dazzling and beautiful. The hour and minute hands are illuminated with green fluorescent glow at night.				
					]]>
				</desc>
				<images>
					<image id="20150113_1">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
				</images>
				<tags>
					<tag>2014</tag>
				</tags>
			</news>



			<news id="20141119_1" date="2014-11-19">
				<title>
					<![CDATA[
					CLASSIC TRADITIONS, ROMANTIC SUSTAINABILITY<br>ERNEST BOREL’S ROMANTIC JOURNEY IN WEIFANG
					]]>
				</title>
				<desc>
					<![CDATA[On 8th November, 2014, Ernest Borel held the event “Classical traditions, romantic sustainability” on the romantic journey in Weifang, known as the capital of kites, to showcase the brand’s latest release for honored guests. The brand’s Chief Executive Officer, Mr. Su Da, and the brand ambassador, Miss Kelly Chen, attended the event to announce the debut of new automatic couple watches in Retro Collection.

					The unique historical city, Weifang, is the birthplace of kites. As the cradle of humanity and nature in Shandong, the city has hosted various cultural events and cultivated many outstanding figures since ancient times. Those experienced and finest craftsmen showing exquisite craftsmanship have continued the charming traditions of folk arts, particularly world-famous kites, woodblock New Year paintings and mahogany inlay silver lacquer ware. Ernest Borel’s new automatic couple watches in Retro Collection showed up in Weifang to create a romantic mood for this land of passion. For over 158 years, adhering to romantic and elegant mechanical aesthetics and the brand philosophy of “Romantic Moment” Ernest Borel has always committed to present elegant luxury artistic watches for those in pursuit of fashion lifestyle.

					The ceremony reached its climax when Kelly showed up in the event and ignited the audience’s enthusiasm. Mr. Su and Kelly announced the launch of new automatic couple watches in Retro Collection and as a gift, he gave Kelly a watch with precise shape, clean lines, understated natural curvature and harmonious geometric elements. As Kelly said, “Ernest Borel, a long history Swiss brand over 158 years, is synonymous with romance and elegance. I hope Ernest Borel will witness more stories of romantic love. May their love last as long as the kite flying high.” Kelly personally represents the brand image of elegant temperament and romantic style as a perfect model of romantic love.

					Ernst Borel watches have always followed the original spirit of enterprise and the belief of creating the perfect, not only occupying an important position in the watch industry and also providing an irreplaceable way of life for those in a constant pursuit of perfection, style and romantic spirit. After the event, Kelly went to the brand’s counter to give her autograph, building a warm atmosphere. Just as Mr. Su said, “Since its establishment in 1856, the Ernest Borel has been committed to spreading the romantic and elegant lifestyle to every corner of the world.” Wish Borel watches may forge ahead and continue to write the legend of high-end watches!
					]]>
				</desc>
				<images>
					<image id="20141119_1">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20141119_2">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20141119_3">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20141119_4">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20141119_5">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
				</images>
				<tags>
					<tag>2014</tag>
				</tags>
			</news>
			<news id="20141020_1" date="2014-10-20">
				<title>
					<![CDATA[
					Classic Traditions, Romantic Sustainability,<br>Ernest Borel’s Romantic Journey in Ordos
					]]>
				</title>
				<desc>
					<![CDATA[On 12th October, 2014, Ernest Borel held the event “Classical traditions, romantic sustainability” on the romantic journey in Ordos, the pearl of grassland, to showcase the brand’s latest release, new couple watches in Retro Collection for honored guests. The brand’s Regional Sales Director (Mainland China), Mr. Quan Lin, and the brand ambassador, Miss Angie Chiu, attended the event to announce the debut of new automatic couple watches in Retro Collection.

					Ernest Borel’s new automatic couple watches in Retro Collection showed up in Ordos to create a romantic mood for this land of passion. For over 158 years, adhering to romantic and elegant mechanical aesthetics and the brand philosophy of “Romantic Moment” Ernest Borel has always committed to present elegant luxury artistic watches for those in pursuit of fashion lifestyle.

					The ceremony reached its climax when Angie Chiu, the brand ambassador, showed up in the event and ignited the audience’s enthusiasm. Mr. Quan Lin and Miss Angie Chiu announced the launch of new automatic couple watches in Retro Collection and as a gift, he gave Angie Chiu a watch with precise shape, clean lines, understated natural curvature and harmonious geometric elements. Known as “the classic beauty of China, the gorgeous Asian woman,” Miss Angie Chiu personally represents the brand image of elegant temperament and romantic style as a perfect model of romantic love. As she said, “Ernest Borel, a long history Swiss brand over 158 years, is synonymous with romance and elegance. I hope Ernest Borel will witness more stories of romantic love.”

					Ernst Borel watches have always followed the original spirit of enterprise and the belief of creating the perfect, not only occupying an important position in the watch industry and also providing an irreplaceable way of life for those in a constant pursuit of perfection, style and romantic spirit. After the event, Miss Angie Chiu went to the brand’s counter to give her autograph, building a warm atmosphere. Just as Mr. Quan Lin said, “Since its establishment in 1856, the Ernest Borel has been committed to spreading the romantic and elegant lifestyle to every corner of the world.” Wish Borel watches may forge ahead and continue to write the legend of high-end watches!
					]]>
				</desc>
				<images>
					<image id="20141020_1">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20141020_2">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20141020_3">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20141020_4">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
				</images>
				<tags>
					<tag>2014</tag>
				</tags>
			</news>
			<news id="20140924_1" date="2014-09-24">
				<title>
					<![CDATA[
					Inspire Hope & Share Love
					]]>
				</title>
				<desc>
					<![CDATA[On 17th September 2014, the Swiss watch brand, Ernest Borel, held a lovely opening ceremony for a charity event called “Romantic Love” in Leidian Elementary School, Fulu Town of Shawan District, Leshan City, Sichuan Province. This event was co-sponsored by Ernest Borel, the Youth League of Shawan District, Leshan City and the local board of education. Mr. Chengxiang Cheng, Ernest Borel’s deputy sales manager in China, led the charity team and the brand’s charity ambassador, the internationally renowned movie star, Ms. Angie Chiu, to participate in this event, where they deliver poor student brand new desks and chairs and teaching supplies.

					On this charity journey in Leshan City, Ernest Borel provided Leidian Elementary School 400 sets of teaching and learning tools such as teaching tables, desks and stationery, school bags, etc., moreover, the brand used their Internet media to call for “romantic love” actions to the community collecting extracurricular books and stationery for this mountain school, and received a warm response. Mr. Chengxiang Cheng and Ms. Angie Chiu have distributed those books and stationery in person to those joyful children. Seeing their innocent and naive smiles, Mr. Angie Chiu could not help but said: “poor mountain children cannot enjoy quality life, some of them even don’t have the basic living resources, but their desire and commitment to learning and dreaming truly move us! Thanks Ernest Borel for giving me the chance to make some contribution and share love! And I hope there are more companies and people in the community to deliver their love and participate; increasing contribution can make a big difference, let’s try our best to make a positive contribution!”  

					According to Mr. Chengxiang Cheng, Ernest Borel will continue this meaningful event supporting poor students and delivering love for the cause of education to the whole world so that more poor students can get funding to study and acquire knowledge in a better environment.  After the ceremony, Ernest Borel charity team visited the classrooms and teaching in Leidian Elementary School, playing games and talking with children as a vivid example of how to share love to all students there. Ernest Borel will take more efforts in the future to love and support all students in need and bring hope to them, and make the children under the same blue sky grow up healthily together.
					]]>
				</desc>
				<images>
					<image id="20140924_1">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20140924_2">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20140924_3">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20140924_4">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
				</images>
				<tags>
					<tag>2014</tag>
				</tags>
			</news>

			<news id="20140910_1" date="2014-09-10">
				<title>
					<![CDATA[
					Served as Brand Ambassador for 5 Years, Super Star Kelly Chen Exudes Elegance and Happiness
					]]>
				</title>
				<desc>
					<![CDATA[With a 158-year history and adhering to the brand concept of “Romantic Moments,” Ernest Borel perfectly combines the romantic story for its lovers’ trademark and rigorous, excellent watch making craftsmanship.  In this advertising with “Romantic Life” as the theme, the brand invited Kelly Chen, the Goddess of Romance, to be the ambassador for the fifth year, shooing the brand new advertising.  Kelly’s slow living and elegant life style builds her a charming and romantic image, capturing the hearts of her fans.

					This time the wildly-acclaimed art director, Yee, was invited as the image consultant to create a unique fashion goddess style for Kelly Chen.  He looked to Cocktail Collection as design inspiration to highlight the distinct personalities of women today.  The turning dial represents the changing and colorful life, giving the meaning that those women with their own efforts will have a life as wonderful as Kelly’s, playing a perfect role in her career, love and family life.

					For the first time, the advertising had a male model shoot with Kelly, who looked mysterious and sexy with a Deep V black dress and a watch in Cocktail Collection characterized with stylish and magnificent temperament.  The two took their warm and sweet time before a European shooting scene, displaying the best romantic moment.

					As a fashion icon and stylish mother, Kelly admitted that she adores the unique design and dazzling color of watches in Cocktail Collection, which are suitable for all occasions in different outfits and easily get the limelight. As Kelly said, “Cocktail Collection watches are a great boon as they have many choices of colors and look sharp; I can wear them when working, shopping, or attending a ball or a party.”  Asked whether she would ask for a gift from her husband, Kelly responded with a lovely smile that the beloved one has given her the best gift since he was able to spend time with her; after all, sending a gift is just one of the ways to express love.  She also said that most of women in this new era have their own career, so they are free to buy any high-quality things such as Ernest Borel watches to reward themselves.  She is such a example of intelligent career women.

					When asked how she manages time since she is very busy with work and family, she smiled and said, “I wish I had 48 hours a day! If we don’t have enough time, we should make more efforts on planning. I will arrange some activities for and on summer holidays, so I save time to prepare a new album. But kids grow up so fast; I want to stay with them whenever I am free.”]]>
				</desc>
				<images>
					<image id="20140910_1">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20140910_2">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
				</images>
				<tags>
					<tag>2014</tag>
				</tags>
			</news>




			<news id="20140901_1" date="2014-09-01">
				<title>
					<![CDATA[
					The Brand New Print Ad for Ernest Borel Watches Interprets Extraordinary Retro Charm
					]]>
				</title>
				<desc>
					<![CDATA[Raymond Lam as a brand ambassador for Ernest Borel watches earlier shot a new series of print ads for the brand, showing his romantic and affectionate attributes. With a 158-year history and adhering to the brand concept of “Romantic Moments” Ernest Borel perfectly combines the romantic story for its lovers’ trademark and rigorous, excellent watch making craftsmanship. As a perfect model of Prince Charming in the mind of thousands of girls, Raymond Lam has always seemed to be stylish, confident and courageous, and with his meticulous work attitude, coinciding with the brand’s rigorous watch making philosophy, he always exudes a breathtaking stylish charm.

					In this brand new advertising, as his romantic and chic image remains, Raymond Lam and a western model costar a romantic love story, showing a romantic fashion sense.  During the shooting, they were wearing the brand’s Retro Collection watches.  According to Raymond Lam, the collection is his favorite because of its vintage style with simple and unique designs, which are suitable for wearing on any occasions such as public performances and dating, so that it is the best choice for couple watches!

					During the shooting, the western model sat behind Raymond Lam holding him tightly on a vintage scooter. This sweet and heartwarming scene implies that the couple in love will face any difficulties in the future together, commit to each other forever and create every romantic moment. Later the couple profitut on evening dresses to adopt a love pose, showing the brand as the romantic model of Swiss couple watches.]]>
				</desc>
				<images>
					<image id="20140901_1">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20140901_2">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20140901_3">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
				</images>
				<tags>
					<tag>2014</tag>
				</tags>
			</news>

			<news id="20140829_3" date="2014-08-28">
				<title>
					<![CDATA[
					Ernest Borel Holdings Limited Announces FY2014 Interim Results
					]]>
				</title>
				<desc>
					<![CDATA[(Hong Kong, 28 August 2014) – Ernest Borel Holdinsg Limited (“Ernest Borel” or the “Group”) (stock code: 1856), one of the best-selling Swiss-made premium watch brands in the PRC, today announced its unaudited interim results for the six months ended 30 June 2014, its first interim results since its listing on the Main Board of The Stock Exchange of Hong Kong Limited (“HKSE”) on 11 July 2014.

					During the period under review, the Group’s revenue amounted to HK$271.8 million (2013 Interim: HK$285.8 million), primarily due to the delay in the placement of orders as retailers and distributors have generally waited for the launch of new watch models at the end of June 2014. Despite the competitive operating environment, the Group managed to record a rise in gross profit of approximately 1.3% to HK$182.7 million, while gross profit margin likewise rose, climbing from approximately 63.1% to approximately 67.2% for the corresponding period of last year. However, profit attributable to equity holders slipped to HK$13.5 million (2013 Interim: HK$38.2 million) due to a non-recurring listing expense of HK$18.5 million that was recognised during the reporting period. Excluding the above item, net profit was approximately HK$32.0 million. Another factor that negatively impacted on net profit was Renminbi depreciation whereby the Group recognised a foreign exchange loss of HK$6.1 million during the period. The Group’s basic earnings per share were HK$4.8 cents.

					Business Review
					Established in Switzerland in 1856 with 158 years heritage, Ernest Borel ranked fourth in the premium watch market and ranked second in the premium couples watch market in the PRC in 20131. The Group is directly involved in a full breadth of operations, spanning from design, production, marketing and sale of mechanical and quartz premium watches. Its product offerings include a total of over 20 different collections of watches, comprising more than 208 models. Ernest Borel has established an extensive distribution network that effectively taps the lucrative PRC, Hong Kong, Macau and Southeast Asia markets. As at 30 June 2014, the Group has a total of 1,019 points of sale (“POS”), which have increased significantly from 969 POS as at 31 December 2013.

					With respect to the PRC, the Group’s largest market, with over 848 POS in 23 provinces and cities across the country as at 30 June 2014, revenue declined modestly to HK$203.3 million (2013 Interim: HK$223.9 million), accounted for approximately 74.8% of the Group’s total revenue. The decline was principally due to the delay in orders placed by its customers until the launch of new watch models at the end of June 2014. Retailers and distributors have started placing orders soon after the launch, which the sales will be reflected in the second half of 2014. Further optimism can be drawn from the growth of the PRC luxury goods retail market, which is expected to maintain strong growth and become the leading luxury goods market in the world, with the retail sales value of the premium watch market in the PRC projected to increase at a CAGR of approximately 20% from 2013 to 2018. Ernest Borel is positioned for capturing the immense growth potential and the management will remain fully committed to sustaining the growth momentum, and will prudently increase the number of POS in the country as opportunities arise.

					Turning to business in Hong Kong, Macau and Southeast Asia markets, thanks to the Group’s effective branding and marketing strategies, revenue from this business segment has steadily risen from HK$57.8 million to HK$64.4 million. As at the end of the reporting period, the Group has 150 POS in these markets, compared to 135 POS as at 31 December 2013.

					Prospects
					Looking ahead, the Group will continue to strengthen its position as the leader in the Swiss-made premium couple watch market  and an attractive global brand. To fuel for sustainable growth, the Group will seek to bolster its presence in the PRC through expanding its distribution network. To better tap into the robust premium watch market in the PRC, the Group has aimed to increase an aggregate of 300 POS across the country within the next three years commencing from 1 January 2014. Not ignoring the importance of the markets outside the PRC, an aggregate of 100 POS will be established outside the PRC at the same time. Up until 30 June 2014, the Group increased 31 POS in the PRC and 15 POS outside the PRC. Ernest Borel also intends to further reinforce its brand recognition and implement marketing initiatives and conducting promotional activities where the POS are located, so as to further reach out to its current and potential customers.

					In addition, the management is fully aware of the importance of improving the profit margin and profitability. The Group will increase its design and production capabilities, as well as place a greater effort towards the sales of high-end and mid-to-high-end timepieces. To cope with the increasing demand of premium watches, Ernest Borel plans to construct additional production facilities on the land parcel adjacent to its existing production facility in Le Noirmont, Switzerland. The Group will also expand the Production Department. Ernest Borel will introduce a new range of timepieces during the second half year that will further enhance the product mix. 

					Mr. David Su, Chairman and Executive Director of Ernest Borel, said, “With our successful listing on the Main Board of the Hong Kong Stock Exchange this year, Ernest Borel’s capital base is further enhanced, and our brand is also strengthened. Moving forward, we will continue to leverage Ernest Borel’s well-recognized global brand image and our vertically integrated business model to enjoy numerous competitive advantages. Underpinned by a long history of producing premium Swiss-made timepieces and a name synonymous with quality and craftsmanship, Ernest Borel is well positioned to become one of the best selling brands in the premium watch market in the PRC, leading to stable and long-term returns to its shareholders.”

					Remark 1:   According to the Frost & Sullivan report, Ernest Borel ranked second in the premium couples watch market and ranked fourth in the premium watch market in the PRC in terms of total retail sales value and total retail sales volume in 2013. 
					]]>
				</desc>
				<images hidden="1">
					<image id="20140829_3">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
				</images>
				<tags>
					<tag>2014</tag>
				</tags>
			</news>

			<news id="20140808_1" date="2014-08-08">
				<title>
					<![CDATA[
					Raymond Lam Shows up in Quanzhou, Interpreting Romantic Vintage Charm
					]]>
				</title>
				<desc>
					<![CDATA[Ernest Borel made its launch of New Retro Collection couple watches entitled “Romantic Chinese Valentine’s Day, Love at First Sight” in Quanzhou, Fujian Province, on the 26th of July, 2014. Mr. Su Da, Asia Pacific Chief Executive Officer of Ernest Borel, and Mr. Raymond Lam, the brand ambassador, attended the event together to announce the big debut of New Retro Collection couple watches.

					This time Ernest Borel watches had its romantic encounter with Quanzhou as Chinese Valentine’s Day was approaching, bringing its most distinctive Retro Collection couple automatic watches to this historical and cultural city surrounded by mountains and sea. As described in the excerpt of the poetry, “The doors at the end of the Bridge of Magpies are open; the couple cross the river to meet once every year,” the annual meeting of the cowherd and weaver girl on the Bridge of Magpies has become an immortal love story. And Ernest Borel watches are really the icing on the cake for this romantic festival. According to Mr. Su Da, “Ernest Borel has attached itself to China for over one hundred years since it entered into China in 1903. During which, the brand has witnessed countless romantic moments of couples, so that we hope to use this event in Quanzhou to share with every customer our romantic attitude to life.

					The grand opening ceremony began with a romantic and elegant modern dance duo, where the graceful dance has showed the audience a magnificent visual feast. The ceremony reached its climax when Raymond Lam, both the special guest of this event and the brand ambassador, appeared and attracted greatest attention. After the event, Raymond Lam went to the tour area of Ernest Borel watches to give his autograph and interact with his fans, building a friendly and warm atmosphere. This event allowed people to closely enjoy the brand charisma of “Romantic Moments” and to be impressed by its hundred year tradition of excellent craftsmanship and relentless pursuit.
					]]>
				</desc>
				<images>
					<image id="20140808_1_1">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20140808_1_2">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20140808_1_3">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20140808_1_4">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20140808_1_5">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
				</images>
				<tags>
					<tag>2014</tag>
				</tags>
			</news>

			<news id="20140714_1" date="2014-07-14">
				<title>
					<![CDATA[
					Congratulations to Ernest Borel Holdings Limited for its successful listing in Hong Kong
					]]>
				</title>
				<desc>
					<![CDATA[Shares of Ernest Borel Holdings Limited (stock code: 1856), one of the best-selling Swiss-made premium watch brands in the PRC, commenced dealing on the Main Board of The Stock Exchange of Hong Kong Limited (“SEHK”) today.

					Mr. David Su, Chairman and Executive Director of Ernest Borel said, “Ernest Borel’s listing today marks a major stepping stone to a brighter future. To seize tremendous market opportunities, we will actively bolster Ernest Borel’s position in the PRC market while enhancing our brand image globally. We will also extend our global sales network, particularly in the PRC, expand our production capacity and enhance our design and development capabilities in order to take our business to new heights.”

					Mr. David Su, Chairman and Executive Director of Ernest Borel Holdings Limited, presents an oil painting autographed by the four ambassadors of the Swiss Ernest Borel (including Ms. Kelly Chen, Mr. Raymond Lam, Ms. Angie Chiu and Mr. Marcel Nguyen) to Ms. Yvonne Ho, Listing Committee Member of Hong Kong Exchanges and Clearing Limited, as souvenir.
					]]>
				</desc>
				<images>
					<image id="20140714_1_1">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20140714_1_2">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
				</images>
				<tags>
					<tag>2014</tag>
				</tags>
			</news>

			<news id="20140703_1" date="2014-07-03">
				<title>
					<![CDATA[
					Ernest Borel celebrates its 20th anniversary in China with four celebrated ambassadors getting together to witness such extraordinary achievements
					]]>
				</title>
				<desc>
					<![CDATA[
					（27 June 2014, Hong Kong）The Swiss watch brand, Ernest Borel, held a gala dinner at the InterContinental Hotel, where the famous artist, Ms. Bowie Tsang, was invited to serve as a master of ceremonies. The event has turned glamorous when four brand ambassadors, Ms. Kelly Chen, Mr. Raymond Lam, Ms. Angie Chiu, and German gymnast Mr. Marcel Nguyen, got together for the first time to toast and celebrate the brand’s 20th anniversary in China along with the president of Ernest Borel, Mr. Boillat, its Chief Executive Officer, Mr. de Retz, Asia Pacific Chief Executive Officer, Mr. Su Da and all attendees. 

					Started in 1856, Ernest Borel has a 158 year history and is one of the few independent Swiss watch manufacturers. Most of Ernest Borel’s high-end watches have won Swiss official Observatory certified (COSC). By 2013, the brand has moved into the top 11 in the Swiss watches with the number of Observatory COSC watches, highlighting its adherence to quality of excellence and “Swiss made watches” reputation. Meanwhile, Ernest Borel has been leading a romantic and elegant culture in the market of China and is honored as the model of “Swiss Couple Watches,” earning people’s praise and favor.

					Ernest Borel has won people’s heart with its over 100 years of heritage of exquisite craftsmanship and elegant and gorgeous design while it also shines with the charisma and glamour of its brand spokespersons. The global ambassador of Ernest Borel, Mr. Marcel Nguyen is one of them. The Munich-born gymnast has attained remarkable achievements at the 2012 London Olympics and came out as the third German gymnast in 76 years to have won the gold medalist of individual all-around gymnastics competition. His extraordinary gymnastic skills, striking physique and charming smile have made him one of the fastest rising stars in the sports world.

					It has been second time Marcel attended the brand’s big event since wearing its Retro Collection last year, he felt so honored. He believes that every gymnastic move requires precision, grace, skills, and the mastery of time as well, and those beautiful, precise and difficult moves are just in the same vein as the world renowned meticulous craftsmanship of Ernest Borel. 

					Moreover, the presences of other three Ernest Borel’s ambassadors have dazzled the venue with their charm. Ms. Angie Chiu wearing Romance Collection looked exactly the same, as elegant as before, and was pleased to meet everyone in the event. Since Ernest Borel entered into China in 1993, with spirit of Swiss exquisite excellence and determination, the brand has ensured its visibility and completed the layout of whole China market by 2000. From 2011 to 2013, Ernest Borel has continuously become one of the top five watch brands in China and obtained numerous awards over years. There are over 800 points of sales across China, selling products in over 30 provinces and autonomous regions.  Hong Kong, Macau and Southeast Asia have over 135 points of sales selling Brand’s products. And Ms. Angie Chiu revealed that this year she has visited a number of cities with Ernest Borel together and witnessed the brand’s expanding in China.

					The Prince of Romance, Raymond Lam, wearing Retro Collection, sang two songs “Let Me Love You For An Hour” and “Nice,” and the audience was visibly moved. He said that the brand’s romantic culture has always inspired him. He was very pleased to serve as the Asian ambassador for the sixth consecutive year from the beginning of 2008. He hoped the brand would develop a stronger and broader business, and everyone would continue to support Ernest Borel.

					The finale performance of Kelly Chen, the Goddess of Romance wearing a watch in Cocktail Collection, has reached the event’s climax. To tie the brand’s romantic image, she performed the song “Arctic Snow” full of winter romantic feelings by depicting lovers expressing love to each other in snow, and then the song “A Notebook,” telling about love stories. 

					Kelly thanked the brand’s favor on her, so that she had the opportunity to go to different places in China for opening ceremonies and tried different ad shoot. She said the Cocktail Collection she was wearing that night was her favorite and explained that the watch was both classic and stylish, inheriting the brand’s elegant and romantic essence and just fitting her personality and style. This year was the second year she attended the brand’s Dealers and Distributors Conference Gala dinner, Kelly was very grateful for the support of the attendees and hoped to see everyone again in other occasions. She also expressed that it was a rare opportunity she could stand on the same stage with other three ambassadors.

					During the event, in addition to sharing the four ambassadors’ current status, the gala dinner also introduced a number of unique luxury watch series and provided some activities such as interactive games with great prizes, the dancing performance of Ernest Borel’s staff, and reviewing clips of business meetings over years and taking group photos. The dinner was ended successfully in a pleasant, warm, and romantic atmosphere.
					]]>
				</desc>
				<images>
					<image id="20140703_1_1">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20140703_1_2">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20140703_1_3">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20140703_1_4">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20140703_1_5">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20140703_1_6">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
				</images>
				<tags>
					<tag>2014</tag>
				</tags>
			</news>

			<news id="20140703_2" date="2014-07-03">
				<title>
					<![CDATA[
					The Goddess of Romance, Kelly Chen, Cheers for Ernest Borel’s IPO Press Conference
					]]>
				</title>
				<desc>
					<![CDATA[
					（June, 29, 2014, Hong Kong）The Swiss brand, Ernest Borel, owned by Ernest Borel Holdings Limited, held an IPO press conference at the Island Shangri-La Hotel, and invited the prestigious brand ambassador, Ms. Kelly Chen, to support for the event. 

					During the press conference, the Goddess of Romance Ms. Kelly Chen was wearing a Cocktail Series watch, which made her a perfect match for presenting Ernest Borel’s elegance. Kelly was very happy for the brand’s rapid development and felt honored to witness this important moment when the corporate announced the details of proposed listing. Kelly joked that as artists often attend many events, where punctuality is very important, they will wear a watch in any outfits for any occasions. Ernest Borel’s Cocktail Collection has proved the brand’s delicate watchmaking art by presenting different kaleidoscope patterns from inside out as the sub-dial rotates, which is one of Kelly’s first choices.   

					Ernest Borel Holdings Limited was founded in Switzerland in 1856 and has 158 years of glorious history. Adhering to the purpose of "Swiss made" quality and stringent quality control, the company built its own brand Ernest Borel for the design, manufacture, marketing and sales of Swiss-made mechanical and quartz luxury watches for men and women, which has become one of the oldest Swiss watch manufacturers.

					Ernest Borel’s watch products contain 30 different collections including Swiss made mechanical and quartz watches with over 250 models. There are more than 960 points of sales in the world.

					]]>
				</desc>
				<images>
					<image id="20140703_2_1">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20140703_2_2">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20140703_2_3">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
				</images>
				<tags>
					<tag>2014</tag>
				</tags>
			</news>

			<news id="20140415_1" date="2014-04-15">
				<title>
					<![CDATA[
					Ernest Borel appears in TIME Sweet TIME exhibition
					]]>
				</title>
				<desc>
					<![CDATA[
					La Chaux-de-Fonds, Switzerland, is the global capital of watchmaking and its watchmaking museum is the most beautiful in the world. 2014 marks the 40 years of the current building Musée International d'Horlogerie (The international Watchmaking Museum) in La Chaux-de-Fonds. The anniversary exhibition aims to demonstrate the relevance of the increase in its collections. Visitors are invited to browse through the entire museum to discover 40 highlights.

					The international Watchmaking Museum has asked watch companies to donate contemporary pieces in a move to conserve these items which, in addition to being technical or prestige items, are part of the heritage and could provide a window for future generations into the ingenuity and artistic endeavours of the experts of today. 

					More than 30 companies including Ernest Borel responded to the museum’s request, 44 timepieces including 2 Ernest Borel antique watches, are exhibited in two special display cases. Ernest Borel was established in Switzerland since 1856. The company has a deep and profound watch-making culture of more than 150 years, bringing countless romantic sentiments to couples over the years with classic designs. The couple logo is also very well known to the public. Ernest Borel is so proud and pleased to showcase the valuable antique watch to all.

					One the other hand, the latest Cocktail Collection is exhibited in the watch showcase, it is one of the most representative models of Ernest Borel. Cocktail Collection has a patent for its external structure since it was introduced in 1940s. The ultra-slim hollow sub-dial rotates in accordance, forming the dynamic kaleidoscopic pattern keeping extending from inward to outward. The new generation of Cocktail Collection recreates classic in color, creativity and uniqueness and displays a perfect blend of physical mechanics, classical aesthetics and Swiss exquisite watchmaking techniques. Come and visit the International Watchmaking Museum if you are interested. For exhibition details, please visit <a href="http://www.mih.ch">http://www.mih.ch</a>.
					]]>
				</desc>
				<images>
					<image id="20140415_1_1">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20140415_1_2">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20140415_1_3">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20140415_1_4">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
				</images>
				<tags>
					<tag>2014</tag>
					<tag>2013</tag>
				</tags>
			</news>

			<news id="20140211_1" date="2014-02-11">
				<title>
					<![CDATA[
					Ernest Borel in Baselworld 2014 --- Mar 27 - Apr 3
					]]>
				</title>
				<desc>
					<![CDATA[
					The 42nd BASELWORLD 2014 (Basel Watch Fair) will be held in Basel, Switzerland. 
					Ernest Borel will participate in the 2014 BaselWorld and we are pleased to invite you to discover the latest models of Ernest Borel Timepieces. 
					Do visit us at our booth located in Hall 2.2 Hall of Visions First Avenue – Booth no. B05.
					]]>
				</desc>
				<images>
					<image id="20140211_1_1">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20140211_1_2">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
				</images>
				<tags>
					<tag>2014</tag>
					<tag>2013</tag>
				</tags>
			</news>
			<news id="20140121_1" date="2014-01-21">
				<title>
					<![CDATA[
					Swiss Ernest Borel Watches Show up at Chengdu for a Chinese New Year Romantic Exhibition Tour New Releases of Retro Collection Couple Watches<br />Ernest Borel Offers Special Chinese New Year Gifts
					]]>
				</title>
				<desc>
					<![CDATA[
					Swiss Ernest Borel made its official launch of New Retro Collection couple watches, which is entitled “Warm New Year Gift, Romantic Couple Watches,” in Chengdu on the 17th of January, 2014. Swiss made Ernest Borel watches across 158 years have showed up for the most romantic and luxurious new year exhibition tour in Chengdu known as “the Land of Abundance.”  Mr. Su Da, Asia Pacific Chief Executive Officer of Ernest Borel, and Mr. Raymond Lam, the brand ambassador, attended the event together to announce the debut of New Retro Collection couple watches. 
					On that day, Swiss made Ernest Borel watches have arrived at the most beautiful city of Southwest China, Chengdu, also called the City of Hibiscus, to experience a romantic encounter with Chunxi Road, which is also nicknamed as the “Hundred Year Gold Street.” Similar to that Chunxi street has gone through hundred years of testing and accumulation but is still flourishing in the ever changing times, Ernest Borel has always insisted on the heritage of exquisite watchmaking craftsmanship and romantic legendary story. Adhering to the brand philosophy of “Romantic Moments, A life Companion” and the spirit of pursuing “excellence,” Ernest Borel watches combines traditional Swiss watchmaking craftsmanship with high-end techniques to bring customers more stylish, elegant, classic, romantic and high-tech wristwatches.  
					According to Mr. Su Da, “Chengdu’s long history, rich cultural heritage and comfortable urban pace just coincide with the brand philosophy we have pursued and insisted on. Swiss Ernest Borel has attached itself to China for over one hundred years since it entered into China in 1903. During which, the brand has witnessed countless romantic moments of couples, so that we hope to continue the romantic love in Chengdu and share it with people with a romantic attitude to life, leading them to enjoy romantic moments in theirlives.” 
					The grand opening ceremony for the new collection of Swiss made Ernest Borel watches began with the violin and guitar ensemble, where the perfect classical and modern combination has showed the audience a magnificent visual feast. The ceremony reached its climax when Mr. Raymond Lam, both the special guest of this event and the brand ambassador, appeared and attracted greatest attention. As a renowned artist in the Asia-Pacific region, Raymond is the pop idol that has won the hearts of millions of fans. Mr. Su Da attended the event with Raymond to announce the debut of New Retro Collection couple watches, and as a gift, he gave Raymond a watch with precise shape, clean lines, understated natural curvature and harmonious geometric elements. Raymond  said that “Since Ernest Borel is the Swiss brand with a 158-year long history and rich cultural heritage, it can evoke people’s desires and dreams for better and romantic life in their deepest heart. It is a reliable brand."  
					As the event day was also the opening ceremony of “Romantic journey of Swiss Ernest Borel Watches in the City of Hibiscus,” Raymond sent the gift with Shu brocade and wished good luck for this special event. When asked why he chose the Shu brocade as a gift, he replied: “Shu brocade is one of the distinctive products in Sichuan and is also known as the leading one of four famous brocades in China. At this special moment, I sent this Sichuan brocade with the brand philosophy, “Romantic Moments, A life Companion,” embroidered on it, to wish Ernest Borel a successful event for the ‘Romantic Journey in the City of Hibiscus.’”  The event for romantic journey in the City of Hibiscus started by the “Romantic Prince”, Mr. Raymond Lam, will convene 12 pairs of romantic couples from the city to find 12 romantic dating places with Ernest Borel together. The brand will help more romantic lovers witness happiness in Chengdu, this historic fashion city. In the event, Raymond enjoyed the interaction with his fans in a very warm atmosphere until nightfall, where the event has successfully ended under dazzling lights.
					]]>
				</desc>
				<images>
					<image id="20140121_1_1">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20140121_1_2">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20140121_1_3">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
				</images>
				<tags>
					<tag>2014</tag>
					<tag>2013</tag>
				</tags>
			</news>

			<news id="20140107_1" date="2014-01-07">
				<title>
					<![CDATA[
					Swiss Ernest Borel Watches Give a Warm New Year Greeting in Liuzhou with New Releases of Retro Collection Couple Watches
					]]>
				</title>
				<desc>
					<![CDATA[
					4th January 2014, Ernest Borel’s Warm New Year Gift, Romantic Couple Watches  Swiss Ernest Borel made its official launch of New Retro Collection couple watches in Liuzhou, Guangxi.  With the 158 years of history, the brand began its romantic journey here with the traditional Swiss watchmaking craftsmanship and elegant, classic lifestyle.  Mr. Su Da, Asia Pacific Chief Executive Officer of Ernest Borel, and Miss Angie Chiu, the brand ambassador, announced the debut of new automatic couple watches in its Retro Collection. 

					Liuzhou is romantic in that the warm landscapes in the winter of the south are beautiful, poetic, and mesmerizing.  Similarly, after 158 years of testing and accumulation, Swiss Ernest Borel watches have always insisted on the heritage of exquisite watchmaking craftsmanship and romantic legendary story.  Adhering to the brand philosophy of “Romantic Moments, A life Companion” and the spirit of pursuing “excellence” while following the trend of the time, Ernest Borel watches combines traditional Swiss watchmaking craftsmanship with high-end techniques to bring customers more stylish, elegant, classic, romantic and high-tech watches.  According to Mr. Su Da, “Liuzhou’s status in the territory of Ernest Borel's development in China cannot be ignored; it has become one of the most important Ernest Borel watch markets.  With this Swiss Ernest Borel new product opening, we hope to help customers develop a romantic and elegant attitude to life.”

					On that day, Mr. Su Da, Asia Pacific Chief Executive Officer of Ernest Borel, and Miss Angie Chiu, announced the debut of new automatic couple watches in its Retro Collection.  The unparalleled romantic aesthetics of automatic couple watches in Retro Collection displays the ultimate retro glamour.  Its precise shape, clean lines, understated natural curvature and harmonious geometric elements all contribute to the elegant style. 

					The ceremony reached its climax when Angie Chiu, the brand ambassador, appeared and attracted greatest attention.  As one of pivotal actresses in Hong Kong, the dignified and gracious Angie Chiu known as “the classic beauty of China, the gorgeous Asian woman,” represents the brand image of elegant temperament and romantic style.  After the opening, Mr. Su Da gave a pair of charming gifts, the couple watches in Retro Collection, to Miss Angie Chiu and her husband.  As a great model of romantic love, this couple who treat each other with respect perfectly interpreted Retro Collection automatic couple watches with their love stories.

					 After the event, Miss Angie Chiu showed up in the tour area of Swiss Ernest Borel watches and signed her name on the light box and interacted with her fans, building a friendly and warm atmosphere.  Just as Mr. Su Da said, “Since its establishment in 1856, the Swiss Ernest Borel has been committed to spreading the romantic and elegant lifestyle to every corner of the world.  We also believe that the SwissErnest Borel watches can forge ahead and continue to write the legend of high-end watches! "

					]]>
				</desc>
				<images>
					<image id="20140107_1_1">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20140107_1_2">
						<![CDATA[]]]>
					</image>
					<image id="20140107_1_3">
						<![CDATA[]]>
					</image>
				</images>
				<tags>
					<tag>2014</tag>
					<tag>2013</tag>
				</tags>
			</news>

		<news id="20131219_1" date="2013-12-19">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[
				Ernest Borel Spread Love at an Ancient Capital with a Romantic Opening of Xi’an Flagship Store and a New Collection Debut Ernest Borel Offers Unique Christmas Gifts
				]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[
				Ernest Borel celebrated its grand opening ceremony of Xi’an Bell Tower flagship store and the debut of Retro Collection I in Xi’an on December 14, 2013. The 157-year-old brand was excited to introduce their masterpieces to Xi’an, the ancient capital with thousand years of brilliant civilization, starting a conversation with this cultural city with long history and also paying tribute to the rich heritage of Qicheng. Mr. Su Da, Asia Pacific Chief Executive Officer of Ernest Borel, and Raymond Lam, the brand ambassador, attended the event, cut the ribbon for the new store opening ceremony, and announced the debut of new automatic watches, Retro Collection I.

			    Xi’an Bell Tower, the landmark building located in the most prosperous downtown area, is vast and elegant, mysterious and romantic with more than 600 years of history, telling the stories and legends of this Chinese ancient capital. Similarly, after 157 years of testing and accumulation, Ernest Borel has always insisted on the heritage of exquisite watchmaking craftsmanship and romantic legendary story. Adhering to the brand philosophy of “Romance in Heart” and the spirit of pursuing excellence while following the trend of the time, Ernest Borel combines traditional Swiss watchmaking craftsmanship with high-end techniques to bring customers more stylish, elegant, classic, romantic and high-tech watches. In this way, Ernest Borel has built its flagship store at Xi’an Bell Tower to pay tribute to both Chinese culture and classic legends.

				According to Mr. Su Da, “Xi’an is one of the four world's most famous ancient capitals, ranking first among Chinese ancient cities. It is not only the birthplace of Chinese civilization, representing Chinese culture; it is also an innovative and stylish modern city. Xi’an has cultural heritage with grace and elegance Ernest Borel understands; its fashion sense also has resonance for the brand. In 2013, the development of Ernest Borel in China’s watch market entered a new accelerated period. As an ancient capital of Chinese civilization, Xi'an’s status in the territory of China's development cannot be underestimated; it has become one of the most important Ernest Borel watch markets. With this Ernest Borel new flagship store in Xi'an, we hope to help customers develop a romantic and elegant attitude to life. I believe the opening of Xi’an Bell Tower flagship store will bring new vitality to the city!”

				On that day, Ernest Borel watches celebrated the grand opening ceremony of Xi’an flagship store and the debut of automatic watches, new Retro Collection I. The ceremony reached its climax when Raymond Lam, the brand ambassador, appeared and attracted greatest attention.  As a renowned artist in the Asia-Pacific region, Raymond Lam is the pop idol that has won the hearts of millions of fans and also the representative of elegant and romantic style. Mr. Su Da gave Raymond the stylish gift, a new model of automatic watches - Retro Collection 8380, whose delicate design and exquisite craftsmanship highlight the brand’s excellent artistic taste and elegant temperament. After the ceremony, Raymond Lam attended Ernest Borel’s cocktail party and unveiled their favorite Christmas watches. Mr. Raymond Lam enjoyed the interaction with his fans in a very warm atmosphere.

				When asked about his favorite Christmas gift, Raymond Lam said Retro Collection I would be the best choice for Christmas gifts for its perfect combination of vintage art and excellent workmanship, quality movement and unique design, and original style and superior performance.   This model can both express romantic feelings and feature aesthetic and practical functions.
				]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20131219_1_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20131219_1_2">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20131219_1_3">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2013</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20130902_1" date="2013-09-02">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[
				Prince of Gymnastics Marcel Nguyen Named as Global Ambassador of Ernest Borel <br> Welcome ceremony held in Hong Kong with Nguyen displaying latest Retro Collection
				]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[
				(Hong Kong – 2 September 2013) Ernest Borel today hosted a grand ceremony in Hong Kong to mark the appointment of German gymnast and Olympic medallist Marcel Nguyen as the global ambassador of the 157-year Swiss timepiece brand. During the event, the prince of gymnastics formally assumed his role and also put on a dashing array of watches from Ernest Borel's brand new Retro Collection, effortlessly highlighting the series' classic elegance and modern sophistication.

			    At the 2012 London Olympics, Marcel stunned the world with his brilliant performance on the gym floor and came out as the third German gymnast in 76 years to have won an Olympic medal. His impressive gymnastic skills, striking physique and affable smile have grabbed headlines around the world, making him one of the fastest rising stars in the sports world. In every aspect, the 25-year-old athlete is the perfect figure to represent Ernest Borel. For one thing, his recognised achievement as an athlete and the inch-perfect precision with which he performs all manner of difficult moves are in the same vein as Ernest Borel's sophisticated watchmaking art. The immense confidence, charisma and charm that the Munich-born gymnast exudes echo the unique allure and romantic style of Ernest Borel's design.

				Following the ceremony, Marcel said: "I am absolutely delighted and excited to be the global ambassador of Ernest Borel. As a professional gymnast, every move I make on the gym floor has to be precise and elegant and demonstrate my skills. When Ernest Borel first approached me, it occurred to me that gymnastics had a lot in common with a magnificent timepiece brand. Ernest Borel's superb watchmaking art and romantic, classic image are second to none. So I did not hesitate for a moment about Ernest Borel's invitation."

				"Recently I was invited to Ernest Borel's factory in Switzerland to learn how to assemble watch components. It was an eye-opening experience that brought me closer to understanding the highly sophisticated and complex work that goes into watchmaking at Ernest Borel. It is a procedure that somewhat echoes what I do professionally. Both involve enormous concentration, a lot of trying and testing and pursuit for perfection."

				Speaking of Marcel's appointment, Mr. Renaud de Retz, Chief Executive Officer of Ernest Borel said: "Ernest Borel is celebrated for its romantic, elegant and stylish design. For more than a century, the romantic and elegant philosophy of the brand has fulfilled the desires of those with discerning taste. It is with great delight and excitement that we have invited the internationally renowned Olympic medallist Mr. Marcel Nguyen to be Ernest Borel's global ambassador. As the prince of gymnastics, Mr. Nguyen's personal aura, talent and achievements are a perfect fit for Ernest Borel's unparalleled status and exquisite watchmaking art, and for presenting our brand new Retro Collection. Besides, our brand logo features a dancing couple to reflect the elegance and romance associated with the brand. Both dancing and gymnastics are about grace and style, which makes the choice of Mr. Nguyen all the more fitting as the brand's global ambassador."

				Officially unveiled today, the Retro Collection is Ernest Borel's signature collection in 2013. Its design is characterised by dual time function, Roman numerals and a variety of classic motifs. Grounded on the original collection's classic retro design 70 years ago, the new version pays tributes to the classics and is fused with modern elegance and cutting edge watchmaking technology, highlighting aesthetics and functionality in equal measure. The Retro collection is a limited edition of 1,000 pieces released worldwide, with each piece carrying a serial number in a unique certificate that proves the watch is Swiss made. It is the first masterpiece collection presented by Ernest Borel to celebrate our affiliation with Marcel.

				The appointment of Marcel follows the naming of Asian pop diva Kelly Chen as Ernest Borel's "Goddess of Romance" in March 2010, when a grand ceremony was held in Shanghai to celebrate Kelly appointment. As Ernest Borel's Cocktail Collection is unveiled this year, the Hong Kong-born star is now in the limelight, displaying the brand's latest Cocktail Collection in her elegance and grace. "This collection is an absolute masterpiece. I love the special visual effect that plays with the brilliant colours. The incredible precision with which the watches are made is simply in keeping with Ernest Borel's sophisticated watchmaking art," Kelly said.

				This year, Ernest Borel marks the 70th anniversary of the birth of Ernest Borel's Cocktail Collection. To celebrate the Platinum Jubilee, the brand has restored the historic continuity of the classic collection with a brand new version. The most representative technical interpretation of Ernest Borel, the Cocktail Collection drew inspiration from Art Deco of the 20th century. It was immediately known as a masterpiece when it first came out and obtained patents for its appearance and structure in the 1940s. The new collection is a brilliant showcase of classic beauty and modern joie de vivre. The needle plate is hollowed to an ultra-thin extent. The rotation of the second and minute plates creates a striking kaleidoscope effect whereby the plates seem to reach out from the epicentre of the dial.
				]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20130902_1_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20130902_1_2">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20130902_1_3">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2013</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20130822_1" date="2013-08-22">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Olympic “prince of gymnastics” Marcel Nguyen becomes the new global ambassador of Swiss watch brand Ernest Borel]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[In fall 2013, the Olympic “prince of gymnastics” Marcel Nguyen from Germany officially becomes the global ambassador of the Swiss watch brand Ernest Borel. He will spread the brand-new romantic fashion all over the world and show the romantic and elegant style of the Ernest Borel watches.

			    In London Olympic Games, the sport new star Marcel Nguyen collected the third all-round gymnastic medal for Germany since 1936. He not only excels at gymnastic skills but also fascinates the global fans with his handsome outlook and charming smile.

				Marcel Nguyen’s performance and status in the international sport field is greatly acclaimed. His elegant and precise high-difficulty gymnastics elements are as exquisite as the precise and delicate watchmaking crafts. The medal winner Marcel Nguyen, endowed with the unique confidence and glamour of a successful man, perfectly presents Ernest Borel’s brand essence.

				The international fashion image of the well-known “prince of gymnastics” Marcel Nguyen highly corresponds to the romantic elements of Ernest Borel, making him well-deserved as the new global ambassador of the Swiss watch brand Ernest Borel.
				Marcel Nguyen then plays the leading role in the promotion of the Retro Collection of Ernest Borel, showing the world the outstanding watches of the Retro Collections. The brand-new Retro Collection looks extremely charming, elegant and glamorous through Marcel Nguyen’s presentation.

				The Retro Collection 8880T is a limited edition with only 1,000 in number, which makes it even more precious. The case is engraved with Marcel Nguyen’s autograph. The collection is also the first masterpiece aimed to celebrate that Marcel Nguyen becomes the new global ambassador, so it is worth collecting. The Retro Collection 8880T is the 2013 classic collection of Ernest Borel. The medieval Roman numerals and various classic patterns are added into the design. The classic nostalgic design is combined with the elements of the latest trend and fashion. The classic beauty and the contemporary famous watchmaking crafts are perfectly integrated.

				The 8880T Retro Collection is equipped with Swiss TT651 mechanical caliber. The exclusive design of showing double time zones in the large and small chapter rings is not only eye-catching but also useful during business trips. It is inspired by the chapters of the main time zone on the tower bell of St. Peter’s Church in Zurich, intertwining geometric metal with the Medieval Roman numerals. The small chapter ring shows the second time zone in modern standard Roman numerals. In the clear and elegant style, the collection inherits the romantic and delicate elements of the brand.

				12 H digit exhibition of the big calendar and the 3D case made by multiple crafts concretize the extraordinary spirit of the brand. Five handmade sapphire hands in different styles bring the most comfortable visual enjoyment, manifest the great taste, and clearly show the time. The tip of the second hand is decorated with the classic butterfly icon in the 1940s, which furthers emphasizes the nostalgic elegance of the brand.

				Ernest Borel plans to show each of the eye-catching and touching collections with the global ambassador which will surely make the brand prosper in the international timepiece industry and climb onto another peak.
				]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20130822_1_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20130822_1_2">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20130822_1_3">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20130822_1_4">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2013</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20130809_1" date="2013-08-09">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[The Swiss Watch Brand Ernest Borel Cocktail Collection is Released<br> A flower in the wrist blossoms, to waltz the glamour of time]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Ernest Borel is founded by Jules Borel in 1856 in Neuchatel, Switzerland. The brand perfectly combines the romantic and elegant culture, as well as the high-quality watchmaking crafts. It is not only a prestigious brand in the timepiece industry, it also wins the title of “the model of Swiss couple watch.” In the 41st BASELWORLD: the World Watch and Jewelry Show, Ernest Borel’s Cocktail Collection, once exhibited, caused a sensation due to its exquisite beauty and excellent functions. Now, the Cocktail Collection is going to make its debut in the Chinese market and bring the romantic trend. Asian superstar Kelly Chen earlier starred in the commercial advertisement for the Cocktail Collection of Ernest Borel and presented the glamour of romance and dream. Kelly high praises the Cocktail Collection. She said, “The Cocktail Collection is the combination of precision and color. The sophisticated caliber accompanied by the colorful strap enchants the ladies.”

				The Cocktail Collection is the most representative of Ernest Borel. It is inspired by the European decoration. In the 1940s, the Cocktail Collection of Ernest Borel was a hit once it was released. It is considered “masterpiece” in the watchmaking industry, and its exterior and structure are also patented. The chrysanthemum pattern on the dial is composed of several pentagrams. The rim is inlaid with crystals, which makes the watch rich in femininity. The sun-shaped chapter ring responds to the radial dial. Besides, it adopts genuine leather as the material for the strap and embellishes it with a chain of oval-shaped golden rings. Classic black is accompanied by gold, which shows the noble and elegant texture.

				The resplendent claim in the era of mechanics shows the strong characteristic of the times. Since the Cocktail Collection was released, it has tried to preserve the European Romantic spirit in the iconic dial and integrate the new elements to show the brilliant colors of the era and its exquisite romance and elegance.

				In 2013, Ernest Borel extends its history and represents its classic romance. Classic aesthetics and mechanics in physics are perfectly combined into the Swiss exquisite watchmaking crafts. The ultra-slim hollow sub-dial rotates in accordance with the Swiss high-end automatic movement, forming the dynamic kaleidoscopic pattern keeping extending from inward to outward. From the elegant mystery submerges the exquisite and classic nostalgic atmosphere. The unique 3D design of the dial and the polygon glossy bezel inlaid with six natural diamonds endow it with the femininity. The chapter ring in the same color serves as the soft contour. The tone on tone genuine leather strap with the contrast material to the dial shows the simple modernity, bringing out the utmost beauty of the pattern.

				Color is always a key point in establishing feelings. At the age that emphasizes character and independent spirit, color has naturally become the important tool to express feelings. The new Cocktail Collection in 2013 has strong and abundant color elements: white, red, green, and brown. No matter for work days or night parties, the brightly-colored Cocktail Collection is the necessity to go with the garments.

				The elegant exterior and extraordinary caliber of the Cocktail Collection both exhibits its exquisite fashion and lively temperament.
				]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20130809_1_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20130809_1_2">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20130809_1_3">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20130809_1_4">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20130809_1_5">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2013</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20130718_1" date="2013-07-18">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[ERNEST BOREL SPREADS THE SPIRIT OF ROMANCE WITH THE OPENING OF ITS FIRST FLAGSHIP STORE]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Singapore, 18 July 2013 – Everyone loves a romantic love story. With a trademark logo featuring the silhouette of a couple, Ernest Borel has established itself as a brand filled with romance and elegance, bringing timeless elegant sentiments to couples over the years with their romantic couple timepieces. Now, Ernest Borel continues to spread the spirit of romance here in Singapore, with the opening of its first flagship store at Chinatown Point.

				Founded by Jules Borel and Paul Courvoisier in Neuchatel, Switzerland since 1856, Ernest Borel has a deep and profound watch-making culture of more than 150 years, achieving spectacular results with its exquisite watch-making art and romantic elegant design. The brand’s history has always been closely tied to the watchmaking region of the Jura – since its founding, Ernest Borel relied on regional manpower and savoir-faire to pursue its development, and in doing so, the brand won numerous Swiss and International prizes and awards. Notable mentions were the first prize from the Observatory in 1866 and two first prizes for wrist-chronometers by the Neuchatel Observatory before celebrating its centenary.

				The “Lovers” Trademark
				The trademark of Ernest Borel originates from a beautiful romantic legend where once upon a time during a royal ball, the young Ernest Borel met a beautiful girl. Their graceful dance drew the audience in with others looking on enviously, a photographer then caught their romantic moments on camera. The elegant dance and the romance of the moment ignited Ernest Borel’s inspiration, prompting him to design the trademark logo to immortalize this magical experience. The dancing couple has been the brand’s trademark and inspiration since the late 19th/early 20th century, this striking image becoming firmly established as the “Lovers” trademark.

				The Brand Development
				Ernest Borel underwent rapid international expansion in 1859 with contacts established in various countries throughout Europe, North and South America. The brand further expanded its network into Asia, with Japan, China as well as India gaining traction and fast becoming the main markets for the brand. A century on in 1959, Ernest Borel has established itself in more than 70 markets across five continents.
With strategic intent to grow its network in South East Asia and continue to spread the spirit of romance, Ernest Borel has strategically opened its first flagship store with the size of 295 sq ft in Singapore at the newly renovated Chinatown Point.

				“Singapore is an important market for Ernest Borel and we believe the consumers here will appreciate this time-honoured, high-quality and well-established romantic brand. All Watches has represented Ernest Borel for four years in Singapore, and the good working relations over the years gave the brand the confidence in opening a boutique here when the opportunity came, to further extend our brand offer to reach out to more people here,” said Mr Su Da, Chief Executive Officer of Ernest Borel (Asia Pacific).

				On the collaboration with Ernest Borel, Mr Sunny Ng, Managing Director of All Watches Group, expressed the importance of retail space and location, “We saw the opportunity to align ourselves with Chinatown Point, a landmark mall that possesses a rich heritage in the history of Singapore. Chinatown Point has successfully reinvented itself with its recent revamp drawing in a strong following of locals and tourists which we are positive that the brand can capitalise on. With an extensive brand offer, and its unique position of couple timepieces, Ernest Borel relates to the consumers and projects a huge sensibility and sentimental charm which connects to people.” Ernest Borel is available exclusively and currently retailing at All Watches and Aptimos outlets.

				Raymond Lam, the Asia-Pacific Ambassador of Ernest Borel since 2008, attended the official opening of the Ernest Borel flagship store on 18 July. Raymond is a familiar face on television for our target consumers. He carries with him a stylish and gentlemanly appearance that has adorned many roles as the knight in shining armour. With a refined and romantic charisma, he joins the Ernest Borel team to spread the spirit of romance with timepieces that radiate vitality under a new historical milestone.
        ]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20130718_1_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20130718_1_2">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20130718_1_3">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20130718_1_4">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2013</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20130418_2" date="2013-04-18">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Ernest Borel Opens Largest Flagship Store in Shanghai]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Shanghai, April 18th, 2013 : Prestigious Swiss watchmaker Ernest Borel held the grand opening of its largest flagship store in Shanghai, located on Nanjing East Road in The Bund. Ernest Borel has combined 157 years of romantic history with its traditional Swiss watchmaking craftsmanship, using both elegant and classic elements to create the exclusive “Ernest Borel Museum”. The president of Ernest Borel, Mr. Raphael Boillat, the Asia-Pacific CEO of Ernest Borel, Mr. Su and the brand ambassadress Ms. Angie Chiu took part in the ribbon cutting ceremony to celebrate the opening of the new store, marking yet another “romantic moment” milestone  for Ernest Borel.

				Founded in 1856, Ernest Borel has perpetuated the concept of “Romantic Moments” and the exploring spirit of “Striving for Excellence”. For  over 150 years, it has been forging ahead with determination, creating industry classics and constantly expanding its international business. In addition to opening new stores in Switzerland, the US, France, Ireland, Vietnam and Singapore, it has paid more attention to market development in China over the past two decades and has achieved impressive results. During the celebration, Mr. Boillat said:, “After years of hard work, Ernest Borel has successfully fused broad-reaching, traditional values with Chinese fashion sense. We are committed to creating new consumption concepts for numerous Chinese consumers. China has now become one of the major growing economic regions for Ernest Borel. We strive to supply markets in the Asia-Pacific region with genuine Swiss-made watches while constantly intensifying our sales network.”

				Meanwhile, Mr. Su also revealed that Ernest Borel has been linked to China since 1903. “Now, Shanghai has turned into a highly international city and The Bund is one of its most romantic locations. Ernest Borel has opened its largest global flagship store in Shanghai, indicating the importance of China and the Asia-Pacific region to Ernest Borel. We promise to continue the concept of striving for excellence and to remain consistant in our efforts to provide consumers with quality products and professional services.”

				In addition to two  of Ernest Borel's chief executives, MessrsMr. Su and Boillat, Ernest Borel's ambassadressor Ms. Angie Chiu, the Swiss General Consul in Shanghai Mr. Heinrich Schellenberg and the Executive Director of the Chinese Chamber of Commerce in Shanghai, Mr. Ken Goenawan, also attended the celebration. Ms. Angie Chiu, who is an honored “oriental goddess” for playing the role of the graceful and mild “Feng Chengcheng” on the famous Hong Kong TV show “Shanghai Bund”, wore a new Ernest Borel watch model and an elegant long skirt. Generous and beautiful,  all eyes were on Angie.

				After making light conversation with the emcee, Angie teamed up with Mr. Boillat, Mr. Su , Mr. Schellenbe and Ken to host a grand ribbon cutting ceremony and a toast announcing the official opening of Swiss Ernest Borel’s flagship store on The Bund, Shanghai.

				Angie explained in an interview that she has been the ambassadriceor of Swiss Ernest Borel since 2005. She was glad to collaborate with Ernest Borel in the creation and promotion of  romantic and classic wristwatches. The romantic watch brand launched in Shanghai today reflects the unique creativity and spirit of time so elaborately presented by Swiss Ernest Borel, a brand that embodies the essence of  time.

				Ernest Borel’s largest flagship store in the world is located on Nanjing Road, The Bund, Shanghai and sells all the models from the Ernest Borel collections as well as showcasing dozens of antique Ernest Borel watches.

				The store is divided into three areas; the History Gallery, the Product Display Area and the Sales and Business Area. The History Gallery showcases the brilliant achievements of Ernest Borel through photos, interactive devices and precious antique watches. Customers can follow the 157-year “golden age” of Ernest Borel in a classic, elegant environment. The Product Display and Business Areas are magnificently decorated, with a graceful, romantic atmosphere. Here, customers can enjoy the glamour of Ernest Borel. As a guest says:, “I’m honored to visit such an engaging Swiss watch museum. It is more like an interesting conversation about romantic European lifestyle, the art of luxury watches and a demonstration of traditional Swiss watchmaking craftsmanship rather than a simple exhibition.”
        ]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20130418_2_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20130418_2_2">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2013</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20130418_1" date="2013-04-18">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Ernest Borel, Swiss made watches since 1856, Announce Their Arrival in India]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[March 9th, Mumbai, India: Swiss luxury watchmakers Ernest Borel known for their rich heritage, elegant designs and remarkable craftsmanship, in partnership with Bayside Labels (India) Pvt. Ltd., an importer of luxury products into India, has officially launched the brand in India at Tote on the Turf, Mumbai. Ernest Borel, the brand which was founded and established in 1856 in Neuchâtel, Switzerland by Jules Borel has recognized the significance of the Indian Market. With their focus on “romantic moments” and adherence to a philosophy of “pursuing constant perfection”, the brand aims to bring the best of the Ernest Borel’s world to India and its watch connoisseurs. This 157 year old timepiece manufacturer exhibited its most coveted time pieces during an exclusive event at Tote. The launch of the brand in India is yet another strong statement of Ernest Borel’s proud legacy. The launch was done completely in the brand’s style with ‘Romance’ as the theme of the evening.

		The party witnessed the presence of Dr. Linus von Castelmur, Ambassador of Switzerland to India and Bhutan, Mr. Werner E. Nievergelt, Counsel General of Switzerland to India and many other watch enthusiasts and prominent personalities. Speaking on the occasion, Mr. Pietro Meloni, International Sales and Marketing Director of the Ernest Borel, says “We always wanted to make our presence felt in India, since it is the known for its rich heritage and history. Our brand also stands for similar values hence, making it a perfect market for us. It will allow us to not only showcase one of the most internationally acclaimed and desirable watch brands adequately but also get to know new clientele with a taste for exclusive watches”.

		The party witnessed the presence of Dr. Linus von Castelmur, Ambassador of Switzerland to India and Bhutan, Mr. Werner E. Nievergelt, Counsel General of Switzerland to India and many other watch enthusiasts and prominent personalities. Speaking on the occasion, Mr. Pietro Meloni, International Sales and Marketing Director of the Ernest Borel, says “We always wanted to make our presence felt in India, since it is the known for its rich heritage and history. Our brand also stands for similar values hence, making it a perfect market for us. It will allow us to not only showcase one of the most internationally acclaimed and desirable watch brands adequately but also get to know new clientele with a taste for exclusive watches”.

		Ernest Borel timepieces are already available in India with retail partners in Mumbai: Watches of Switzerland and Swiss Boulevard and in Pune with C.T. Pundole & Sons.
        ]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20130418_1_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20130418_1_2">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20130418_1_3">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20130418_1_4">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2013</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20130409_1" date="2013-04-09">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Swiss Ernest Borel Presented 2013 Brand-new Commercial Shot in Switzerland:<br>Romantic Journey of Couple Watches]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Honored as a model for Swiss couple watches, Swiss Ernest Borel invited the artist Maria Chen and the TV host Cheuk Li to film the brand’s new 2013 commercial. This TV Commercial involved a film crew comprised of more than ten professionals for filming in the well-known watch manufacturing region of Le Noirmont, Switzerland. The grand premiere of the commercial took place on March 4, bringing the audience the feeling of the brand's exquisite watchmaking craftsmanship and its classic, romantic history! Shot mainly in three locations, the brand’s new factory in Le Noirmont, a lively urban scene and a fascinating night scene, this commercial exudes a romantic atmosphere, especially when accompanied by the couple’s loving, sincere dialogue.  It is a romantic journey for the model of Swiss couple watches, presenting the brand’s classic concept of Romantic Moments. In order to catch the most romantic moment, the film crew went on location early in the morning for preparation, while the two highly experienced artists were also very professional in that they carefully checked the script and repeatedly tested camera positions before filming. They replayed the video after each shooting and gave professional advice in order to film the most perfectly sincere and loving scenes.

          To tie in with the theme of a romantic commercial, Maria, with no fear of the cold weather, dressed in an elegant evening gown and danced with Cheuk Li in front of classic European architecture to successfully recreate the brand logo - a couple of dancing lovers. In addition, the fashion show host, Cheuk Li, with his unique charisma and courtesy, made shooting the scene a pleasant experience and filled the atmosphere with Romance.

          The film crew was particularly charmed by an elegant garden in the middle of the mountain from which one could overlook the city’s spectacular views. The two performers were wearing the brand’s classic watch from the Romance Series III and Jules Borel Collections, interpreting romantic, loving feelings in the garden, displaying the brand’s concept of “romance and elegance." To better understand the brand’s history, they even visited Ernest Borel’s brand new factory in person, to see first-hand its modern equipment and exquisite watchmaking craftsmanship.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20130409_1" video="http://www.youtube.com/embed/5kdVMEbj_WY">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2013</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20130403_1" date="2013-04-03">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[2013 SWISS ERNEST BOREL PRESENTATION OF ROMANTIC NEW SPRING COLLECTION]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[(Hong Kong) Honored as a model for Swiss couple watches, Ernest Borel embodies romantic, stylish and graceful qualities. The brand concept of “romantic moments” by Ernest Borel watches has been the instigation for innumerable moving couple stories. In springtime, romance is in the air! And what better way to create a lasting memory of this romance than with an ingeniously romantic timepiece? Ernest Borel Swiss watches have launched the new Romance Series II and Jules Borel Collections,  adhering to the brand’s unique logo and philosophy. The former, composed of glittering stones with delicate geometric lines and the latter’s luxurious touch of an 18 carat pink gold bezel, create the most romantic and uniquely stylish collection of this season. The power of love is evoked with breathtaking style, and since the initial inauguration of the Romance Series, watch lovers have enthousiatically recommended the watches with their perfect combination of geometric art and fashion design and instilled with romantic legend. The 2013 Spring Romantic Series II presents six watch models, each perpetuating the legendary 150-year history of Ernest Borel. The highlighted products, GS1856N-4090 and LS1856N-4090, are designed by watchmakers with glittering, graceful MOP dials and dazzling diamonds. Each dial is unique, adding an elegant touch. The center circle radial stripes, coupled with irregular circumference texture distribution and Roman numerals gives the watches different layers of texture, creating a unique geometric style. The carefully crafted line design also symbolizes the pursuit of free love. It is worth mentioning that the new series' have Ernest Borel’s unique “hand in hand” strap structure, which builds  upon the scenario of holding your lover’s hand and growing old with each other; timelessly and sincerely romantic!

				In addition to meticulous design, Ernest Borel watches also uphold the principles of watchmaking through their excellent performance. Those who favor high performance watches cannot miss another of the brand’s new products: the Jules Borel Collection. The model is named in honor of Ernest Borel’ s founder, Mr. Jules Borel, for his outstanding contributions to the brand and the over 150 year impact he made on the industry. The Jules Borel Collection is equipped with a high-end Soprod9040 movement which has  excellent mechanical properties. Coupled with the ingenious design of kinetic display, the wearer can see the flow of time on the wrist; the silver dial set with 15 natural diamonds and the 18K pink gold bezel and midddle chain links on the bracelet exude classic, elegant charm; the scale on the kinetic display is also embellished with diamonds, adding to the luxury!
				]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20130403_1_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20130403_1_2">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20130403_1_3">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2013</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20130402_1" date="2013-04-02">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Ernest Borel To Sponsor USA Dance National DanceSport Championships in Los Angeles; Judging By ABC’s ‘Dancing With The Stars’ Celebrity Judge Bruno Tonioli]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[LE NOIRMONT, SWITZERLAND -- Having successfully expanded its market position in the United States in recent years, the legendary Swiss watchmaker Ernest Borel is now the official sponsor of the 2013 National Star Quality Awards at the upcoming USA Dance 2013 National DanceSport Championships in Los Angeles. Held at the JW Marriott Hotel/LA Live!, on Friday, April 5 and Saturday, April 6, this event will be live streamed during the evening sessions. You may visit the following link to watch it live:

          <a target="_blank" style="color:#8B7F65;" href="http://www.livestream.com/usadance?utm_source=lsplayer&utm_medium=embed&utm_campaign=footerlinks">http://www.livestream.com/usadance?utm_source=lsplayer&utm_medium=embed&utm_campaign=footerlinks</a>

          The 4th annual National Star Quality Awards will be judged by Honorary Judge Bruno Tonioli, ABC-TV’s celebrity judge for “Dancing With The Stars”. Now celebrating its 16th season, it is the network’s number one-rated reality show, with millions of viewers throughout the world.  Along with Bruno Tonioli, the National Star Quality Awards on Friday and Saturday evenings will be presented to DanceSport couples in 11 championship divisions by Ernest Borel representatives Pietro Meloni of Switzerland, International Sales and Marketing Director, and Thomas Huggler, Business Development Manager for the USA.

          The National Star Quality Awards, a tradition started in 2009 by Dancing With The Stars celebrity judge Carrie Ann Inaba, are considered among the most prestigious amateur DanceSport awards bestowed in the industry. At the Championship Division level, from Pre-Teen to Senior I (ages 35 to 44), dancers must unequivocably demonstrate an exceptional level of star performer quality. As Ken Richards, USA Dance Vice President of DanceSport, explained, star quality criteria is often called “the X Factor,” and is best measured and judged by those whose own professional careers have embodied those rare attributes and achievements. Even the best DanceSport athletes want to be known for their artistry, their expressive performance and their creativity. For the athlete, it can be their competitive edge.

          Ernest Borel is sponsoring the 2013 National Star Quality Awards for the second year in a row. In January, Ernest Borel and USA Dance also signed a co-branding sponsorship alliance, both sharing missions to expand their outreach in the United States. As Pietro Meloni explained, what brought Ernest Borel and USA Dance together are their shared   inherent values of precision movement and timing and the embodiment of romance, passion and artistry. The Ernest Borel-USA Dance co-branding alliance is a strategic, win-win relationship for both brand partners. “And, the timing couldn’t be better,” confirmed Pietro Meloni, adding that “Ernest Borel has returned to America in celebration of the traditions that launched and have sustained our company’s brand for a century and a half, but even more so, the Ernest Borel brand association comes at a time when dance is  inspiring mass audiences throughout America and around the world.”

          ABOUT USA DANCE: USA Dance, a member organization of the U.S. Olympic Committee and the World DanceSport Federation, is the country’s leading DanceSport association.  With 174 social dance chapters throughout the country and the primary mission to support America’s DanceSport athletes by providing the highest level of ballroom and latin competitive dance and training opportunities, USA Dance supports the global movement to bring DanceSport to the Olympic Games. One can say Ernest Borel has become the “official timekeeper” of USA Dance and for DanceSport. Among the world’s fast-growing competitive sports, dance has been recognized by the International Olympic Committee, and is heading to The World Olypmic Games 2013 as an official sport in Cali, Colombia, South America.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20130402_1_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20130402_1_2">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2013</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20130314_1" date="2013-03-15">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[The Swiss watch brand Ernest Borel will be at the 2013 Basel Watch Fair  – from April 25 to May 2]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[The 41st edition of BASELWORLD –The Watch Fair, in Basel, Switzerland – will be marked this year by the official inauguration of the new exposition hall. The Ernest Borel brand will participate in the 2013 Watch Faire and is pleased to invite you to come and discover our latest models. We hope that you will also appreciate the architecturale design of our new stand. We look forward to greeting you in Hall 2.2 Hall of Visions First Avenue – Stand # B05.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20130314_1_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20130314_1_2">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2013</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20121228_1" date="2012-12-28">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[The Swiss watch brand Ernest Borel presents the latest models from its latest Romance Series III collection during a Christmas lights ceremony in Nanning]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Nanning, 8th December 2012. In Nanning, a city located in southern China, Christmas is fast approaching and the famous Swiss watch brand Ernest Borel has organized a presentation of its Romance Series III collection during a Christmas lights ceremony at the Landmark Dream Island Shopping Center Plaza. Mr Su, director of Ernest Borel Asia-Pacific, and Ms Kelly Chen (Chen Huilin), brand ambassador, inaugurate the ceremony together and welcome the numerous people who are in attendance. Loyal to its philosophy of creating ”romantic moments”  through its watches, Ernest Borel created a veritable fairy tale castle, with red and gold towers creating a warm Christmas atmosphere. From its imposingly solemn red and white walls emanates an impression of luxury and royal magnificence. The snowflakes scattered on the top of the castle add a wintery touch without which the Christmas party would seem incomplet. But the most unforgettable moment will remain the stage presentation of the fairy tale “Beauty and the Beast”. It is the tale of an egocentric and arrogant prince who is transformed by a witch into a repulsive beast; the prince, who falls in love with a beautiful girl named Belle, repents his ways and is transformed back into his human form thanks to the power of love. The moral of the story is that a love that is pure and sincere always brings with it the hope and guarantee of happiness. This corresponds perfectly with the philosophy of Ernest Borel, and the Romance Series III collection is testimony to this. As the brand ambassador, Ms Kelly Chen then got up on stage and opened, in front of a public that was at once seduced and in admiration, a mysterious box which, when opened revealed, like precious gems in a jewel box, the magnificent new watches in the Romance Series III collection by Ernest Borel. Ms Kelly Chen siezed this magic moment in order to share with auditors her own concept of love and romantisme, in which “sincerity and honesty are the two pillar feelings of romantic love, like a kind of force that is gentle yet strong”. After this presentation, Ms Kelly Chen and Mr Su  proceeded to light the Christmas lights together, a fairy-like moment where the castle suddenly appeared as if it was studded with innumerable shining stars. Mr Su  then spoke of the history and philosophy of Ernest Borel and ended with these words: “I am very happy with the success of this beautiful ceremony and wish that these romance filled moments that you have just experienced, as well as the shining image of this fairy tale castle will remain in your memories and help you to have very happy Christmas holidays and an excellent New Year! I thank you all for coming and also for being attached to our brand philosophy, which I would resume in these few words: create for you romantic moments by offering you high quality watches, bearers of life and love”.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20121228_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20121228_2">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20121228_3">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20121228_4">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2012</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20121207_1" date="2012-12-07">
			<title>
				<![CDATA["A Time 4 You", the new concert event by Raymond Lam (Lin Feng) in 2013 in Hong Kong]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[“A Time 4 You”, the fourth tour in Hong Kong by the singer Raymond Lam, will take place in the Coliseum, from the 26 to the 28 January 2013. For the third consecutive year, the Swiss watch brand Ernest Borel will be one of the sponsors of this event. The theme of “time” will be the main thread of this concert wherein Raymond Lam will push his technique and his speed to the utmost limits. He will share this breathtaking performance with his fans. A video entitled “Give Me One Minute to say I Love You”, sponsored and coproduced by Ernest Borel, will be released in early December.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20121207_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20121207_2">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20121207_3">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2012</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20121104_1" date="2012-11-04">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[The new additions to the Royal collection of Ernest Borel watches is luxuriously revealed in Shenzhen]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Shenzhen 4th November 2012. The Swiss watch brand Ernest Borel revealed in a press conference the new models in its Royal collection in Cocopark, in the city of Shenzhen in the south of China. Mr Su , the director of Ernest Borel Asia-Pacific, and Mr Raymond Lam (Lin Feng), an ambassador for Ernest Borel, inaugurated the ceremony. Surrounded by numerous romantic sites, such as Dameisha island, nicknamed Lover’s Island, Wutongshan point and Shahe Park, the city of Shenzhen, which is the youngest metropolis in all of China, doesn’t suffer any lack of romanticism. Since its creation in 1856, the Swiss brand Ernest Borel has always associated the best of its technology and the excellence of its master craftsmen with romantic love. The arrival of the new watches in its Royal collection in  Shenzhen is the consecration of a brand for which the signature carries with it the stamp of time and for over 150 years, has flowed to the rythm of the most romantic of life’s moments. Messrs Raymond Lam and Su  both inserted their swords into the “Royal” column and it opened, allowing a royal crown to appear rising slowly to reveal the new pair of watches in the Royal collection, for which the source of inspiration was royal love. These two new models both have a high quality automatic movement, protected by a stainless steel watchcase, plated with 10 microns of 18 carat pink gold. The dial has an “engine turned” decor, with the date at 3 o’clock and fluorescent hands, and is set with 10 natural diamonds. Mr Raymond Lam was able, by his presence, to give this ceremony a dimension that we can quite justly qualify as being royal. A renowned actor, he has often held roles in connection with romantic love. On a personal level, he quite gladly defines himself as having a very traditional concept of love: “Men and women start off by meeting each other, then they appreciate one another, fall in love and, finally live together. This image of an eternal love where two people walk hand in hand is among the most  romantic.” Mr Su  said, for his part: “To celebrate the opening of a boutique in Cocopark and hold this press conference in Shenzhen makes me feel the full romantic ambiance that is the charm of this young metropolis”. He then thanked the inhabitants of Shenzhen for their support and kindness, and formulated the wish that this new pair of watches from the Royal collection may further strengthen the bonds between the citizens of Shenzhen and Ernest Borel watches.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20121104_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20121104_2">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20121104_3">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20121104_4">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20121104_5">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2012</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20121120_1" date="2012-10-28">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Presentation in Tianjin of new models from the Royal collection of Swiss watches by Ernest Borel]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Tianjin, 28 October 2012. Mr Su, director of Ernest Borel Asia-Pacific, and Ms Angie Chiu (Zhao Yazhi), brand ambassador, arrived together in Tianjin to present the new pair of watches in the Royal collection. Tianjin, which is also known as “The Pearl of Bohai sea”, is the most important seaside city in the north of China and the first to have opened up to the outside world. Six centuries of history and most particularly these last hundred years, have shaped the city of Tianjin, giving it its unique style and apparence, a sort of alloy of old and new. The Swiss watch brand Ernest Borel, after over one and a half centuries of existence blending elegance and romanticism is, for the residents of Tianjin today, the image of the alliance between european nobility and chinese culture. Mr Su  wanted to have this press conference in the city of Tianjin in order to bring the Ernest Borel brand closer to the inhabitants of this city that so adeptly combines tradition with modernity, and also to breath into it a fragrance of romanticism. Situated in the bustling commercial center of Tianjin, the Quanyechang Shopping Mall has become the place to be in the city. A man and a woman dancing the waltz, like lovers in a bygone day, is the image used by the Swiss brand Ernest Borel since its creation to convey its message of elegance and love. When Mr Su , Ms Angie Chiu and Mr Yongsheng, general director of Quanyechang (Group) Co. Ltd in Tianjin, inaugurated all together the launch of this new pair of watches in Ernest Borel’s Royal collection, the second hands immediately started ticking, thus marking the entrance of these new watches in Tianjin. The guests then raised a toast to celebrate the event, wishing that all could experience the same romance as that depicted by Ernest Borel watches.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20121120_1_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20121120_1_2">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20121120_1_3">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20121120_1_4">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2012</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20121119_1" date="2012-10-27">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Presentation in Dalian of new models from the Royal collection of Swiss watches by Ernest Borel]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Dalian, 27 October 2012. The Swiss watch brand Ernest Borel invited its prestigious ambassador, Ms Angie Chiu (Zhao Yazhi), to Dalian to present the new models in the Royal collection. Nicknamed “The Pearl of the Orient”, the city of Dalian is renowned for its charm and elegance. White fences, beaches of the finest sand and vast green parks make it a romantique garden. Since its creation in 1856, the Swiss watch brand Ernest Borel has been struck with the seal of romanticism. The presence of the brand’s ambassador, Ms Angie Chiu, who is admired by hundreds of millions of people for whom she personifies the height of elegance and refinement, was particularly noticed at the press conference. Concerning the notions of love and romance attached to Ernest Borel watches, she declared: “I admire the dimension of love, but I also attach great importance to the charm of romance and to the fact that one must constantly maintain it. For me, romance is always paying attention to one’s partner, supporting each other in difficult times as well as in happy times, and to do this for your whole life.” When Angie Chiu inserted her sword, symbol of authority and glory, into the “Royal” column, a dazzling crown rose slowly up, revealing the new pair of  watches in the Royal collection. Mr Su , director of Ernest Borel Asia-Pacific, presented the Ernest Borel brand philosophy to representatives of the media, specifying in particular that “this romantic city in the north, Dalian, was predestined due to its elegance and romantic charm, to welcome in its heart the Swiss watch brand Ernest Borel”. He then thanked the inhabitants of Dalian for the quality and warmth of their welcome and formulated his wish that a long and profitable collaboration should be installed between Ernest Borel and the city of Dalian. Today, Ernest Borel’s reputation as a brand that creates romantic watches, as well as the quality and elegance of its products, is well anchored in the world. The watches in the Royal collection are perfectly matched. The men’s model, refined and distinguished, is perfectly matched with the ladies model which is soft and elegant; they both combine force and tenderness perfectly. At the conclusion of the presentation, Ms Angie Chiu wished to all those present the power to experience a love that is both eternal and romantic, and that Ernest Borel Swiss watches could bring to each of them a lifestyle tinted with love and romance.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20121119_1_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20121119_1_2">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20121119_1_3">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20121119_1_4">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20121119_1_5">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2012</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20121021_1" date="2012-10-21">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Presentation in Zhengzhou of new models from the Royal collection of Swiss watches by Ernest Borel]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Zhengzhou 21st October 2012. In the plains of the Chinese province of Henan, Mr Su , director of Ernest Borel Asia-Pacific, and Ms Angie Chiu (Zhao Yazhi), ambassador for Ernest Borel Swiss watches, opened the press conference together that was organised in Zhengzhou to present the new watch models in the Royal collection by Ernest Borel. Mr Su  introduced the conference by explaining to members of the media that Ernest Borel had chosen the city of Zhengzhou to present its collection in the hope of creating close ties between the residents and the Ernest Borel brand and also in the hope that the noble and romantic image of its watches would spread across the fertile lands of the central plains of Henan. The city of Zhengzhou, renowned for its glorious history and its cultural richness, could not miss the opportunity to welcome Ernest Borel, a brand with over 150 years’ experience creating watches which have a reputation for nobility and romantic charm. An elegant, romantic couple dances in the square situated across from the  Dashang New-Mart Jinboda store in Zhengzhou’s city-center. The gracefulness of the dancers draws the attention of the public, inspiring a mixture of feelings, nobility and romanticism –¬ two concepts that are the very source of inspiration for the creators of Ernest Borel watches, which are also known as “lover’s watches”. Mr Su , Ms Angie Chiu and Mr Zhang Jie, general director of the Dashang New-Mart Jinboda store, inaugurated the launch of the new watches from the Royal collection. Ms Angie Chiu, always very refined and elegant, brought with her an additional touch of seduction to this event. A famous actress, Angie Chiu has interpreted romantic roles in numerous films and television shows and represents the image of Ernest Borel  watches with great class. She then, accompanied by Messrs. Su  and Zhang Jie, raised a toast celebrating the official arrival of the latest Royal collection models and wished the best of success to the watch fair in Jinboda. They also wished that everyone could experience romantic moments with the “lover’s watches” by the Swiss watch maker Ernest Borel.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20121021_1_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20121021_1_2">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20121021_1_3">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
				<image id="20121021_1_4">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2012</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20120926_1" date="2012-09-26">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Raymond Lam (Lin Feng ) embarks on a romantic cruise on the high seas with Ernest Borel Swiss watches]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Raymond Lam has once again embarked on a publicity tour for the Swiss watch maker Ernest Borel, for whom he has been the spokesperson for the past five years. During its 156 years of existence, Ernest Borel has remained the unchanging bearer of the romantic image of a loving couple that has, with the languishing steps of a waltz, led the history of Ernest Borel watches in an eternal romance. The advertising message has for a theme a “Romantic cruise”, wherein Raymond Lam undertakes a sail on the high seas on a luxurious sailboat leaving from the bay of Aberdeen Shum Wan Pier. Ernest Borel invested over a million Hong Kong dollars to rent the sailboat, a Sun Odyssey made by the famous cruise and competition shipbuilder, French Jeanneau. This luxurious sailboat is capable of confronting storms and raging elements. Its design as well as the luxury and confort of its infrastructures matches the creative and perfectionist spirit of Ernest Borel watch makers and is an ideal source of inspiration for photographers. Another boat, in which the members of the technical team embarked, accompanied the sailboat. Raymond Lam, wearing a completely white  suit and a v-necked sweater, is seen to be very much at ease on board the Sun Odyssey, perfectly integrated into the natural environnement that surrounds him, in harmony with the sea, the sky and the sun. He appears elegant, sure of himself and smiling as he sports a watch from the Retro collection on his wrist. It is a perfectly romantic moment, the very image of the Ernest Borel brand. Raymond Lam admitted having enjoyed this romantic cruise very much as he rarely has a chance to get out on the high seas due to his busy professional schedule. This time, he was able to combine work with pleasure, something which is very rare for him. “After posing for the pictures, I was able to find time to lie out in the sun on the deck with seemingly not a care in the world. It’s my most recent and most joyous romantic trip”, he declared with a smile. This Ernest Borel advertisement will be visible in October.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20120926_1">
					<![CDATA[1 Royal Hands Ignite Eternal Romance]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2012</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20120920_1" date="2012-09-20">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Presentation in Beijing of the new models in the Royal collection of Swiss watches by Ernest Borel and launching of the “Romantic Cruise” advertising campaign]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Beijing 20th September 2012. On the central axe in Beijing, at # 23 Qianmen Beijing, the Swiss watch brand Ernest Borel presented the newest models in its Royal collection and took this occasion to launch its “Romantic Cruise” advertising campaign. The ambassadors for Ernest Borel, Ms Angie Chiu (Zhao Yazhi) and Ms Kelly Chen (Chen Huilin), Mr Raphaël Boillat, president of Ernest Borel Suisse, and Mr Su , director of Ernest Borel Asia-Pacific, were all present at this grand event. The city of Beijing, the capital of China, is known throughout the world for having been the seat of imperial China as well as for its exceptional monuments, such as the Forbidden City, the Summer Palace and the Great Wall of China, which protected the border of the ancient “Middle Kingdom”. One can practically feel the centuries of history and royalty. The watch brand Ernest Borel, created over a century and a half ago, also has a history that is filled with noble sentiments, elegance and distinction. The watches are steeped with romanticism perfectly combining this symbol of Chinese imperial power, dominant and majestic, with the elegant and distinguished nobility of the Royal collection. A collection wherein the watches presented here reflect a royal love which is the source of their inspiration. Ms Angie Chiu makes her appearance in front of the guests, who are subjugated by her exquisitely refined elegance. It seems that every year she appears more gracious and distinguished, and her presence at the inauguration of the launch of the new Ernest Borel watches is an invaluable homage to a lifestyle of distinction and elegance imprinted with the most seductive of romantic charms. When Ms Angie Chiu lifted the imperial scepter and set it slowly and gracefully on the table where the watches were displayed, everyone was breathless, enthralled by her queenly bearing. She then majestically revealed the new pair of watches from the Royal collection. Next, the president of Ernest Borel Switzerland, Mr Raphaël Boillat, invited Ms Kelly Chen to present the other grand event, the launching of the new Ernest Borel watches advertising campaign: the “Romantic cruise”. Ms Kelly Chen is the  star of this advertising campaign which was made in Hong Kong. During the filming, the sun was shining and its rays glittered on the waves around the boat, while Ms Kelly Chen spoke: “Life is a voyage where, like waves, the ups and the downs intermingle.” And yet, no impetuous wave nor storm came to disrupt Kelly Chen’s voyage, which can be seen in the reflection of a happy family and a brilliant career. During the ceremony, Ms Angie Chiu and Ms Kelly Chen wished all the guests that they, too, should experience such romantic moments during their lives. Then the president, Mr Raphaël Boillat, speaking on behalf of Ernest Borel Switzerland, expressed the wish that “Ernest Borel watches may reinforce their position in various world markets and that they may incite more and more people to experience the “romantic moments” that they convey”. During the presentation of the new Royal collection models, Ms Angie Chiu and Ms Kelly Chen as well as Messrs. Raphaël Boillat and Su  shared anecdotes with the guests about romantic moments they had experienced themselves. These exchanges were very much appreciated by the guests and were felt to have been experienced by everyone through this “romantique voyage”. At the end of the ceremony, everyone present raised a toast to the Swiss watch brand Ernest Borel, wishing that it may continue to spread its message throughout the world of romance, of love, so that all may have such wonderful, romantic moments in their lives.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20120920_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2012</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20120920_2" date="2012-09-20">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[The Swiss watch brand Ernest Borel invited to Wangfujing International Brand Festival 2012 in Beijing]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Once again the Swiss watch brand Ernest Borel has been invited to participate in the Wangfujing International Brand Festival. The new pair of watches in the Royal collection, in particular, lit up the Festival, for which the theme was “ International Brands and Cities of the world”. Inspired by the concept of royal love, this new pair of watches strives to be a romantic image of the grandeur of european royal families. The european style of the models in the Royal collection, launched by the Swiss watch brand Ernest Borel, perfectly reflects the reason for being of this Festival: “to facilitate exchanges between China and foreign brands”. Representatives of Beijing’s town council, the president of Ernest Borel Switzerland, Mr Raphaël Boillat, the director of Ernest Borel Asia-Pacific, Mr Su , as well as representatives of the media were all present. Ms Kelly Chen (Chen Huilin), spokeswoman and ambassador for Ernest Borel, cut the silk ribbon marking the access to the Ernest Borel pavilion at the exposition located on Wangfujing Avenue. Since its creation in 1856, Ernest Borel has had as an objective to create watches that guarantee the criteria of perfection, precision and reliability, of quality and durability, elegance  and user-friendliness. This is how throughout its centuries-old history, Ernest Borel has shaped its brand identity by offering a lifestyle to a clientele that loves perfection, romanticism and fashion. Time goes by, but the convictions that animate Ernest Borel’s will to create perfect beauty and to remain at the cutting edge of fashion persist. After Ms Kelly Chen’s ribbon cutting ceremony, the president of Ernest Borel Switzerland, Mr Raphaël Boillat, officially invited his guests to enter the pavilion where the different watch collections were on display, but most especially to admire the latest addition to the Royal collection, which was the  highlight of the exposition: this new pair of watches sparkled brilliantly under the lights. Through its presence at the Wangfujing International Brand Festival in Beijing, the Swiss watch brand Ernest Borel demonstrated its will to offer clients around the world the possibility to experience, through its watches, the kind of dreamy, romantic moments that make life beautiful.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20120920_2">
					<![CDATA[Romantic Moment]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2012</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20120914_1" date="2012-09-14">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Raymond Lam (Lin Feng) in Shanghai presented the latest model of Ernest Borel  Royal Collection]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Shanghai, 8th September 2012 : In Shanghai, Mr Su , director of Ernest Borel Asia-Pacific, accompanied by Mr Raymond Lam (Lin Feng), ambassador for Ernest Borel, unveiled the new pair of watches in the Royal collection. Shanghaï is a city at once fascinating and full of charm, but also very contrasting, with “thousands of styles”. Where the closed mindset of the middle-class mingles with the noble and majestic. Where great intentions, tree-lined avenues, architecture styles inspired from every corner of the world  and  animated markets  give off an air of romance and luxuriance. Founded in 1856, the Swiss watch brand Ernest Borel is renowned for the quality of its watches that are linked with a beautiful and romantic love story. For over a century and a half, it has touched the minds of all those who have encountered the elegance and nobility of its products, handing down from one generation to the next the image of “the lover’s watch”. The new pair of watches in the Royal collection, launched today, are the perfect illustration of this. And the grandeur of the site in which the ceremony unfolds, with its white and gold decor and the majestic spiral staircase, exhudes the sentiment of being in a sumptuous royal palace. The ceremony  began with the famous song from the first act of Verdi’s “La Traviata”: Libiamo Ne’ Lieti Calici… “Let's drink, let's drink from this merry chalice” which is an ode to love. The watches in Ernest Borel’s Royal collection have always exalted the beauty and romantic purity of royal love and, according to Mr Su , “the choice of Shanghaï for this presentation is not only a response to the support and fidelity of our customers, but also because the charm and elegance of this city is in perfect harmony with the romantic message carried by Ernest Borel watches”. Mr Su  then presented Mr Raymond Lam, ambassador for Ernest Borel, as being “the romantic prince” adored by the public, corresponding perfectly with the image of royal love that inspired the creation of this new pair of watches. Mr Raymond Lam, declared that for him, this pair of Ernest Borel watches is the most romantic and elegant image to be found of royal love. After this, Messrs.  Su  and Raymond Lam opened together the jewel box that was presented to them by the two palace guards, allowing the guests in attendance to discover the extraordinary beauty of these watches. The men’s model radiates energy, strength, righteousness and distinction, while the ladies’ model exhudes tenderness, exquisite softness, elegance, charm and beauty. A harmonious combination of strength and tenderness, this pair of watches is the brillantly successful realization of over a century and a half of devoted effort by the master craftsmen of Ernest Borel in the search for watch making perfection. Upon offering these watches to Mr Raymond Lam, Mr Su  also offered him the romantic spirit inspired by Ernest Borel and wished that he be the vector of this spirit via his respectful attitude towards royal romantic love. At the ceremony’s end, Messrs Su  and Raymond Lam invited their guests to lift their  “merry chalices” in a toast, wishing that everyone could live the kind of romance depicted by royal love and that the Ernest Borel  brand may continue to spread its romantic message via its “lover’s watches”.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20120914_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2012</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20120906_1" date="2012-09-05">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Inauguration of the first Ernest Borel Swiss watches boutique in Hong Kong, in conjunction with the presentation of the Romance Series III collection]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[The Swiss watch manufacturer Ernest Borel, which celebrated its 155th anniversary last year and for which the degree of popularity has increased by 20% in just two years, according to the “Baidu” classification, continues its rapid expansion and reinforces its position in the Asia-Pacific market by opening its first boutique in Hong Kong in Yee Wo Street in the Causeway Bay. The inauguration, which took place on September 5th, was presided over by Ms Angie Chiu (Zhao Yazhi) and Ms Kelly Chen (Chen Huilin), brand ambassador, in the presence of Messrs Raphaël Boillat, president of Ernest Borel Switzerland, and Mr Su , director of Ernest Borel Asia-Pacific, as well as numerous guests and representatives of the media. Mr Raphaël Boillat reminded everyone in his opening speech that since its creation in 1856 and still today, Ernest Borel has become an internationally renowned brand of watches, known for its classic watch styles that also take into account current fashion trends, elegance, quality and reliability. The concept of the Ernest Borel brand remains steadfastly centered on the romantic image of the watch “a lifelong companion”. Ernest Borel continues its progression on the world market with the opening of numerous boutiques in different countries; in Switzerland, of course, but also in the United States of America, France and Ireland. The brand has maintained a strong presence on the Chinese market for over twenty years with results that are truly remarkable. Ernest Borel blends  traditional Chinese culture and heritage with styles that are currently popular with clients in this country, where there are no less than 800 Ernest Borel shops. The global number of points of sale in the Asia-Pacific region increases by 8% every year. In order to provide the best customer service, Ernest Borel has opened fifty after-sales service centers throughout the country and the number is constantly rising. The brand decided to increase its investments in the Chinese market as well as in the rest of the world in order to better diffuse its image of quality, perfection and romance-tinted elegance, always at the cutting edge of fashion. Mr Su , of Ernest Borel Asia-Pacific, then spoke about the opening of the first boutique in Hong Kong, reminding all that Ernest Borel had first begun develop the markets in Hong Kong and Southeast Asia in the 1960’s and 1970’s, perfecting the manufacturing of watches, sales and after-sales service and striving to offer the best quality and service to its customers. This first boutique, inaugurated in a very animated commercial district in Hong Kong, will allow the concept of perfection, the basis of the brand’s philosophy, to be better diffused, as well as providing complet and professional service to clients, reinforcing the brand image locally and contributing to the development of its overseas activities. For the occasion of this boutique opening, Ms Kelly Chen and Ms Angie Chiu then presented the Romance Series III collection which so aptly reflects the brand’s history. This particular boutique offers a spacious and comfortable environnement that is very appropriate for the acquisition of high quality watches. The Causeway Bay neighborhood center where it is situated is very busy and has numerous other watch and jewelry boutiques. It is therefore, for Ernest Borel, a major entryway into the Hong Kong market and even a foothold in South-East Asia. The boutique’s interior decorating tastefully and delicately highlights the brand color which is brick-red. The Italian marble floor in which the veins suggest natural wood blend harmoniously with the brick-red tint of the walls, which are also painted in a trompe-l’œil fashion to look like natural wood. The arch-shaped display cases and false ceilings are illuminated by LED bulbs, and the overall atmosphere is soft, harmonious and romantic. The brand logo, representing a dancing couple, is also made up of LED bulbs, and its outline is highlighted by a metal structure that adds a contemporary touch to this romantic vision. The visual effect is both original and pleasing to the eye. The address for the new Ernest Borel boutique in Hong Kong is: Shop B, No. 1, Yee Wo Street, Causeway Bay, Hong Kong.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20120906_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2012</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<!-- <news id="20120827_1" date="2012-08-27">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Kelly Chen Presented the Romantic Journey for Ernest Borel]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Ms. Kelly Chen, the advertising spokesperson for Ernest Borel, acted to be photographed in the latest advertisement for Ernest Borel. With a history of 156 years and the concept of "Romantic Moment", Ernest Borel perfectly combines the romantic story of the lovers' logo and the rigorous and excellent watch-making craftsmanship. Kelly is also a perfectionist and tries to make everything perfect. Her image of happiness and romance also closely relates herself to Ernest Borel. Kelly has been the advertising spokesperson for Ernest Borel over these three years. This advertisement was themed as "the Romantic Journey" and Kelly boarded the luxury cruise romantically to present the romantic journey.

          After the cruise set off in the Aberdeen Shum Wan Pier, passengers put their worries and concerns aside and began the romantic journey of Ernest Borel far way from the dins and dons of the earthly world. Ernest Borel spent more than one hundred thousand HK dollars on the rental of the three luxury cruises, whose classical design and delicate craftsmanship, plus the luxury decorations and comfortable layout, brought more muses for the photographer. Ernest Borel also invited the famous HK film art director Yee Chung-man to be the image consultant for this advertisement. Mr. Yee designed two appearance styles for Kelly on this cruise, both based on the inspiration of the ocean, the cruise and the sunshine to bring out the comfortable and leisurely summer breath. Kelly fully blended into the natural environment with the sky and the ocean merging into one. Dressed in a lily-white long-skirt giving her a mysterious sense with a small tint of sexy, she put on the Romance Series III and the latest Retro Collection of Ernest Borel and became more elegant and distinguished, presenting the perfect romantic time for Ernest Borel.

          Kelly said that she was enjoying this romantic journey Ernest Borel arranged for her. Despite the arduous photographing process and the high temperature, she was still dedicated and delighted and combined work with pleasure by playing well with the working staff. As delicious food was also provided on the cruise, it was like a voyage with best friends and everyone enjoyed it. Life is like a voyage on the sea, with changing climates. Kelly seems to have a smooth life with success in her working career and a happy family. But there must be happiness and sorrows. We hope that she can remain optimistic to enjoy every romantic journey and accept every challenge in the future.

          Kelly said happily, "The most romantic journey in my life was the recent travel with my husband and my son. It was the first travel for my son after he had grown up a little and we went to see the penguins for the first time. I felt happy when I saw him happy. It was the most romantic and nicest journey for me."]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20120827_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2012</tag>
			</tags>
		</news> -->
		<news id="20120717_1" date="2012-07-17">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Ernest Borel Journey of Romance on Luxurious Cruise in 2012]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[On 24th June 2012 Ernest Borel Journey of Romance on luxurious cruise witnessed a grand set-off in Shanghai after a long time preparation. Mr. Boillat, President of Swiss Ernest Borel, Mr. Su Da, CEO of the Asia-pacific area, and a total of nearly 500 distributors in the Asia-pacific area and popular artists embarked the luxurious Royal Caribbean Voyager of the Seas, one of the ten largest cruises in the world and the largest in Asia, and spent 5 days and 4 nights together in the journey of romance to Fukuoka of Japan and Jeju of South Korea.

          Established 156 years ago, the world-renowned Swiss Ernest Borel has been sticking to the core brand concept of "Romantic Moment". The host party specially moved the largest and most important event of Ernest Borel to a luxurious cruise in the ocean, which was full of romantic flavors, making it not only a feast for all senses but also the perfect presentation of Ernest Borel's brand spirit.

          On 25th June, the grand 2012 Ernest Borel Annual Conference was held in the Grand Theater on the cruise. Distributors across the world gathered here to witness the splendid achievements Ernest Borel had made these years. The conference began with the opening speech of Mr. Boillat. He extended heartfelt gratitude and congratulations to colleagues and business partners who had made enormous efforts for the exciting achievements of Ernest Borel. Then Mr. Su delivered an important speech. He summarized the new breakthroughs and take-offs of Ernest Borel in the past two years and set forth development direction in future.

          The conference invited performing masters to celebrate the event. As is known to all, the logo of Ernest Borel originated from the silhouette of a couple of dancing lovers. It combines romance and elegance which symbolizes eternal love and happiness. The famous dancer Yang Yang described the century-old history of Ernest Borel with retro classical dancing. Her movements also incorporated a strong sense of modern times, indicating that while maintaining the traditional Swiss watch-manufacturing techniques, Ernest Borel never stopped exploring new technology. Then, renowned magician Fu Yan Dong also presented the guests with a mysterious and warm romantic show. He gently waved his hands and filled the sky with falling snowflakes, making everyone present feel the romance of Ernest Borel. The limited edition watch for Ernest Borel's 155th anniversary, which disappeared and reappeared in the hands of the magic master, was given to a lucky guest as a lucky prize. Last but not least, Taiwan singer Huang Pin Yuan, famous for his love songs, appeared romantically on the stage and sang several love songs to embody Ernest Borel's unabated persistence and pursuit for love. With the graceful waltz of performing dancers, 2012 Ernest Borel Business Conference saw a perfect ending in the romantic love songs.

          Later in the evening, distributors well dressed-up and gathered in the elegant main dining room on the cruise. Guests toasted with Mr. Su Da to celebrate the success of this event. They held the red wine goblets high, wishing and praying for the splendid future of Ernest Borel. In this scene the guests were like in a warm and romantic Ernest Borel family. In addition, the waiters from all over the world in the dinning room also sang songs to celebrate, pushing the atmosphere of the dinner party to a climax.

          On the deck of the cruise, you feel too delighted to leave with the fresh sea wind blowing at your face. The romantic concept of Ernest Borel has once again made a deep impression with the natural stage of the blue sky, the ocean and the cruise. And the ever-lasting spirit of "romance" carried by Ernest Borel for centuries has indeed spread away.

          As Mr. Boillat put it in his opening speech, "We have been taking the brand motto"romance in heart" as our core spirit and we are sure to continue the resplendent legend of Ernest Borel successfully." Ernest Borel will surely plough through and sail further into a fantastic future.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20120717_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2012</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20120519_1" date="2012-05-19">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[The Release of Swiss Ernest Borel's Harmonic Collection in Nanning, Guangxi]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[May,19th, 2012 witnessed the release of Swiss Ernest Borel's Harmonic Collection in the ancient frontier city of Nanning, Guangxi. Present at the event were Su Da, CEO of Swiss Ernest Borel in Asia-Pacific area and Raymond, a well-known actor from Hong Kong and also the brand spokesman, along with models demonstrating Swiss Ernest Borel's latest Harmonic Collection in 2012. Later distinguished guests came to the exhibition zone of Wanda Plaza for the ribbon-cutting, making a grand scene.<br>
          It was a splendid event that started with eye-catching popping. Su Da officiated the release of Harmonic Collection together with the distinguished guests and RaymondLing Feng in the melodious music, pushing the event to a small climax. The elegant gentry manner of RaymondLing Feng attracted everyone present. He talked and interacted with the spectators, telling the story of his being attached to Ernest Borel watches. The Ernest Borel watch show led by RaymondLing Feng was the grand finale performance, with other models demonstrating the charm of the new collection, showing its elegant, noble and romantic temperate that belonged to the Ernest Borel brand. "Time records growth" was the most meaningful part of the event. Guests and spectators watched the video of Swiss Ernest Borel's 2012 charity activity "Romantic Loving Heart" in Guangxi and had a full knowledge of Ernest Borel's care and support of China's Education cause. In addition, student representatives from the beneficiary Disu Town Primary school and Anyang No.6 primary school extended their gratitude by singing the song "Grateful Heart" at the event. They also expressed to the effect that they would reply the care from the society with hard work.<br>
          At the end of release, guests, friends from the press and RaymondLing Feng went to the exhibition zone of Ernest Borel in Wanda Plaza for the ribbon-cutting of Ernest Borel's Harmonic Collection and were warmly welcomed. Displayed in the Ernest Borel zone were the newest design and other classics, bringing high quality of life for city residents.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20120519_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2012</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20120430_1" date="2012-04-30">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[The Grand Release of 2012 Swiss Ernest Borel's Limited Numbered Edition of Harmonic Collection in Changchun]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[After the initiation of 2011 Swiss Ernest Borel "Romance" in Shanghai and its continuum in Guangzhou and Xi'an, April, 30th, 2012 witnessed the arrival Of "Romance", swearing to spread romance to every corner of the world, with Swiss Ernest Borel's limited numbered edition of Harmonic Collection at the beautiful and prosperous city of Changchun.  In the open-air square of New World Shopping Park of Changchun, Li Ling, the famous mainland actress, and Li Bo, Swiss Ernest Borel's General Sales Director in China, released the Ernest Borel's limited numbered edition of Harmonic Collection together.

          The event began with passionate Latin dance. Li Ling came on stage with Li Bo, Swiss Ernest Borel's General Sales Director in China, representatives from the New World Shopping Park and lit the heart-to-heart lamps together. The romantic, gorgeous light and two closely related hearts set people in emotions of deep love and attachment. The lily-white pearl-mother gradually unfolded itself and released the romantic limited numbered edition of Harmonic Collection, which, with a MOP dial and natural diamonds, was glorious after its debut like a pearl coming into being through years of efforts.

          The limited numbered edition of Harmonic Collection has intensified the delicate shape of the harp and its artistic temperate. Its MOP dial gives out colorful light under the sunshine. The decoration of 30 natural diamonds in the form of heart in heart, one standing for love and the other beauty, presents the most precious love and beauty to her. Combined with romantic scales in Arabic hearts, it is elegant and luxury, making the best interpretation of love. The 999 limited numbered watches are put in special heart gift boxes. It is like you are listening to the beautiful music at the seaside, lost in the romance of the Aegean Sea.

          Li Bo said, " This edition gains its inspiration from the harp with a clear tone and elegant connotation. Lightsome and refreshing melody renders us into the feeling of bathing in the tender harmony, making her the best representation of "romance". Bouncing harp notes can convey our sincerity in affection to the deepest heart of our beloved ones. The limited numbered edition of Harmonic Collection, corresponding to the brand spirit of Swiss Ernest Borel with restless romance, is the wristwatch made for your beloved ones and also a sincere present to Changchun from Ernest Borel.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20120430_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2012</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20120418_1" date="2012-04-18">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Swiss Ernest Borel Charity Activity of 2012"Romantic Loving Heart"]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[April, 18th, 2012 witnessed the initiation of Swiss Ernest Borel's charities activity of 2012, "Romantic Love", in Du'an Yao People Autonomous County of Hedi, Guangxi Province. This activity was initiated by the county government and education officials in combination with Ernest Borel. The volunteer team of Ernest Borel led by Su Da and Angie Chiu, the charity ambassadress of Ernest Borel, went to the two poor primary schools----Disu Town Primary School and Anyang No.6 Primary School----together with the county government and education officials and offered their donations to those poverty-stricken pupils there.

          The volunteer team of Swiss Ernest Borel and Angie Chiu was warmly welcomed by the teachers, pupils and parents of the two schools. Su Da, Swiss Ernest Brorel CEO of Asia-Pacific area, made a speech in the donation ceremony to the effect that Ernest Borel would stick to its brand spirit of "100-year classical watches reach eternity with love" as an international renowned enterprise with a history of 156 years and continuously carry down love from generation to generation. This donation activity was only the first stop of Swiss Ernest Borel's charities activity of 2012, "Romantic Loving Heart" and would record the growth of the children and witness the future of them like Ernest Borel watches. Mr. Su also promised that they would spread love to the education field of China, Asia and even the world to grant more poverty-stricken pupils financial aids, improving their life and making them work harder.

          Also encouraging was the vigorous support from Du'an Yao People Autonomous County government and education officials. The county governmental officials said that there were still a lot of poor primary schools in this county and more loving-heart enterprises like Ernest Borel were expected to offer care and aids for children, creating better studying conditions for their healthy growth. They also expressed the hope that the children should work hard, be ready to help others and reply to the care from all walks of life with their performance. Mr. Su reiterated that Ernest Borel would continue to pay attention to education and carry on the social enterprise duties of aiding poor students. Meantime, Angie Chiu also extend her expectation that this activity could draw more care and support from all walks of life to bring care and hopes to students in need and enable all children grow up healthily.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20120418_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2012</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20120419_1" date="2012-04-19">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Ernest Borel's Limited Edition of Harmonic Collection Unveiled in Xi'an]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[In April, 13, 2012, the brand spokesperson, Angie Chiu, unveiled the limited edition of Harmonic Collection on the "blue Aegean Sea" together with Su Da, the CEO of Ernest Borel in the Asia-Pacific area, in Kaiyuan Shopping Mall, Xi'an.

          In the event, all the decorations were in breathtaking blue against the white wall. With the sound of wind chimes and the harp of exceptional artistic temperate, the romantic encounter on the Aegean Sea provoked the inspiration of the limited edition of Harmonic Collection. The event began with a duo modern ballet, smooth and elegant in the melodious sound of the harp, and brought the audience into a world of romance. Angie Chiu, Su Da and representatives from Kaiyuan Shopping Mall, lit the romantic heart-to-heart lamps and the lily-white pearl-mother unfolded itself slowly in the poetic music, setting off the romantic climax for the debut of the limited edition of Harmonic Collection.

          The limited edition of Harmonic Collection has intensified the delicate shape of the harp and its artistic temperate. Its MOP dial is decorated with 30 natural diamonds in the form of heart in heart, one standing for love and the other beauty, presenting the most precious love and beauty to her. Combined with romantic scales in Arabic hearts, it is elegant and luxury, making the best interpretation of love. The 999 limited watches are put in special heart gift boxes. It is like you are listening to the beautiful music at the seaside, lost in the romance of the Aegean Sea.

          The limited edition of Harmonic Collection has further indicated the brand spirit of "Romantic Moments" with its precious material and luxury design. Ernest Borel will continue with its romantic and elegant brand image to pursue extraordinary quality, at the same time, striving for excellence and bring more fantastic romantic stories to those who pursue perfection, fashion and romance.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20120419_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2012</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20120330_1" date="2012-03-30">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Official USA Dance Sponsor 2012]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[At the USA Dance 2012 National DanceSport Championships in Baltimore, to be held in March 30 - April 1 2012, Ernest Borel is pleased to announce its new sponsorship of USA Dance. Every year, the best dancers across the nations compete for the USA Dance National DanceSport Championships. This year, the competition is celebrating its 32 years.<br>
          Combining romanticism and elegance, the dancing couple trademark of Ernest Borel is designed to imply blessings for love and happiness. As a young man, Ernest Borel met a beautiful girl at a formal dance party. Their graceful dance attracted the envious eyes of all the other dancers and a picture was taken of this romantic encounter, suspending it in time. The elegant dance and the romance of the moment ignited Ernest Borel's inspiration, prompting him to design the trademark logo to immortalize this magical experience.<br>
          The dancing couple has been the brand's trademark and inspiration since the late 19th/early 20th century, this striking image becoming firmly established as the "Lovers" trademark.
          The USA Dance is the culminating event where the best of the best come as only those who place in the top 75 percent at qualifying competitions are invited to compete in Baltimore. This means approximately 20 DanceSport couple finalists will be selected to compete at 11 World Championships held throughout the year in countries around the globe. â€˜The best of the best" concept consistently follows the initial enterprise spirit and the belief of creating perfection. With skillful and talented inspiration, the craftsmen of Ernest Borel witnessed every exciting precious moment, embedding personality into time.

          The spirit of Ernest Borel provides an unchangeable lifestyle for all pursuing perfection, fashion and romance. Competitors of the USA Dance 2012 Nationals are expected to represent nearly every state in the nation, ranging from different age groups to show their perfect talent.

          Ernest Borel is the proud new sponsor of the USA Dance Nationals and its 3rd annual Star Quality Awards, to be judged and presented by Carrie Ann Inaba, Honorary Judge and new National Celebrity Ambassador for USA Dance.<br>
          Further in 2012, Ernest Borel will also sponsor some of the USA Dance 2012 National Qualifying Events.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20120330_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2012</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20120319_1" date="2012-03-19">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Ernest Borel (Switzerland) in Baselworld 2012 Embodiment of Classic and Fashion, Grace and Vitality]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[March 8th to 15th witnessed the 40th BASELWORLD, the world's annual watch event leading the global watch fashion, in Basel, Switzerland. Ernest Borel, who had just celebrated its 155th brand anniversary, displayed not only its Jules Borel Collection and Royal Collection of great historical significance and collection value, but also the striking Retro Collection to echo the retro trend hot in the fashion world this year. Over recent years, Ernest Borel has developed into an international watch brand that embodies classic and fashion, grace and vitality.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20120319_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2012</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20120316_1" date="2012-03-16">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Ernest Borel in Baselworld 2012 Ernest Borel Factory in Le Noirmont, Switzerland]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Entering the year of 2012, the factory of Ernest Borel in Le Noirmont(Switzerland) has made great improvement in developing and design, watch-making techniques and its production scale. The growing developing team has enriched and diversified Ernest Borel's products. Exquisite techniques have been Ernest Borel's commitment to watch-making in its history of 156 years. A large production scale provides Ernest Borel more confidence in gearing to the rapidly-developing global business, especially in the Asia-Pacific area where dramatic changes are taking place.
          Watchmakers and assembly workers are the hardcore of the watch production line. Ernest Borel, with a team of experienced technicians, also attaches importance to the cultivation of new technicians and provides them professional training on a regular basis, which not only infuses young and fresh air blood into the factory but also makes up the reserve of talents for long term planning.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20120316_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2012</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20120313_1" date="2012-03-13">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Swiss ERNEST BOREL New Arrival for Baselworld 2012]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[The annual global watch industry event -- 40th Swiss BASELWORLD was held ahead of schedule from March 8 to 15. Swiss ERNEST BOREL, just through its 155th Anniversary Celebration, is already well prepared; on the one hand, brings the after heat of its 155th Anniversary to Baselworld this year; and on the other hand, echoes the trend of fashion industry this yearâ€”â€”Retro, revealing its calm, elegant, fully dynamic, and fashionable side.<br>

          Jules Borel Collection is named after the founder Mr. Jules Borel to commemorate his outstanding contribution to Ernest Borel. His profoundimpact on the time-piece industry over 150 years, encourages future generations to pursue his "romantic &amp; elegant" philosophy.

          This line is an incarnation of romanticism and elegance; beside hour, minute, second and date indication, the features are emphasized by the white dial set with diamonds on the power reserve indicator and 3, 9 and 12 o'clock hour-markers. This valuable timepiece comes with a stainless steel case, with 18K pink gold bezel and two-tone bracelet with 18K pink gold links.
          <br>
          Model: GKR9239-4599
          Swiss made 9040 automatic movement
          24 jewels, rhodium plated movement
          Circular-grained bridges, Geneva waves, blue screws
          Stainless steel case with 18K pink gold bezel
          Stainless steel bracelet with 18K pink gold links
          Water resistant to 50 meters
          Case diameter 40mm
          Dial set with 15 natural diamonds
          Date at 3 o'clock, power reserve at 6 o'clock
          Anti-reflection sapphire crystal
          See through back
          <br>
          Royal Collection<br>
          Heritage of classics, future of glories. Through 155 years of experience and tradition, ErnestBorelhas always relied on its values to keep on innovating. Further to its 155th Anniversary Celebration, the romantic brand is launching an upgraded version of the Royal Collection.

          This collection houses a 2895 automatic movement with small second at 6 o'clock, three-dimensional Roman numerals as well as stainless steel bi-color case and bracelet. The see-through back â€“ archetype of the brand â€“ shows the beautiful decorated rhodium plated movement, with its blue screws and brand logo, emphasizing the special care for details.

          Perfect for either business and leisure, this two-tone timepiece is a true refinement, perpetuating heritage of classics
          <br>
          Model GBR6155W-4829
          Swiss made 2895 automatic movement
          27 jewels, rhodium plated movement
          Circular-grained oscillating weight, blue screws
          Small second at 6 o'clock, date indication at 3 o'clock
          Two-tone stainless steel case and bracelet
          Water resistant to 30 meters
          Case diameter 40.5 mm
          Anti-reflection sapphire crystal
          See-through back
          <br>
          Retro Collection<br>
          Aqua Marina is a transparent semi-precious stone with a beautiful sea-water color, recalling its name, especially blending in the sunlight. Inspired by the sparkle of Aqua Marina, Ernest Borel designers had launched a charming collection in the 1940's, paying tribute to the beauty and immensity of the ocean.

          According to legend, Aqua Marina is also the Love Stone. In its pursuit of passion and happiness, Ernest Borel has decided to give a new birth to the creative style of the Aqua Marina collection.As the Lover's trademark, the new Retro Collection perfectly represents Ernest Borel's heritage, with natural elegance and classical style emanating from this beautiful timepiece.

          The retro collection is available for both ladies and gents and displays hour and minute with genuine leather straps or stainless steel bracelet.
          <br>
          Model: LS906-9821GR
          Swiss made quartz movement
          Stainless steel case
          Water resistant to 50 meters
          Case diameter 31mm
          Anti-reflection sapphire crystal
          Hour and minute hands
          Genuine leather strap]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20120313_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2012</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20120308_1" date="2012-03-08">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[2012 BASELWORLD]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[The BASELWORLD 2012 World Watch and Jewellery Show is the best possible position in the run-up to its starts: the industry's key brands will be presenting their innovations in Basel from 8 to 15 March 2012. The booth details of Ernest Borel are as follow and we are glad to invite for your coming. See you there.  <br><br>

          Brand Name	 Ernest BOREL S.A.
          Hall		 HALL OF EMOTION (5.1)
          Booth No.		 E11]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20120308_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2012</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20111208_1" date="2011-12-08">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[In 2011, Ernest Borel marks the release of its majestic "Harmonic" Collection wristwatch]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Following Ernest Borel's Romantic Cruise stop at the fashionable metropolis of Shanghai on October 20, the voyage to bring eternal feelings of warmth and intimacy to every corner of the world continued on its way, reaching the charming southern port of Guangzhou on December 8, where it launch the all-new " Harmonic series" in the city's Tian-he business district. Like a mermaid rising from the Aegean Sea, the goddess of romance, Kelly Chen, joined ERNEST Borel Asia Pacific CEO, Su Da to unveil the captivating new timepiece.

          Established in 1856, Ernest Borel has created countless romantic dreams and fantasies for watch-buyers since first crossing the ocean to reach the Chinese mainland, which, 100 years ago was a distant and vast land. Now, Ernest Borel continues to bequeath ever-lasting romance and feelings of attachment from generation to generation, with precision timepieces honed using of over a century-and-a-half of watch-making experience. This latest "Harmonic" Collection  wristwatch reflects the spirit of the Ernest Borel brand, the makers of heirlooms of quality and distinction.

          The "Harmonic" Collection wristwatch launch event had the air of classical sea adventure on the vast and tranquil Aegean Sea. An enchanting piece was expertly played on a harp, a most perfect musical accompaniment for the Ernest Borel "Harmonic" Collection wristwatch to pass on romantic and harmonious sentiments. Yu Dan, the award-winning harpist added to the occasion with her melodic sound symbolising the ever-lasting romance of the Aegean sea, as if the fine sands slowly flowed through the reflection of an hourglass on Ernest Borel's time-honoured motif - the perfect metaphor for representing the continuation of another 155 years of Ernest Borel romance.

          Soon afterwards Kelly Chen joined harpist Yu Dan to perform a beautiful duet "Star Dreaming, Real Feeling", bringing the mood at the launch event to a crescendo. Ernest Borel Asia Pacific CEO, Su Da, used this emotional moment to present Kelly Chen with a "Harmonic" Collection wristwatch to express Ernest Borel's gratitude for her co-operation from the very start of the journey - it was a romantic a moment as any from her life on stage as actress. The gift is surely a perfect life-long partner for Kelly to enjoy for the rest of her wonderful days.

          With its classical feel and ability to tug the heart strings of those who hear it, the sound of the harp is the inspiration for the Ernest Borel "Harmonic" Collection wristwatch. The harp is a symbol, an emblem, which profoundly encapsulates the intimate feelings shared between lovers - there is no better aural interpretation of romance. The classical sounds emerging from the harp itself are represented in the eye-catching looks of the "Harmonic" Collection wristwatch - the casing of the watch is embedded with eight diamonds arranged in a graduating scale, emanating a vivid and lively feeling of movement. Each individual stone represents a harp string, with the hand of the watch sweeping over each string like the slender fingers of a harpist, realising a delicate, gorgeous scene of unending sentimental beauty. Both sides of the watch strap represent the arm of a man and a woman respectively as if locked in romantic embrace.
          Ernest Borel Asia Pacific CEO, Su Da, remarked, "Music is a channel for expressing feeling, and is also the best way to convey the most heartfelt of emotions. From all kinds of music played on a harp, we can hear the most graceful and moving melodies, and it gives a poetic sound of tender romance, it is a "Harmonic" Collection to catch the intimate harmony shared between lovers, and in a single moment captures eternal feelings of deep attachment and sentiment."
          He continued, "These feelings are the creative inspiration of the Ernest Borel "Harmonic" Collection, and they also represent a perfect match for the spirit of our brand."
          The "Harmonic" Collection brand is a partner for life, a perfect fusion of artistic craft and romantic sentiment. Ernest Borel strives to continue to creatively keep abreast of the latest trends and developments to remain a graceful and exquisite brand of romance which exudes superior quality, utilizing classical expertise and craftsmanship to bring emotional sentiment to every corner of the world.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20111208_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2011</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20111107_1" date="2011-11-07">
			<title>
				<![CDATA["Romance" sets sail on the 155th Anniversary Celebration of Swiss ERNEST BOREL]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[On October 20, 2011, in order to celebrate the 155th Anniversary of ERNEST BOREL, ERNEST BOREL "Romance" set sail romantically in the creative fashion landmark of Shanghai Redtown; ERNEST BOREL Angel of Elegance Miss Angie Chiu, Goddess of Romance Miss Kelly Chan, and Icon of Handsomeness Mr. Raymond Lam gathered here , and turned the steering wheel together with President of ERNEST BOREL, Mr. Raphael Boillat, General Manager of ERNEST BOREL, Ms. Nathalie Boillat, and ERNEST BOREL Regional Chief Executive Officer For Asia Pacific, Mr. Su Da, thus commencing an unforgettable romantic journey with the honorable guests .

          With the melodious sound of the horn, ERNEST BOREL "Romance" set sail, providing panoramic views of the beautiful landscapes of Switzerland. Dressing in a noble palace skirt, Miss Chiu danced with partner airily and nobly on the deck, which was recorded by the photographer similar with the romantic encounter on the logo.

          With ERNEST BOREL "Romance" sailing into metropolises, high-rise silhouettes echoed with vigorous music; Icon of Handsomeness Mr. Raymond Lam led dancers shuttling between bow and sceneries; interaction of images and accuracy of collaboration demonstrated the evolution of watch-making craft of ERNEST BOREL from traditional craft to innovative and modern one.

          Suddenly, "Romance" sailed into a small island, with lovely flower fairies ethereally dancing in the immersive paradise. Goddess of Romance Miss Kelly Chan holding flowers appeared among the fairies, at this moment, "The wind blew up her fairy sleeves; As if she were dancingï¼Œthe dance called the â€˜Rainbow Skirt and Feathered Coat'", reminding us of happy wonderland of fairy-tale scenes!

          Then, several distinguished guests came onto the platform and turned the steering wheel together, unveiling the grand launch of Swiss ERNEST BOREL "155th Anniversary Commemorative" Royal Collection, constituted by a glorious history of 155 years of brand development. The series used 2892 hollow automatic limited edition movement of Royal Collection, which is elaborately polished and delicately engraved with exquisite pattern and see-through back to represent the European royal nobleness, to reveal everything about a timepiece, and to demonstrate perfectly the wonderful and overwhelming techniques of craftsmen. The employment of engraving and see-through back is just perfect. The manufacturing process, which is time-consuming and effort-consuming in every step, is a long-lasting and accumulative even continual improvement approaching perfection; just as ERNEST BOREL continues to pursue sophisticated and exquisite watch-making philosophy in 155 years. It is the continuous accumulation and improvement that constitute today's brand new leaping forward.

          For almost two centuries, Swiss ERNEST BOREL, with its romantic and elegant brand value, is widely acclaimed throughout the world; and also because of its innovative spirit and vigorous character, has become a necessary master piece for modern romantic couples and a shining classic of a lifetime!]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20111107_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2011</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20110621_1" date="2011-06-21">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[The iphone App of Swiss Ernest Borel is launched around the globe.]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[With the iphone App of Swiss Ernest Borel, you can have a perfect experience of the brand&#39;s cultural elements of romance, elegance and optimism, anywhere and anytime. In addition, you can get the latest product information just a tap away.
          Browse App Store     Search for Ernest Borel    <a href="javascript:void(0);">Download the App Now</a>.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20110621_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2011</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20101215_1" date="2010-12-15">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Opening of New Ernest Borel Store in Geneva, Switzerland]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[The Swiss Ernest Borel, with a history of nearly 155 years, has recently opened its new store of Dragon du Ciel in Geneva, the second largest city in Switzerland, an international metropolis, as well as the world&#39;s &#34;capital of watches&#34;. When the Swiss Ernest Borel, famous for its &#34;romance&#34;, is combined with Geneva&#39;s profound timepiece culture, it will certainly offer customers with a special and pleasant experience of purchase.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20101215_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2011</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20101213_1" date="2010-12-13">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[The New COSC-Certified Braque Chronometer]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[The Swiss Ernest Borel continues to offer surprises in 2010. After the COSC-certified Romance Chronometer in October, it launched another masterpiece, the COSC-certified Braque Chronometer in December, which once again proved its superb technologies.
          As early as in the 1940s and the 1950s, Ernest Borel received the &#34;Bulletin demarche&#34; certificate for 4,172 of its watches, and became the second largest manufacturer of chronometers, which were very remarkable achievements. The COSC-Certified Braque Chronometer inherits the essence of the Braque Collection, with each timepiece subject to testing by COSC (ContrÃ´le Officiel Suisse des ChronomÃ¨tres), thus being the perfect combination of precision and art.
          Maximizing the essence of Braque&#39;s &#34;cubism&#34;, the Braque Chronometer features a unique design, with the dial including several patterns such as the trapezoid day window, the round date window, arrows and curved shading. Thus it not only is inclusive but also perfectly highlights the beauty of lines of various patterns. With the focus on the center, it endows comfort, smoothness and elegance. And the indexes of natural diamonds exude the tinge of high-level art.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20101213_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2010</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20100828_1" date="2010-08-28">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[BorelChrono Collection]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Ever since its foundation, the Swiss Ernest Borel has always demonstrated its essence of &#34;romance &#38; elegance&#34;. The BorelChrono Collection is the embodiment of strength and value, illustrating a magical beauty of mechanical elements. The 6.5mm 2021 ultra-thin chronograph movement is 1.4mm thinner than the conventional 7.9mm version. The large date indication and the small second hand transform the complicated mechanical structure into a visual beauty. Besides, the perfect combination of diamonds and time implicitly shows the prominent status.


          Swiss-made  2021 automatic chronograph movement
          Counter function for 1/5 second, 30 minutes and 12 hours
          Tachymeter
          Date indication
          Stainless steel case
          Bezel set with 60 natural diamonds
          Sapphire crystal watch mirror
          Alligator strap
          See-through back
          50-meter water resistance]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20100828_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag/>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20100801_1" date="2010-08-01">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Jules Borel Collection]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Named after Ernest Borel&#39;s founder, this collection commemorates Mr. Jules Borel&#39;s excellent contributions to the brand and his profound influence in the watchmaking industry over 150 years, so that we can carry on his concept of &#34;romance &#38; elegance". The Jules Borel Collection perfectly combines the unique indication of date retrograde with the clear indication of power reserve. Created with full efforts and launched as a global limited edition, it is a very meaningful timepiece in the development of Ernest Borel.

          18K pink gold watch
          Global limited edition of 288 pieces
          Swiss-made 9094 automatic movement
          Date retrograde indication
          Day indication by hand
          Power reserve indication
          Case and in 18K pink gold
          Alligator strap
          Sapphire crystal
          See-through back
          50-meter water resistance]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20100801_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2010</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20100623_1" date="2010-06-23">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Glorious Anniversary in Hong Kong Romance with Ernest Borel in Hong Kong Disneyland]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Ernest Borel, the Swiss brand of fashionable timepieces, is always famous for its romantic image. The brand celebrated its 150th anniversary in Hong Kong Disneyland Hotel on June 23, 2010. Highly popular in the Greater China Region, Ernest Borel has always manufactured its products as per the principles of &#34;durable, reliable, comfortable and beautiful&#34;, bringing quality and fashionable watches to customers through the years.

          In line with its booming and rapid business development in China, this year the brand has invited Kelly Chan to join its long-time endorsers of Raymond Lam and Angie Chiu to illustrate its elaborate and classical timepieces. At the dinner party that night, actor-turned-singer Raymond Lam as the brand&#39;s endorser performed his signature song and shared his joy in collecting Ernest Borel watches. And Kelly Chan, the brand&#39;s new &#34;goddess of romance&#34;, performed the finale for VIPs at the banquet. They both embodied the essence of the brand&#39;s romantic culture and conveyed the brand&#39;s value of &#34;romance &#38; elegance&#34;. The banquet was hosted by Carol Cheung, whose sophistication and humor pleased every one present. And the quiz session even pushed the banquet to the climax thanks to her excellent performance.

          With a history of more than 150 years, Ernest Borel adheres to the profound cultural tradition and established its outstanding characteristics, enjoying unique prominence in the watchmaking industry in Switzerland and even around the world. In recent years, Ernest Borel watches have also made excellent achievements in the Greater China Region, with its flagship stores opened in Shanghai, Qingdao and Liuzhou in 2009, making its products widely popular among customers on the Chinese Mainland. On the other hand, in line with its business development, Ernest Borel was formally relocated to the new factory premises in Le Noirmont, a famous location of timepiece manufacture in Switzerland on February 28, 2009, so as to further develop new products of high quality.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20100623_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2010</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20100325_1" date="2010-03-25">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Romantic Moments with Charm: Report on New Product of Ernest Borel at BASELWORLD 2010]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[The 38th BASELWORLD was held in Basel, Switzerland during March 18-25, 2010. As the annual event for top watches around the world, the BASELWORLD is the thermometer for the global watchmaking industry. Ernest Borel, the top Swiss brand of couple's watches, together with other prominent timepiece brands around the world, displayed the latest models in 2010 and their fine watchmaking techniques. They jointly illustrated the eye-catching charm of the Swiss precise timepieces as well as their own ideas of romance.

          Background of the Swiss Ernest Borel
          In 1856, Ernest Borel was founded by Jules Borel in Neuchatel, Switzerland, the &#34;Kingdom of Watches&#34;.
          In 1859, Jules Borel and his brother-in-law Paul Courvoisier cofounded the Borel and Courvoisier Company.
          In 1860, Borel and Courvoisier Company exported the first batch of timepieces to Uruguay, marking its presence in South America.
          In 1866, the Company beat its competitors to obtain the first prize in the competition organized by the Neuchatel Observatory, the top judge of timepiece products in Switzerland at that time.
          In 1867, the products of Borel and Courvoisier started to be available in Spain, with the sales network expanding rapidly.
          In 1876, the timepiece products by Borel and Courvoisier were granted the Premium Award in Philadelphia, the USA.
          In 1878, the Company obtained the only Precious Premium Award for the Swiss timepiece industry in Paris, France.
          In 1903, sales personnel of Ernest Borel came to China after a six-month journey and sold 388 watches.
          In 1937, Ernest Borel was granted the Grand Prix Honor Award in Greece.
          From 1945 to 1958, the Swiss Neuchatel Observatory issued the &#34;Bulletin demarche&#34; certificate to 4,172 pieces of Ernest Borel watches.
          In 1958, the same observatory even presented the first prize to two of Ernest Borel&#39;s precision timepieces.
          In the 1960s, Ernest Borel focused on developing the markets in the USA, Hong Kong and the entire Southeast Asia.
          In the 1980s, Ernest Borel rapidly integrated itself into China&#39;s profound traditional culture and the fashionable taste, creating a brand-new consumption concept for the Chinese consumers.
          In the 21st century, Ernest Borel has designed more trend-setting products, which are greatly loved and esteemed by consumers.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20100325_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2010</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20100303_1" date="2010-03-03">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Kelly Chen's New Advertisements]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Ernest Borel, a world renowned Swiss watch brand, has had a sparkling and &#34;romantic&#34; cooperation with Kelly Chan, an Asian top diva with legendary romance, and Chung-Man Hai, an art director and costume designer with international fame. Ernest Borel and the two famous figures specially filmed a series of advertisements in Hong Kong to promote Kelly's new image as Ernest Borel&#39;s &#34;goddess of romance&#34;.

          A unique atmosphere of romance is demonstrated in the advertisements thanks to Chung-Man Hai&#39;s meticulous efforts, Ernest Borel&#39;s eternal charm and Kelly Chan&#39;s elegance. Kelly, wearing a timepiece of Ernest Borel&#39;s &#34;Romance Series III&#34;, now slowly walks down the romantic ladder, exuding her romance and charm more than ever. Each print advertisement just seems to be so classical and so sensational.

          We have Ernest Borel, the top Swiss brand of couple's watches with a history of more than 150 years and the design concept of &#34;romance". We then have Kelly Chan, who has always been successful since her career debut, who has been enjoying a romantic love for 16 years and who is still so elegant. Last but not lest, we have Chung-Man Hai, a prominent figure in the film-making and fashion industries, who has once obtained the best historical design award by the US Costume Designers Guild Awards on top of numerous Hong Kong Film Awards and Golden Horse Awards. Ernest Borel&#39;s &#34;match-making&#34; efforts have combined the three in a &#34;romantic&#34; cooperation for a beautiful and wonderful achievement in the watchmaking industry!]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20100303_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2010</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20100303_2" date="2010-03-03">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Kelly Chan Becomes "Goddess of Romance" of Ernest Borel]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[At the grand release at JW Marriott Hotel, Tomorrow Square, Shanghai on March 3, 2010, the Swiss timepiece brand of Ernest Borel announced Kelly Chan, the Asian diva who has unique elegance and legendary love, to be its new &#34;goddess of romance&#34;. At the scene of the event, Kelly shared her &#34;romantic moments&#34; with Ernest Borel with a number of VIPs, including Mr. Raphael Boillat, the brand&#39;s President, Ms. Nahalie Boillat, the brand&#39;s General Manager, Mr. Su Da, the brand&#39;s CEO of the Asia-Pacific region, as well as other guests and journalists.

          Ernest Borel identifies with Kelly&#39;s romantic moments
          The greatest thing in common between Ernest Borel and Kelly Chan lies in their unswerving pursuit of &#34;romance&#34;. Ernest Borel is a top Swiss brand of classical couple's watches with a history of more than 150 years and the design concept of &#34;romance&#34; based on ambitious innovation. Its unique brand culture, together with its meticulous craft, endows the brand with exquisite style and excellent quality. For those who keep pursuing perfectness and adore fashion and romance, Ernest Borel provides a kind of irreplaceable works of art, as witness of romantic love and avocation of beauty.
          Kelly, on the other hand, has always tried to strike a balance between her career and her love since her debut in the show business. And the 16-year long courtship finally culminated in happy marriage not long ago. That not only requires an enthusiastic heart but also shows Kelly&#39;s persistence in &#34;romance&#34;. She believed that her true love had turned up when her boyfriend personally made a unique dish for her. And she will never forget the 214 roses she received on the romantic Valentine&#39;s Day. When she and her boyfriend were finally about to tie the knot, she couldn&#39;t help sharing the good news with her fans at the concert. And when her bridegroom Alex sang out the romantic song of &#34;When I Fall in Love&#34; at the wedding, Kelly was just moved to tears. Kelly was, is and will always be blessed on the path of true love. The birth of her little baby boy has added further joy to this happy and sweet family. And all those beautiful moments witnessed Kelly and her husband&#39;s romantic and legendary love throughout the years.

          Kelly touched by the romantic scene
          The witness of time is just like a ladder full of romantic memories. At the scene of the product release, Kelly Chan as the &#34;goddess of romance&#34; walked down the romantic ladder in an elegant manner. At this point, the big screen behind her was repeatedly playing the photos and videos witnessing the romantic love. And each of her steps seemed to be the illustration of true romance.
          And then Mr. Raphael Boillat, President of Ernest Borel, came to Kelly&#39;s side with the new &#34;Romance Series III&#34;. He praised Kelly&#39;s elegance and legendary romance and happily announced the Asian diva to be the brand&#39;s endorser. Finally he presented the watch to Kelly as a symbol of her identity as the brand&#39;s &#34;goddess of romance&#34;.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20100303_2">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2010</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20091214_1" date="2009-12-14">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Romance in Heart    Love Eternally]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Swiss Ernest Borel Watch Witnesses the Moment of Romance

          The Aegean Sea, also be known as the &#34;Love Sea&#34;, is perhaps an ocean in Greece especially formed for love. Somebody has used 4S to holiday spent there: GSun, Sea, Sand, Sex.

          The national flag of Greece comprises of two colours blue and white. White represents liberty while blue represents romantic love. The flag waves against the wind freely as if it were flying in the air, bringing about the obsession and yearning for free love. Islands spanning across Aegean Sea in Greece also demonstrate a perfect match of blue and white. The vast clear blue sky and sea meet as if there are endless seas and skies bending over one another. Low-rise houses in pure white colour spread over all the islands along the Aegean Sea. Under this breathtaking scene where sea and sky meet, together with the decoration of one and after another white-washed house, it looks as if angels dropping gift of &#34;love&#34; in this place.

          Using tangible objects to represent love, watch always embodies meaning of eternity, which symbolizes that time goes swiftly but love lasts forever. Founded in 1856, Ernest Borel Watch has a heritage of expressing romance and love. It best represents your everlasting love to your beloved. Designers at Ernest Borel are inspired by the &#34;Aegean Sea&#34;, thus created this year&#39;s Valentine&#39;s collection of the brand - &#34;Aegean Sea&#34; Collection couple watch set. The &#34;heart-shaped motif&#34; is embedded in the watch design. On the shell-shaped flashy color dial, classic motif outlines heart-shaped graphic with state-of-the-art craftsmanship. It simulates the changing sea color of the &#34;Aegean Sea&#34;, sometimes green as jade and sometimes blue as sky. Radiating strips in the center of the watch dial accentuate the visual effect, the flashy color diffuse like water color. Under the sunlight, colorful rays flashes, which enchants one in the romance at the Aegean Sea.

          Adding glamour to the watch, not only does the designer set 80 (Gentlemen) and 54 (Ladies) natural diamonds on the case, but also 10 (Gentlemen) and 9 (Ladies) rubies on the dial. These details make the watch all the more extravagant, the long-lasting diamonds echoes with the continuity of time that witnesses the lasting love and passion, while rubies symbolizes honesty and passion that brings about auspiciousness. The combination perfectly expresses the romance and compassion of the &#34;Aegean Sea&#34;. The simplicity and well-defined shape epitomize the romantic love between lovers. Its automatic mechanical movement is comfortable that can be used for a long time, symbolizing precious love that lingers forever.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20091214_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2009</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20090826_1" date="2009-08-26">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[The Grand Inauguration of Ernest Borel Shanghai Flagship Store]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[On August, 26th, Ernest Borel Shanghai Flagship Store had its grand inauguration at 595, Huaihai Mid Road. Raphael Boillat, president of Ernest Borel and Su Da, its CEO in the Asia-Pacific area attended the inauguration ceremony along with the brand spokesperson Angie Chiu, a well-known actress from Hong Kong. They shared the "Romantic Time" with Ernest Borel with the present guests.

          Everyone is seeking for the very person with whom they can share romantic time of whole life. To provoke people's desire for this kind of romance deep down in their heart, Ernest Borel, with her constant romantic style, set Shanghai flagship store at Huaihai Mid Road, the former Avenue Joffre and also the origin of fashion in Shanghai. There she brings forever romantic time, and also dreams and desire for wonderful and romantic life for people living in this city.

          To celebrate the grand inauguration, Raphael Boillat brought Romance Series and invited the spokesperson Angie Chiu and her husband Melvin Wong, to present this series. The two sides of Romance series, made of seashells just like ladies' colorful skirts, remind us of dancing lovers. The radiant stripes on their surfaces symbolizes the radiation of bless and happiness. All is evident of the classical and romantic image of Ernest Borel. Meanwhile, the presentation of  Angie Chiu and Melvin Wong made this series all the more impressive. The couple are always holding hands in whatever events they attend, which is supposed to be the best interpretation of the romantic brand, Ernest Borel.

          Romantic time with Ernest Borel has long been seared on the mind of Chinese people. A long history has made her more elegant and outstanding. Love has made her forever charming. Superior quality and the underlying affluent culture has made her worth possessing for a lifetime.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20090826_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2009</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20090810_1" date="2009-08-10">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[True Love Collection]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Ernest Borel is the brand symbols of love, romance and elegant, we are going to launch a series of True Love Collection in September 2009, which is series of well deserved classic and modern love, the simplicity of design, highlighting &#34;1&#34; and &#34;8&#34; on the dial with natural diamonds, &#34;1&#34; represents a lifetime, while &#34;8&#34; represents a long-lasting love story.

          Specifications:
          Swiss made quartz movement
          Stainless steel case and bracelet
          Bezel and dial set with natural diamonds
          Sapphire crystal
          3 ATM water resistant]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20090810_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2009</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20090711_1" date="2009-07-11">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[The Grand Inauguration of Ernest Borel Qingdao Flagship Store]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[On July 11th, Ernest Borel Qingdao Flagship Store had its grand inauguration, kicking off the opening of its name brand stores. The brand spokesperson, Angie Chiu, a well-known actress from Hong Kong, presented the latest Romance Series on this occasion.

          Zhang Xingen, vice-president of Xinyu Group and Xiao Wenzhang, the general manager and board chairman of Qingdao Hengdeli Company, along with Angie Chiu and Su Da,the CEO of Ernest Borel in the Asia-Pacific area, presided over the ribbon-cutting and toast ceremony to celebrate the inauguration of Qingdao Flagship Store. Angie presented the latest Romance series together with a foreign model, showing the romantic charm of this wristwatch series and making the ceremony more fantastic. There were also a lively lion dance exciting the audience who then gave out warm applaud.

          Ernest Borel is committed to the improvement of its brand images and increase of brand value. For this purpose it sets flagship stores one after another these years. Qingdao flagship store is the 4th one in China and Shanghai flagship store will be open next month. It is estimated that by the year of 2010, there will be over 10 flagship stores in China. Therefore, Ernest Borel holds a very optimistic view of China's economic development and believes that in the coming 5 years China will become one of the world's largest luxury markets.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20090711_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2009</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20090510_1" date="2009-05-10">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Ernest Borel Marine Series Launches]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Relaxation, aggression, heroism and glamour not only are characteristics representing Columbus, but also feature the newest watch series of Ernest Borel Marine Series. Ernest Borel, the renowned Swiss timekeeper with over 150 year-old history, announced the first launch of their newest Marine Series to South China on 10 May, 2009 (Sunday) at Grandview Mall located at Tianhe Road of Guangzhou. &#34;Exploring the Sailing Tour&#34; was the innovative theme of this grand event. The lifestyle fashion brand featuring its design theme &#34;Sailing&#34;, Nautica has also joined this Sailing Tour to sponsor the catwalk wardrobes.

          The venue design of this Sailing Tour was unique and innovative. A huge white sail boat was built as the stage for giving a lively experience of sailing to audiences and presenting the innovating sprit of Marine Series. Mr. Raymond Lam, the brand ambassador, Mr. Raphael Boillat, the CEO of Ernest Borel (Swiss), Ms. Nathalie Boillat, the General Manager of Ernest Borel and Mr. David Su, CEO of Ernest Borel (Asia Pacific) attended the event in which they joined hand-in-hand to host the launching ceremony of Marine Series.

          Soon after the launching ceremony, Mr. Raymond Lam performed a catwalk show with four foreign professional models to present the unique glamour of Marine Series. In order to bring better understanding of the new series to the public, Mr. Raymond Lam explained the unique features of the watches with personal demonstration and shared how watches accompanied his feeling to sailing which put a perfect ending to the event.

          In the 558th anniversary of Columbus&#39;s navigate exploration, Ernest Borel has designed a series of Marine Series, which are high-level automatic GMT watches, promoting the spirit of Columbus never says die and his continuous innovation courage. The new series consists of models for both male and female, continuing the romance of love and presenting the charm of ladies. The model for male has GMT automatic movement, a see-through back and screw crown and being elaborate polished and rhodium plated. The model for female has Swiss made quartz movement. Both models have centre hands for 24-hours, hours, minutes and seconds, date indication, stainless steel case and 100m Water resistant

          Swiss&#39;s Ernest Borel again expresses its everlasting lavish style, state-of-the-art craftsmanship and touching style to sustain the promotion of an artistic lifestyle.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20090510_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2009</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20090313_1" date="2009-03-13">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Baselworld 2009]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[We are delighted to invite you to this year&#39;s Baselworld, which to be held from March 26, 09 to April 2, 09.

          In line with the development of our international sales and the increase of the number of visitors, we are happy to inform you that we shall unveil this year not only a new international Ernest Borel watch collection, but also a brand new stand with a surface bigger than that of last years.

          Company Name :  GErnest BOREL S.A.
          Hall :  GHALL OF EMOTION (5.1)
          Stand :  GE11]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20090313_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2009</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
		<news id="20090310_1" date="2009-03-10">
			<title>
				<![CDATA[Ernest Borel establishes new factory in Switzerland]]>
			</title>
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[In order to cater to the expansion and further development of Ernest Borel, the factory is reallocated from La Chaux-de-fonds to Le Noirmont on February 28, 2009, the maximum output of the new factory could be reached 330,000 pieces of watches annually.
          The new factory mainly includes the administration building and production building two parts, the total area amounts up to 2,000 square meters. Architect uses the brand theme of &#39;Romance In Heart&#39; to design the administration building, which has the European classical concept, the building takes the white and the brown as the contrast, the geometry acme roof design and balcony, carrying the romance, elegance of the brand. The administration building has 3 floors, mainly for holding executive meeting and offices for executives, product research and development technicians, the 3rd floor is designed as showroom, demonstrating the history and latest watches of Ernest Borel.

          The new factory&#39;s production building is a modernized new construction, with 2 floors, production line is especially designed for sophisticated products in the future. Besides original facilities and equipments from old factory, we also introduce the massive advanced production equipment and the user-friendly instrumentation. Settings of the production line conform to the Swiss Clock and watch Association and the international environmental protection standard.

          The company wishes to build on the past experience and achievements and to utilize the very latest in watch making technology in achieving harmony with the surrounding natural environment.

          New Ernest Borel factory address: Case postale 234, rue des Perrieres 8, CH-2340 Le Noirmont, Switzerland]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20090310_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
			<tags>
				<tag>2009</tag>
			</tags>
		</news>
	</active>
	<inactive>
		<news id="20110215_1" date="2011-02-15" title="2011 BASELWORLD">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[The BASELWORLD 2011 World Watch and Jewellery Show is the best possible position in the run-up to its starts: the industry’s key brands will be presenting their innovations in Basel from 24 to 31 March 2011. The booth details of Ernest Borel are as follow and we are glad to invite for your coming. See you there.

          Brand Name	：Ernest BOREL S.A.
          Hall		：HALL OF EMOTION (5.1)
          Booth No.		：E11]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20110215_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20111107_1" date="2011-11-07" title="">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20111107_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="" date="2009-12-15" title="">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20090826_1" date="2009-08-26" title="">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20090826_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20090711_1" date="2009-07-11" title="">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20090711_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20081130_1" date="2008-11-30" title="Ernest Borel Rocky Series II Launches">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Exalted status, supreme authority, outstanding charisma, graceful presence, prestigious lifestyle... not only are characteristics representing success, but also feature the newest watch series of Ernest Borel Rocky Series II. Ernest Borel, the renowned Swiss timekeeper with over 150 year-old history, announced the first launch of their newest Rocky Series II to South China on 30 Nov, 2008 (Sunday) at Grandbuy Department Store located at Xihu Road of Guangzhou.

          &#34;Ernest Borel Rocky Series II Launches&#34; was commenced with the passionate Latin dance which swept away the cool weather from Guangzhou. Mr. Raymond Lam, the brand ambassador, and Mr. David Su, CEO of Ernest Borel (Asia Pacific), attended the event in which they joined hand-in-hand with other management from the department store to host the launching ceremony of Rocky Series II. In order to bring better understanding of the new series to the public, Mr. Raymond Lam explained the unique features of the watches with personal demonstration and shared how watches accompanied his way to success. Being an icon of successful singer in South China, Mr. Raymond Lam performed two songs with his beautiful voices which once again captured the audience hearts and put a perfect ending to the event.

          Ernest Borel Rocky Series II watches are specially designed for successful people. Not only does the new series accentuate successful style, but it also combines this abstract element with the everlasting flow of time to turn it a tangible reality. Along with the breathtaking design, the new series is also equipped with practical features like anti-reflective sapphire crystal, big date with direct change from 31 to 01, day retrograde, small second, very long battery life of 48 months, and strap choices of stainless steel or genuine leather. All these match the need of modern successful people and become the indispensable partner of their busy life.

          Swiss&#39;s Ernest Borel again expresses its everlasting lavish style, state-of-the-art craftsmanship and touching style to sustain the promotion of an artistic lifestyle.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20081130_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20081124_1" date="2008-11-24" title="">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20081124_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20080901_1" date="2008-09-01" title="">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20080901_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20080314_1" date="2008-03-14" title="Baselworld 2008">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[We are delighted to invite you to this year&#39;s Baselworld, which to be held from April 3rd to 10th, 2008.

          In line with the development of our international sales and the increase of the number of visitors, we are happy to inform you that we shall unveil this year not only a new international Ernest Borel watch collection, but also a brand new stand with a surface bigger than that of last years.

          Company Name	: GErnest BOREL S.A.
          Hall	 : GHALL OF EMOTION (5.1)
          Stand	 : GE11]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20080314_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20080229_1" date="2008-02-29" title="Latest TechnoSports Collection Expresses New Sports Watch Trend">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Ernest Borel launched its latest 2008 sports watch collection -TechnoSports Collection, which presents the dynamic side of the brand apart from its elegance in a romantic ambience. This collection introduces a refreshed and healthy personality that epitomize the new trend of &#34;Sporty Lifestyle&#34;.

          Founded in 1856, Swiss watchmaker Ernest Borel with its brand value of cherishing the romantic moment, state-of-the-art watch-making craftmanship, together with the contemporary hi-tech technology, which add the dynamic design concept into this century-old brand famous for its romantic legend, and thus perfectly combine stylish and sporty design in one timepiece. In 2008, the brand proudly presents its TechnoSports Chronograph Collection. Apart from demonstrating the romantic lifestyle, it is suitable for sports need.

          TechnoSports Collection uses professional Swiss quartz chronograph movement, equipping with 30 seconds, 5 seconds and 60 seconds timer function. The stainless steel case is 42mm in diameter that is elaborately-polished, together with PVD bezel and embossed push button. The watch is mainly in cool black, with the dial and indicators offering a choice of yellow, orange and white that symbolize vigor, dynamic and elegance respectively, showing a sense of liveliness and among the classics.

          The back of the watch case has a unique design of the colourful motif of 5 continents, which symbolizes a vision of &#34;One world, One dream&#34; under the same sky for the mankind. It highlights the yearning for a world of equality, harmony, fair competition and sustainable co-existence. The design not only emphasizes its refined structure, but also its sapphire crystal watch case, screw crown and 50m water-resistance function. This collection comes the mature steel bracelet and refreshed TPU strap available for choice.

          Ernest Borel&#39;s TechnoSports Collection accentuate a new generation of romantic yet sporty watch that brings about high level of functionality.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20080229_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20080126_1" date="2008-01-26" title="Store Grandly Opened in Shijiazhuang">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[The Aegean Sea Collection Launched a New Romantic Legend

          Ernest Borel, the renowned Swiss timekeeper with over 150 year-old history, grandly opened new stores in Beiguo Advanced Structure Square and Beiguo Xinbai Shopping Center in Shijiazhuang and &#34;The Shijiazhuang Shop Grand Opening and Aegean Sea Collection Launching Ceremony&#34; were held on 26 Jan, 2008 (Saturday) respectively. The ceremony was to celebrate grand opening of the two new stores as well as launching the brand&#39;s latest couple watch set collection- &#34;Aegean Sea Collection&#34;.

          On the event day, Ms. Angie Chiu, the brand ambassador together with Mr. David Su, CEO of Ernest Borel (Asia Pacific) joined hand-in-hand with other management from the shopping centers to host the ribbon-cutting and toasting ceremony to celebrate the opening of the Shijiazhuang stores. The grand opening ceremony was followed by a striking launching ceremony for the brand&#39;s latest couple watch collection&#34;Aegean Sea Collection&#34;. To create a romantic ambience, white feather fell gradually from the top of the lavish circular arch once Ms. Angie Chiu and Mr. David Su untied the ribbon to kick off the launch. This celebratory scene makes it feels like a enchanting fairy-tale wedding that definitely mesmerized many for a long time. Adding a touch of glamour and romance to the ceremony, a pair of models dressed in couple style went up stage to present the romantic &#34;Aegean Sea Collection&#34; while white feathers were falling down.

          The Aegean Sea, also known as the &#34;Love Sea&#34;, always represents the dream land of romance to couples. &#34;Aegean Sea Collection&#34;, the latest couple watch set collection launched by Swiss&#39;s Ernest Borel, its design was based on the breathtaking scenery of Aegean Sea. Not only does the watch accentuate the unique romantic style from Greece�Abut it also combines this passion with the everlasting flow of time to turn eternal love a tangible reality. The watch case is set with 80 (Gentlemen) and 54 (Ladies) natural diamonds, whereas the dial is decorated with 10 (Gentlemen) and 9 (Ladies) rubies to make it even more refined, in order to express the everlasting love and commitment between lovers.

          Swiss&#39;s Ernest Borel again expresses its everlasting lavish style, state-of-the-art craftsmanship and touching style to sustain the promotion of an artistic lifestyle.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20080126_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20080121_1" date="2008-01-21" title="Ernest Borel Valentine&#39;s Special - Aegean Sea Collection">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Ernest Borel proudly presents this Valentine&#39;s special - &#34;Aegean Sea&#34; couple watch set collection, which helps you to express your sincere love to your beloved with the association of the most romantic city on hand.

          Ernest Borel&#39;s &#34;Aegean Sea&#34; collection has embedded the &#34;heart-shaped&#34; motif in the design. On the shell-shaped flashy color dial, classic motif outlines heart-shaped graphic with state-of-the-art craftsmanship. It simulates the changing sea color of the &#34;Aegean Sea&#34;, sometimes green as jade and sometimes blue as sky. Radiating strips in the center of the watch dial accentuate the visual effect, the flashy color diffuse like water color. Under the sunlight, colorful rays flashes, which enchants one in the romance at the Aegean Sea.

          Adding glamour to the watch, not only does the designer set 80 (Gentlemen) and 54 (Ladies) natural diamonds on the case, but also 10 (Gentlemen) and 9 (Ladies) rubies on the dial. These details make the watch all the more extravagant, the long-lasting diamonds echoes with the continuity of time that witnesses the lasting love and passion, while rubies symbolizes honesty and passion that brings about auspiciousness. The combination perfectly expresses the romance and compassion of the &#34;Aegean Sea&#34;. The simplicity and well-defined shape epitomize the precious love that lingers between lovers. Its automatic mechanical movement is comfortable and light in size which is turning away from the heavy competitive sense common in the market.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20080121_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20071109_1" date="2007-11-09" title="Ernest Borel flagship store grandly opens in Guangzhou">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Renowned timekeeper from Switzerland Ernest Borel held the &#39;Opening Ceremony of the Flagship store in Grandview Plaza&#39; on 9 November and invited the winners of Miss Chinese Cosmos Pageant 2007 as the guests of the ceremony. Also presented was the celebrity endorser of Ernest Borel Men&#39;s Watches, Mr. Zhong Zhen Tao. The opening of the flagship store of the Ernest Borel in Grandview Plaza signifies the brand&#39;s confidence and goodwill towards the market of Southern China.

          Ernest Borel is a well-established brand with a history of over 150 years. At the opening ceremony, the company adopts local Chinese tradition and kicked off the show with Guangzhou Lion Dance. The glamorous lion danced with the vigorous music and led in Mr. Raphael Boillat, the Director of Ernest Borel and Mr. Su Da, the CEO of Ernest Borel in Asia-Pacific Region. The two gentlemen dotted the eyes of the lion (which symbolizes auspiciousness), and the lions went to plucked the greens and uncover the celebrating scroll, adding fortunes to the newly started business of the flagship store in Grandview Plaza.

          To demonstrate the unique romantic artistry of Ernest Borel watches, Mr. Zhong Zhen Tao walked on the runway together with the models, showcasing the elegance, extravagance and classiness of the timepieces. A presentation ceremony was followed immediately after the show, in which the winners of Miss Chinese Cosmos Pageant 2007 were awarded the Venus Collection from Ernest Borel. The watches matched perfectly with the ladies, highlighting the beauty and wisdom of the Miss Chinese.

          Ernest Borel proudly presents the &#39;Artist Collection 2007&#39; automatic skeleton watches. All watches in this collection have their parts pierce carved without hampering its movement and function. Craftsman then polished and carved delicate patterns on the skeletons. All movements are clearly shown on the transparent dial and bottom, interpreting the meaning of time and movement and recalling a treasure for time. It serves not only as a visually alluring timepiece, but also an interaction of emotions and souls. The 20mm golden-plated steel timepiece matches well with the gold cores and deserves to be called as a genuine art piece.

          Ernest Borel is a Swiss timepiece brand committed to develop and promote a romantic lifestyle. It is hoped that the commencement of business in Guangzhou will help introduce the concept of &#39;Everlasting Romance&#39; to the region. The director of Ernest Borel Mr. Raphael Boillat also aspires that with the opening of the flagship store in Grandview Plaza, Guangzhou consumers will experience a brand new romantic and contemporary lifestyle.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20071109_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20071103_1" date="2007-11-03" title="Miss Chinese Cosmos Pageant Contest 2007">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Ernest Borel has sponsored Miss Chinese Cosmos Pageant Contest since 2003 and is appointed as the official timekeeper ever since. Hosted by Phoenix Satellite Television Inc., Miss Chinese Cosmos Pageant Contest is an annual focus for all Chinese women over the world, narrowing the gap among all Chinese globally, and to set new standards for genuine beauty.

          The grande final and awarding ceremony for &#39;Miss Chinese Cosmos Pageant Contest 2007&#39; was held tonight (3 November) at the Asian World-Expo in Hong Kong. The 12 finalists competed for several prizes through sections like singing, dancing and question-and-answer. At the end of the night, Miss Zeng Guang of number 20 won the top prize, while Wang Qian Qian (United States) and Jiang Nan (Beijing) became the first and second runner up respectively. The judges chose He Jing of number 4 as Miss Photogenic, Jiang Nan of number 11 as Miss Cultural and Wang Qian Qian of number 8 as Miss Caring. Furthermore, the World Federation of Chinese Entrepreneurs Organization WFCEO has proposed the prize of Miss Friendly Ambassador WFCEO and nominated by representatives of WFCEO from Americas, Europe, Asia, Tai Wan and Australia. The winner this year is Miss Yang Liu Qing of number 23.

          Mr. Dou Wen Tao, Hu Yi Hu, Miss Shen Xing and Wei Chi Lin Jia were the Masters of Ceremony in this show. The winner of Miss Chinese Cosmos Pageant Contest 2006 Miss Huang Cheng Zi shared her feelings as she was about to hand over her assignment, and presented the first prize together with the President of the Board of Directors and Chief Executive Officer of Phoenix TV Mr. Liu Chang Le, JP.

          The adjudicators include celebrities from China, Hong Kong and Taiwan: famous actress of Hong Kong, Miss Zhu Yin; leading Chinese performer of Huangmei Musical, Miss Ma Lan; renowned directors from China and Hong Kong, Mr. Feng Xiao Gang and Guan Jin Peng; Cultural scholar, Mr. Zhang Xin Gang; the founder and Officer of Managing Committee of Angel Smile Foundation, famed Chinese actor Li Ya Peng; and also the CEO of Ernest Borel, Asia-Pacific Region, Mr. Su Da.

          Recognized singers and bands were invited to perform at the show. Both a singer and actor, Mr. Ren Xian Qi from Taiwan played a part in the musical and sang the theme song of the contest this year &#39;If you were not there&#39; for the audience, while Finnish band &#39;Club For Five&#39; performed melodious English songs and sang a Chinese song &#39;Serpentine Moon&#39; together with the contestants.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20071103_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20071012_1" date="2007-10-12" title="Ernest Borel Venus Collection Launches in ChengDu">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[The prestigious brand, Ernest Borel has its newest Venus Collection launches in CheungDu, China on 11 Oct 2007. Ms. Angie Chiu, the brand ambassador, was there to kick off the grand ceremony together with Mr. David Su, CEO of Ernest Borel (Asian Pacific). As Mr. Su commented, &#34;Ernest Borel is a century brand with its accuracy and perfection famous amongst the public. The accurate operation of Ernest Borel gear will further maintain its highest level of watch manufacturing technology and keep the brand shining in the days coming.&#34;

          The event have been added a touch of glamour by scheduling models to present the brand lovely and trendy watches collection to the guest and audience. Most importantly, the-art-of-masks performance did further add a sense of excitement to the audience. It was undoubtedly an event abounds with romance, trend and excitement.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20071012_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20070922_1" date="2007-09-22" title="Ernest Borel Charitable Event in He Fei">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Ernest Borel, the glamorous brand of Switzerland watches, has just launched its new collection - Venus Collection and at the same time donated an amount to a local charitable organization, Hefei Children&#39;s Welfare Institute, Anhui, for supporting its welfare affairs. It was a remarkable event merging charity and watch launch out of pure benevolence.

          Government officials in He Fei also came and supported the event on 22 Sept 07. A signing ceremony has been conducted between representative of He Fei government official and Mr. David Su, CEO (Asia Pacific) of Ernest Borel, as an appeal to everyone in supporting local social welfare activities.

          As the brand ambassador, Ms. Angie Chiu also came a long way to show her blessings and caring to those who are in need. The flying balloons to the sky did have a symbolic meaning in which the brand sincerely wishes to bring all the good will and luck to people in He Fei.

          Venus Collection presents the feminine and romance of Ernest Borel, clearly reveals the contemporary female&#39;s unique elegancy. In order to continue the concept of &#34;Romance in Heart&#34;, Ernest Borel launches a renewed duplicate stereotype Venus Collection, which is limited in edition (700 pieces worldwide), reappearing the old days European Romance in current modern generation.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20070922_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20070818_1" date="2007-08-18" title="Ernest Borel Flagship Store Grand Opening in Beijing">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[On 18 Aug 2007, Ernest Borel, the famous brand of Switzerland elegant watches, has held a glamorous and trendy catwalk show and performance at Xidan Department in Beijing, for celebrating the flagship store grand opening ceremony in the region. Ms. Angie Chiu, brand ambassadress was also kick-off the regional launching ceremony for latest VENUS COLLECTION.

          According to Mr. Su Da, CEO of Ernest Borel Asia Pacific, expressed Ernest Borel is dedicated to provide elegant watches to people who pursue elegant, fashionable and romantic style of living, it&#39;s expecting that the Flagship Icon opening at Xidan Department Store will exhibit the unique romance and fashion of Ernest Boreal to the consumers in Beijing.

          The performance was lively and elegant, models started to wear graceful and ancient Greek-style dresses and exquisite body paint brought Greek romance and artistic beauty to the audience.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20070818_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20070719_1" date="2007-07-19" title="VENUS NIGHT at Bund 3 Shanghai">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Is there a type of ruler able to measure seventy-year&#39;s time? May be not.

          But there is a type of chronometer which can duplicate the romance of seventy years ago. Its length only just full circle your wrist. Its name is Ernest Borel Venus Collection wrist watch.

          On July 19th, at night, Shanghai Bund 3 as a fashion landmark which has carried uncountable adorable nights, finally embraced its most incredible Night of Venus.

          Tonight, empty your thoughts, sit still, let&#39;s listen to the most romantic story told by the time.

          Station-temporal retroversion, Athens Dreams

          A minute ago, we were at 21st Century&#39;s Shanghai; a minutes later, when we stepped into Bund 3, it seemed the time flew back for thousands years and the space displaced to the Mediterranean sea. Surrounded by mottled stele, immaculate lilies, the models dressed as Venus with beautiful chaplets, holly voile and exquisite faces, under the soft lights, we thought we went to Athens City in our dreams.

          Went through layers of white veil as if we went through one thousands years time tunnel, finally we arrived the hall. On the stele, the paintings of Venus were dancing under the changing lights. On the TV wall, the pictures were flashing the 151 years glorious time and romantic legend of Ernest Borel. A created night of Venus behind windows of Bund 3, overlooked the Huangpu River and the Bund. A night of be arty and wonder.

          Through the silence, Hong Kong star Ricky Chan&#39;s tap dance is like the tick-tack of a timepiece which started the show time of the Venus Night.

          On the back stage, with the Venus Collection watches around their wrists, the &#34;mermaids&#34; swimming in the smoky &#34;water&#34;, and a group of &#34;Venuses&#34; dressed in voile wearing anadem dancing lightly, romance and classic atmosphere rippled over the whole Bund 3. The bemazed audience nearly forgot it was a watch show, only impressed by the holly Goddesses and their lithe and graceful dancing. Then, the essence of elegance, romance, legend and fashion was spreading around the whole &#34;Athens City&#34;.

          Shining Stars and Celebrities

          Venus Night is also a night for celebrities and stars. This first Press of Renewed Duplicate Stereotype Limited Edition Wrist Watches attracted various celebrities and stars. They were as shining as the Venus Collection itself, together in this &#34;Athens City&#34;.

          The Hong Kong super star Ms Angie Chiu was the most shining queen of this Venus Night. She dressed up in a glorious Venus style make-ups and charmed all the audience at the Press. Angie claimed that the true &#34;Venus of the Night&#34; ought to be the Renewed Duplicate Stereotype Limited Edition Venus Collection itself.

          As the Ernest Borel Brand Ambassador, Ms Angie Chiu is beautiful and fashionable. Her timeless elegancy and grace matches the &#34;Beauty&#34; connotation of the Venus Collection perfectly. Her husband always stood by her during the whole night. Between whiles, the couple were eye contacting each other even they had been married for over decades.

          Unconsciously, Angie vividly interpreted the meaning of &#34;Love&#34; in Venus Collection through her own happy family life.

          Hong Kong stars Eddie Kwan Lai kit, Jackie Lui, Remus Choy and Timothy Zao specially attended this Press to show their support, and they were granted the Prize of &#34;Elegant Gentleman&#34; by Ernest Borel.

          Jess Zhang, Zhou Jin, Qi Wei also obtained prizes from Ernest Borel.

          Latest idol band GoGoClub (Zhong Kai, Chen Ze Yu, Wu Di Wen and Mao Fang Yuan) and Guoshuai in &#34;Prince&#34; costumes showed on the stage with three models in &#34;Princess&#34; costumes at the same time. &#34;Prince and Princess&#34; romantic story could be viewed by your eyes and not require any words.

          Every star presented their understanding of what is romance that night. There were several stars claimed if they could wear a Ernest Borel watch to record every second with their beloved, this idea itself was the most romantic thing already.

          Time Passes By, Classic Reappears
          Romantic moments always bring back memories. People who immerse in the Venus Night can not help searching for the story behind this romance.

          70 years ago, Swiss Ernest Borel designer Adamir Debrot took the Muse in his heart ---the ancient Greek myth Goddess &#34;Venus&#34; as inspiration created Venus Collection. &#34;Venus&#34; is the beautiful incarnation and love symbol, Adamir Debrot ingeniously shaped the enchanting contour with the beautiful connotation, integrating to the wrist watch design, modeling graceful unique and brief line exquisite concept, just like the lovers heart to heart embracing each other and their love legend.

          As soon as Venus Collection launched, it was favored and recommended widely amongst the celebrities then because of its unique design and craft. In the same year, Ernest Borel obtained and grand Prix honorary award in Greece, and became a symbol for elegance, romance, grace and classic.

          Time moves on while classic passes on. 70 years can change the world yet not change Ernest Borel heritage spirit. To continue the romance, to represent the glory and to salute at the outstanding original designer Adamir Debrot, Ernest Borel launches a renewed duplicate stereotype Venus Collection to recollect its enchanting charm of yester-years.

          The Renewed Duplicate Stereotype Limited Edition faithfully follows the original watch design, mixes the technology nowadays, 61 VVS1 natural dazzling diamonds on bezel, dial and buckle; elegant 18K rose gold watch case and buckle; feminine dark brown leather belt with silk surface. This collection design perfectly presents the elegant, meaningful and romantic style of the Ernest Borel watch, also endows the ladies who wear them with noble, fashionable and graceful flavor.

          There are only 700 Ernest Borel Renewed Duplicate Stereotype Limited Edition Wrist Watches of the Venus Collection for sale globally, of which 260 are available in China. Each 18K rose gold watchcase is marked by its unique individual serial number.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20070719_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20070428_1" date="2007-04-28" title="&#34;Ernest Borel Flagship Store Grand Opening Ceremony&#34;">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Swiss Ernest Borel has been famed for its serious production and elegant style of watches for over 150 years. In order to deliver the brand philosophy of A Lifelong Romantic Moment to Shenzhen, Ernest Borel held a simple but solemn ceremony celebrating the Flagship Store Opening at COCO Park in Fu Tian on 28th April, 2007. Mr. Kenny Bee was invited to perform a catwalk show demonstrating the brand watches with Ms. Vanessa Yeung and Ms. Rosemary Vandenbroucke, Hong Kong eminent models. The show has brought highlight to the ceremony.

          Ernest Borel has held the tradition of Kingdom of Watch, since 1856, to produce watches of unique style and excellent quality. The brand has established an extensive distribution network covering over 300 points throughout PRC. The setting up of a Flagship Store in COCO Park further signifies the determination of the brand to explore more local markets in China. The grand opening was made more special with a simple but meaningful ribbon cutting ceremony conducted by Mr. Kenny Bee, the Brand Ambassador, Mr. David Su, CEO (Asia Pacific Region) of Ernest Borel, and Mr. Lin Shao Wei, Managing Director of Modern World Watch and Clock Ltd. in Shenzhen.

          All the guests and audience were spotted enjoying the vibrant show atmosphere. The magnificent western music performance kick-started the Ceremony and the graceful Swan Lake Dance Show then lifted up the opening curtain. It was the first time that Mr. Kenny Bee was introduced as the Brand Ambassador to Shenzhen people and the media from various places of China. With the Hong Kong media, they witnessed this grand occasion. Kenny Bee, in ceremonial dress, thanked Ernest Borel for inviting him to be the Brand Ambassador. He said he would help advocating and promoting the dignified and elegant image of the brand in order to enlarge its market penetration in China.

          The ceremony was climaxed by the catwalk show graced by Ms. Vanessa Yeung and Ms. Rosemary Vandenbroucke, Hong Kong eminent models. Vanessa represented the Venus collection, Mermaid Series and Gary Series (leather strap) while Rosemary demonstrated the Danaus Series and Gary Series (steel strap). Their noble and modern deportment flawlessly revealed brand��s art of classical romance. Wearing the Majestic Collection, Kenny Bee met challenge with the two professional models on the flyover. The star turn of the show was the exhibition of the ��Legend of Romance�� Diamond Series commemorating the 150th anniversary by the three celebrities.

          Special Thanks to:
          Female model&#39;s wardrobe provided by LuLu Cheung
          Male model&#39;s wardrobe provided by BALLY]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20070428_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20070425_1" date="2007-04-25" title="Introduction to Ernest Borel Skeleton Automatic Mechanical Watch">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[You will actually experience the precision and magical actions of mechanical watch with Ernest Borel&#39;s skeleton automatic mechanical watch, such as the winding and release of spring, the high frequency of balance wheel oscillation, the elasticity of balance springs, the mystical escapement, the role implementation and systematic rotation of gears, the engagement and disengagement and time regulation of the clutch mechanism, and the way how the automatic mechanism relies on natural swinging of the wristwatch to make it wind, which in return delivers energy to the watch continuously. You will also see clearly each of the rubies that are bearing the rotating axes, and even the lubricant inside the watch. Ernest Borel&#39;s skeleton automatic mechanical watch defines the inner meaning of movement and time visually, and hence revokes people that time is precious. Mechanical watch does not only represent a visual art, but also enables interaction of minds and communication of emotions.

          Carving movement means carving as much as possible the bridges and other components of the movement without spoiling their functions and leaving only its skeleton. Carving movement requires a calm mind and exquisite technique. Any lapse will cause the previous hard work go down the drain. So each product is embodied with the painstaking efforts of the watchmakers. It is as if they are tending a new born baby scrupulously with all their concentration. Upon completion of carving, the watchmakers will polish the skeleton, and further engrave it with decorative strips. Polish and engraving procedures require real technical skills, craftsmanship and a great deal of time. The work is often accomplished with the help of a magnifier.

          Ernest Borel&#39;s skeleton watch employs a transparent dial scale. The perspective effect will not influence the accurate reading of time. The use of sapphire crystal enables you to appreciate the movement work from upside and downside. The perfect match of the steel 20 micron gilded case with the gold movement is the ingenious intelligence and magical techniques of the watchmakers. The watch is not only a fine timepiece, but also an artistic production.

          Global limited collection 1500 watches, each bearing a unique serial number.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20070425_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20070424_1" date="2007-04-24" title="Basel World 2007">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[ERNEST BOREL, the Swiss-based watch manufacturer has produced many watches over its long history, exhibited the latest creations and watches in Basel World 2007. The latest collection of Femininity ��Venus Collection��, which was come from the designer Adamir Debrot, who took the multitudinous artist mind and creativity with the ancient Greece myth Venus, designed Venus Collection in 1937. Venus is the beautiful incarnation and love symbol, Adamir Debrot ingeniously shaped the enchanting contour with the beautiful connotation, integrating to the wrist watch design, modeling graceful unique and brief line exquisite concept, just like the lovers heart to heart embracing each other. In the same year Ernest Borel obtained and Grand Prix honorary award in Greece.

          In 2007, in order to continue the concept of Romance in Heart and celebrating the 70th anniversary of Venus Collection, Ernest Borel launches a renewed duplicate stereotype Venus Collection, which is limited in edition, reappearing the old days European Romance in current modern generation. The duplicate stereotype faithful original watch design, mixes the technology nowadays, 61 VVS1 natural dazzling diamonds on bezel, dial and buckle; 18K rose gold watch case and buckle; dark brown leather belt with silk surface, each timepiece has its independent serial number. Limited edition with 700 pieces worldwide.

          In Basel World 2007, we also showcased 150th anniversary Romance Series, Majestic Collection, Gary Mermaid Series, Skelenton Automatic S etc, attracted many visitors from Europe, Russia, US, South Korea, Japan etc, they felt great interest in the timepieces and collected many information for futher business contacts. Besides, Miss Swiss 2006 Ms. Nadine Thalmann arrived our place during the exhibition, attracted many passers-by audience sticking around and asked for autographs.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20070424_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20070411_1" date="2007-04-11" title="Venus Collection Feminine, Romance &#38; Elegance">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Ernest Borel designer Adamir Debrot took the multitudinous artist mind and creativity with the ancient Greece myth &#34;Venus&#34;, designed Venus Collection in 1937. &#34;Venus&#34; is the beautiful incarnation and love symbol, Adamir Debrot ingeniously shaped the enchanting contour with the beautiful connotation, integrating to the wrist watch design, modeling graceful unique and brief line exquisite concept, just like the lovers heart to heart embracing each other. In the same year Ernest Borel obtained and Grand Prix honorary award in Greece.

          In 2007, in order to continue the concept of &#34;Romance in Heart&#34;, Ernest Borel launches a renewed duplicate stereotype Venus Collection, which is limited in edition, reappearing the old days European Romance in current modern generation. The duplicate stereotype faithful original watch design, mixes the technology nowadays, 61 VVS1 natural dazzling diamonds on bezel, dial and buckle; 18K rose gold watch case and buckle; dark brown leather belt with silk surface, each timepiece has its independent serial number. Limited edition with 700 pieces worldwide.

          Venus Collection presents the feminine and romance of Ernest Borel,
          clearly reveals the contemporary female&#39;s unique elegancy.

          Email : enquiry@Ernestborel.ch

          Website : http://www.Ernestborel.ch]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20070411_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20070211_1" date="2007-02-11" title="&#34;Everlasting Romance 2007&#34; Valentine&#39;s Day">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[The Grand Valentine&#39;s Day event &#34;Everlasting Romance 2007&#34; was held at Guangzhou Wangfujin Department Store on Feb 11, 2007 by Ernest Borel, renowned elegant watches from Switzerland. Ms Angie Chiu, the Brand Ambassador of Ernest Borel, shared with the audience her views towards romance and plans for Valentine&#39;s Day. In the romantic atmosphere, there were drama shows and foreign models&#39; catwalk introducing the latest masterpiece of Ernest Borel The Gary Series.

          Mr. Magic started the event, giving life to a pair of dancers to perform &#34;Dance of the Lovers&#34;. Ms. Grace Dan, famous anchor, acted as the Master of Ceremony. Mr. David Su, CEO (Asia Pacific) of Ernest Borel delivered a speech to introduce the latest romantic Gary Series, which matched perfectly with the romantic theme of Valentine&#39;s Day. Three couples representing the young, elderly and old age played in three acts of drama. Romance was not constrained to young people. Ernest Borel watches represented their everlasting love for their beloved ones.

          Ms. Angie Chiu brought the first climax of the day. Her appearance on stage raised the temperature immediately. She shared her views with Grace and VIPs towards romance and even her secret of how she would spend the romantic day with her husband, Mr. Melvin Wong. Mr. David Su stepped on stage again to host with Angie a simple ceremony of the launch of Gary Series.

          Foreign male and female models, dressed elegantly, exhibited the latest collections of Gary Series, Columbus Series, Majestic Collection, Romance Memorial Edition and Danaus Series. Finale of the show was a group photo session for Ms. Angie Chiu, Mr. David Su, Mr. Melvin Wong, and representatives from Ernest Borel and Guangzhou Wangfujin Department Store.

          Afterwards, Ms. Angie stepped inside the department store to Ernest Borel exhibition area with the help of more than 20 security guards. She was surrounded by thousands of passionate citizens of Guangzhou. Ms. Angie however was keeping her poise of elegance, smile and charm. Spectators surrounded the exhibition area while media was interviewing Angie. Media came not only from Guangzhou but also from Shenzhen, Hunan, Shanghai and Beijing.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20070211_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20070207_1" date="2007-02-07" title="Valentine&#39;s Pick - Danaus Series">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Swiss Ernest Borel, on this St. Valentine&#39;s Day, specially recommends her romantic and elegant Danaus Series that brings classical glamour to a visual and sensual space. Its simplicity matches flawlessly with the rose gold. The watch, named after Danaus, perfectly represents the classics and romance of the brand culture. Its light and slim style of design reveals a brand new vision. The rose gold plated numbers, case and hands do not only exhibit its high quality, but also effuse a sense of elegance. Stainless steel case, convex shaped sapphire crystal watch surface with a choice of black, white or gold dial provides you a selection of grace, ethereality and modesty.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20070207_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20070207_2" date="2007-02-07" title="Gary Mermaid Series (Model: GS8688C)">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Inspired by the fairy tale of The Pretty Mermaid, the designers of Ernest Borel designed the Gary Series that is perfectly integrated with classic and vogue. The pink or light purple watchstrap made of devil rays skin, together with the graceful barrel-shaped case, represent the utmost charm of intellectual women, while the frothy white dots portray the feminine elegance along with the liveliness. These features exactly echo with the theme of &#34;Born Pretty; Intelligence Glorifies Life&#34; of Miss Chinese Cosmos Pageant. Being the precious presents for Miss Chinese this year, Gary - Mermaid Series is able to manifest their special nature of possessing both inner intelligence and outer beauty.

          The Swiss made quartz Gary - Mermaid Series of Ernest Borel embraces 1/10 second, 60 second and 30 minutes counter functions. It features a sapphire crystal watch surface and 3 ATM water-resistant, giving a graceful appearance while implying a valuable cultivation. The artistic and functional Gary - Mermaid Series is a new product line integrated with fashionable idea and exquisite technique.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20070207_2">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20061101_1" date="2006-11-01" title="Ernest Borel Male Ambassador presents new Majestic Collection">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Ernest Borel has held a glamorous Prize Presentation Ceremony for the champions of 2006 Miss Chinese Cosmos Pageant and a Signing Ceremony for its Male Ambassador, Mr. Kenny Bee, at the Harbour Plaza Metropolis Hotel on 1 November, 2006. The brand new supremely elegant Majestic Collection has also been introduced at the occasion.

          Kenny Bee was delighted to become the Male Ambassador of Ernest Borel, a brand he always cherishes. He was thrilled to demonstrate the Majestic Collection to the guests. Ms. Angie Chiu, a long time Brand Ambassador, shared with him the pleasure she enjoyed working with it. Her elegant and lady image, loved by Hong Kong and Chinese people since Shanghai Bund, blends excellently with the renowned watch. Mr. Daniel Goy explained lively to the guests the qualities of the Majestic Collection. As yet another outstanding masterpiece of Ernest Borel, the Majestic Collection promises to enchant all watch lovers. It was named because each set of the timepieces is tested by C.O.S.C., and just like the noble knight, it summons respect, as much as pride and honor. The Series continues Ernest Borel&#39;s aesthetic design style and brand philosophy and fully exhibits through its extraordinary quality the knightly confidence, courage and might.

          In the Ernest Borel Press Conference &#38; 2006 Miss Chinese Cosmos Pageant Prize Presentation Ceremony, prestigious guests such as Miss Nadine Thalmann, Miss Beaute Romande 2006, Mr. Raphael Boillat, CEO of Ernest Borel, Mr. Daniel Goy, Assistant Chief Executive Officer &#38; Technical Director of Ernest Borel, have flown all the way from the paradise of elegant watches, Switzerland, to come to congratulate the winners of Miss Chinese Cosmos Pageant 2006, who have just won their crowns on 28 October 2006. Extravagant diamond watches were awarded to the oriental beauties. Chinese and western enchanting beauties grouped together in a stylized hotel function room, embedded in a European atmosphere.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20061101_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20061028_1" date="2006-10-28" title="Miss Chinese Cosmos Pageant Final Competition 2006">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Ernest Borel was assigned the Official Watch of Miss Chinese Cosmos Pageant Final Competition and Prize Presentation Ceremony 2006 that was hosted by Phoenix Satellite Television Company Limited and held in the Asia World Expo Hong Kong on 28th Oct. evening. In five different dance shows, the 12 beauties entering final had to partake in debate and be interviewed by the adjudicators. In the end of the keen contest, Echo Huang, No. 9 beauty, won the championship, while Ada Liu from Australia and Qiu Ye from Chong Qing clinched the 1st and 2nd runner-ups. Qiu Ye, Tong Bing Yu and Echo Huang were honoured the titles of Miss Photogenic, Miss Asian Culture and the Phoenix Network Popular Award respectively.

          The Ceremony was emceed by the Phoenix star presenters including Dou Wentao, Hu Yi Fu, Shen Xing, Jiang Sheng Yang and Yuchi Linjia. After delivering her farewell speech, Yolanda Li, champion of Miss Chinese Cosmos 2005, together with Mr. Liu Changle, JP, Chairman of Board and CEO of Phoenix, crowned the winner.

          The judging panel was formed by the celebrities from China, Taiwan and Hong Kong. They are Vivian Chow, a Hong Kong star, Cheung Siu Yin, a Taiwanese star presenter, Professor Chang Hsin Kang, Master of Hong Kong City University, Zhang Tie Lin, a film star from China, and Donnie Yan, an international famed Chinese kung-fu movie star.

          The Ceremony was spiced up by various shows. Harlem Yu from Taiwan sang the theme song ��Longer Than Forever�� composed by Chris Babida. Marsha Yuen, a new singer in Hong Kong, performed a dance play, while Chris Wong staged a Broadway Musical. Dorian Ho and Chris Babida were invited to be the Image Director and Music Director of the Ceremony respectively.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20061028_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20061026_1" date="2006-10-26" title="Majestic Collection Official Certified Chronometers...">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Each set of the latest Majestic Collection has passed the C.O.S.C. test and comes with its own C.O.S.C. Certificate of Precision in recognition of its Swiss officially certified movement. The movement and the case side of each watch are individually numbered corresponding to the certificate.

          Features:
          - Swiss automatic Chronometers movement
          - Elaborate polish
          - Geneva stripes
          - Rhodium plated
          - Month window
          - Week window
          - Date by centre hand
          - Moon phase
          - Power-reserve 42 h
          - Stainless steel case and bracelet
          - See-through back,
          - Sapphire crystal,
          - 5 ATM water-resistant

          Case number and see-through back

          C.O.S.C. Certificate of Precision and movement number

          Stamp and idiograph of C.O.S.C.

          Various angles show of Majestic Collection]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20061026_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20061017_1" date="2006-10-17" title="Miss Chinese Cosmos Pageant 2006">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Ernest Borel has been entitled as official watch sponsor of Miss Chinese Cosmos Pageant held by Phoenix TV for 4 years since 2003. As of the Swiss Made watch and 150th anniversary of Ernest Borel this year, we are pleased to sponsor an overseas visit for 26 finalists of Miss Chinese to Switzerland in Oct, and also as the place of its semi-final.

          During the visit, we tailor-made a series of Miss Chinese Gary Series for all 26 finalists, each watch&#39;s belt is specially made with skin of Devil Ray, the series has 5 colors, pearl, light blue, pink, brown and purple, which are very suitable for the elegant and prestige characteristics of Miss Chinese.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20061017_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20060909_1" date="2006-09-09" title="Ernest Borel Watch Show Open at Nanning">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Ravished by fall weather, the renowned Swiss Ernest Borel held the &#34;150 years of Romance Witness&#34; at the Dream Island Department Store in Nanning on 9th September, marking the opening of exhibition in Nanning, Guangxi, China. Miss Angie Chiu, the celebrity who possesses a unique romantic and graceful nature plus a generous mindset, carried out a modern performance on the historically decorated stage at the main entrance of the Department Store. Her show, embodying a gorgeous model casting in Ernest Borel&#39;s romantic story, drew attention of a large audience and fans.

          Nanning is the third stop, after Hong Kong and Guangzhou, of Ernest Borel exhibition in China. It was reported that Miss Angie Chiu presented as the Brand Ambassador to attend the Event. The reason that Angie was invited as the Brand Ambassador was due to her unique possession of romantic and graceful nature, elegant and modern image plus a generous mindset, which does not only harmonise with the romantic and everlasting brand philosophy of Ernest Borel, but also blends excellently with the brand advocation of A Lifelong Romantic Moment.

          Romance is always the brand theme Ernest Borel. On her 150th anniversary this year, Ernest Boreal exhibited her antique watches of 100 years old to the Chinese audience. These antique watches have experienced more than 100 years&#39; test and examination. They still reveal a great originality and the exquisite technique of Ernest Borel.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20060909_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20060514_1" date="2006-05-14" title="&#34;150 years of Romance Witness&#34;">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[Ernest Borel held the &#34;150 years of Romance Witness&#34; Flagship Store Opening at Zheng Jia Square and Start-up Ceremony of the Roving Exhibition in China areas at Zheng Jia Square, Guangzhou. Miss Angie Chiu, the super star who once cast in Shanghai Bund creating a fad throughout Asia, presented as the Brand Ambassador and witnessed this great romantic moment. On this day of celebration, the models wonderfully presented each of the classical watches on a georgeous stage. Their brilliant performance flawlessly expressed the impact and appeal of Ernest Borel.

          The significance of the opening of the flagship store at Zheng Jia Square and start-up of the roving exhibition is to demonstrate the Ernest Borel watches embodied with romantic culture and exquisite technique to the Chinese customers. If you love to live, you will be proud to own them for the whole life. In order to commemorate the 150th anniversary, Ernest Borel offered a limited collection of &#34;Legend of Romance&#34; for sale in China. Ernest Boreal would also exhibit her antique watches of 100 years old to the Chinese audience. These antique watches have experienced more than 100 years&#39; test and examination. They still reveal a great originality and the exquisite technique of Ernest Borel. You will fall for them.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20060514_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20060510_1" date="2006-05-10" title="Ernest Borel Celebrated 150th Anniversary">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[The renowned Ernest Borel recently celebrated her 150th anniversary at Tsim Sha Tsui. The star-studded party, hosted by Mr. Boillat, CEO (Switzerland) of Ernest Borel and Mr. David Su, Managing Director (Great China Region), welcomed the presence of Angie Chiu, Anthony Wong, Kenny B Chung, Bowie Lam, Joe Ma, Charmaine Sheh, Annie Lau and Emme Wong.

          As the venue was facing Victoria Harbour, the guests were able to appreciate the wonderful night view of Hong Kong, which created a festive atmosphere at the party. Miss Angie Chiu then led a catwalk show with some of the celebrities while Kenny B Chung, accompanied by a 10 men band, delivered 3 songs. The superb successfully shows livened up the air of the party.

          Miss Angie Chiu, who represents an image of romance and elegance, was announced to be the Brand Ambassador of Ernest Borel for China and Hong Kong region.

          Swiss Ernest Borel was founded by young Jules Borel in Switzerland. Having a history of 150 years, Ernest Borel always positions herself as &#34;romantic elegance&#34;, revealing an elegant and classic nature. &#34;Romance in Heart&#34; is the product and advertisement theme this year, expressing the concept that romance is a lifestyle. Miss Angie Chiu, being the Brand Ambassador of Ernest Borel, possesses a unique romantic and graceful nature plus a generous mindset. Her image does not only harmonise with the romantic and everlasting brand philosophy of Ernest Borel, but also blends excellently with the brand advocation of A Lifelong Romantic Moment.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20060510_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20060420_1" date="2006-04-20" title="The Ernest Borel &#34;Legend of Romance&#34;">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[The epitome of 150 years of chronological design philosophy, Ernest Borel&#39;s &#34;Legend of Romance&#34; collection is the crystallization of one and a half century of renowned watch-making culture.

          40 (0.39 carats) and 30 (0.23 carats) natural diamonds are hand-set into the bezels of the Man&#39;s and the Lady&#39;s watch respectively, composing a perfect symbol for life-long romance that eclipses even the tides of time. An automatic mechanism faithfully records every moment shared together. The finely crafted steel casing is complimented by a steel belt that bears Borel&#39;s unique &#34;Hand-in-hand&#34; design. Sapphire glass and heart-shaped transparent caseback looks through to the heart of romance. Engraved in blue, the number &#34;150&#34; bears witness to the romantic pursuit of watch-making perfection from 1856 to 2006. Individually numbered at the side of the watch, each set of timepieces comes in a delicate wooden box with Ernest Borel Certificates of Authenticity.

          Movement Parameter
          -ETA automatic mechanical movement
          -8,800 A/H, 4Hz
          -Bi-directional automatic winding
          -Ball bearing
          -25 Jewels
          -Incabloc
          -Centre hands for hours, minutes and seconds
          -Fine timing device and stop-second
          -Date window instantaneous date
          -Date corrector
          -Elaborate polish
          -Rhodium plated
          -Blue steel screw
          -5 ATM water-resistant]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20060420_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20051103_1" date="2005-11-03" title="Swiss Ernest Borel Romantic Show in Shanghai">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[On 2nd November, 2005, Swiss Ernest Borel held the &#34;2005 Miss Chinese Cosmos Pageant Prize Presentation Ceremony&#34; in Shanghai, specially awarded the extravagant diamond collections from Gary Series to the crown winner, 1st and 2nd runners-up.

          In order to perform a perfect show in Shanghai, Ernest Borel specially invited Miss Angie Chiu, the super star who cast as Feng Cheng Cheng, and Melvin Wong to join and travel Huang Pu Jiang together. The couple admired the romantic night view with Miss Chinese and the Ernest Borel team.

          The Ernest Borel officials together with the couple presented the prizes to the 1st Miss Chinese 2005. Romantic moment was freezed on the glamorous night view of Huang Pu Jiang that night.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20051103_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
		<news id="20051024_1" date="2005-10-24" title="2005 Miss Chinese Did Romantic Performance">
			<desc>
				<![CDATA[&#34;2006 Miss Chinese Cosmos Pageant Meeting&#34; and &#34;Launch of Swiss Ernest Borel &#39;Z&#39; Series&#34; were held at Xindongan Market in Wangfujing Avenue, Beijing on 24th Oct, 2005 (Final eve).

          After Mr. Boillat, CEO (Switzerland) of Ernest Borel and Mr. David Su, Managing Director (Great China Region) of Ernest Borel had delivered the opening speeches, 48 oriental beauties played an excellent &#34;Ernest Borel Watch Show&#34;. Each beauty, wearing a brand new &#34;Z&#34; Series watch, demonstrated their enchanting figures by means of T-shaped stage walk.

          The Z Series launched this time is a brand new collection of Ernest Borel. Revealing both vogue and elegance, each watch from Z Series carries a different production theme and presentation style. Each of the 18K gold cast watches is an individualised artistic creation.]]>
			</desc>
			<images>
				<image id="20051024_1">
					<![CDATA[]]>
				</image>
			</images>
		</news>
	</inactive>
</data>
